<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://ehsanedalat.github.io/securitynews/index.html</id>
    <title>News | S&amp;P Homepage</title>
    <updated>2023-06-13T01:36:28.756Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://ehsanedalat.github.io/securitynews/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://ehsanedalat.github.io/securitynews/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Report First Instance of Automated SaaS Ransomware Extortion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/researchers-report-first-instance-of-automated-saas-ransomware-extortion</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/researchers-report-first-instance-of-automated-saas-ransomware-extortion"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T22:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The attack highlights growing interest among threat actors to target data from software-as-a-service providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Loader Delivering Spyware via Image Steals Cryptocurrency Info]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/new-loader-delivering-spyware-via-image-steals-cryptocurrency-info</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/new-loader-delivering-spyware-via-image-steals-cryptocurrency-info"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T22:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sophisticated attackers are lacing malware into PNG image files in order to steal cryptocurrency and business information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use of Multifactor Authentication (MFA) Nearly Doubles Since 2020, Okta Secure Sign-in Trends Reports Finds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/use-of-multi-factor-authentication-mfa-nearly-doubles-since-2020-new-okta-secure-sign-in-trends-reports-finds</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/use-of-multi-factor-authentication-mfa-nearly-doubles-since-2020-new-okta-secure-sign-in-trends-reports-finds"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T20:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Okta platform data-based study finds FastPass and WebAuthn offer far stronger security and faster, more reliable user experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RomCom Threat Actor Targets Ukrainian Politicians, US Healthcare]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/romcom-threat-actor-targets-ukrainian-politicians-us-healthcare</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/romcom-threat-actor-targets-ukrainian-politicians-us-healthcare"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T19:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The group appears to be targeting victims based on their proximity and involvement to and within pro-Ukraine organizations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Eddy, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Important Security Tasks You Shouldn't Skip]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge/10-important-security-tasks-you-shouldn-t-skip</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge/10-important-security-tasks-you-shouldn-t-skip"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T19:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time and money are valuable and finite, but some actions are well worth spending those resources on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joshua Goldfarb, Security and Fraud Architect, F5</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Stealth Soldier' Attacks Target Libyan Government Entities With Surveillance Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/syealth-soldier-attacks-target-libyan-government-entities-surveillance-malware</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/syealth-soldier-attacks-target-libyan-government-entities-surveillance-malware"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T16:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Surveillance malware targets Libyan government entities, with possible links to a 2019 Egypt attack campaign.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Raywood, Senior Editor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supply Chain Attack Defense Demands Mature Threat Hunting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/supply-chain-attack-defense-threat-hunting-monitoring</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/supply-chain-attack-defense-threat-hunting-monitoring"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T16:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Active threat hunting is the best protection against supply chain attacks like MOVEit and 3CX, experts say.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Becky Bracken, Editor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6148-1: SNI Proxy vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6148-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6148-1"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T14:16:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was discovered that SNI Proxy did not properly handle wildcard backend
hosts. An attacker could possibly use this issue to cause a buffer overflow,
resulting in a denial of service, or arbitrary code execution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6157-1: GlusterFS vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6157-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6157-1"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T14:02:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tao Lyu discovered that GlusterFS did not properly handle certain event
notifications. An attacker could possibly use this issue to cause a denial
of service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doing Less With Less: Focusing on Value]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/doing-less-with-less-focusing-on-value</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/doing-less-with-less-focusing-on-value"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Always reach for defense in depth with proposed security changes. Measure and test results, focus on items of greatest impact, and get C-suite members involved to drive better outcomes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Johnson, Co-Founder and CTO, Obsidian Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Government Provides Guidance on Software Security Guarantee Requirements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=33949</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/us-government-provides-guidance-on-software-security-guarantee-requirements/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T12:52:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OMB has published new guidance on federal agencies obtaining security guarantees from software vendors.
The post US Government Provides Guidance on Software Security Guarantee Requirements appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Arghire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Uncover Publisher Spoofing Bug in Microsoft Visual Studio Installer]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/researchers-uncover-publisher-spoofing.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/researchers-uncover-publisher-spoofing.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T12:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security researchers have warned about an "easily exploitable" flaw in the Microsoft Visual Studio installer that could be abused by a malicious actor to impersonate a legitimate publisher and distribute malicious extensions.
"A threat actor could impersonate a popular publisher and issue a malicious extension to compromise a targeted system," Varonis researcher Dolev Taler said. "Malicious]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Charges Russians With Hacking Cryptocurrency Exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=33946</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/us-charges-russians-with-hacking-cryptocurrency-exchange/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T12:15:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two Russian nationals are charged in the US with hacking a cryptocurrency exchange and conspiring to launder the proceeds.
The post US Charges Russians With Hacking Cryptocurrency Exchange appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Arghire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6156-1: SSSD vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6156-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6156-1"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T12:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was discovered that SSSD incorrrectly sanitized certificate data used in
LDAP filters. When using this issue in combination with FreeIPA, a remote
attacker could possibly use this issue to escalate privileges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fortinet Releases Security Updates for FortiOS and FortiProxy]]></title>
        <id>/node/18315</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/06/12/fortinet-releases-security-updates-fortios-and-fortiproxy"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fortinet has released security updates to address a heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability CVE-2023-27997 in FortiOS and FortiProxy. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to take control of an affected system.
CISA encourages users and administrators to review Fortinet security advisory FG-IR-23-097 and apply the necessary updates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6155-1: Requests vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6155-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6155-1"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T11:54:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dennis Brinkrolf and Tobias Funke discovered that Requests incorrectly
leaked Proxy-Authorization headers. A remote attacker could possibly use
this issue to obtain sensitive information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6154-1: Vim vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6154-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6154-1"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T11:33:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was discovered that Vim was using uninitialized memory when fuzzy
matching, which could lead to invalid memory access. An attacker could
possibly use this issue to cause a denial of service or execute arbitrary
code. This issue only affected Ubuntu 22.04 LTS, Ubuntu 22.10 and Ubuntu
23.04. (CVE-2023-2426)

It was discovered that Vim was not properly performing bounds checks when
processing register contents, which could lead to a NULL pointer
dereference. An attacker could possibly use this issue to cause a denial
of service or execute arbitrary code. (CVE-2023-2609)

It was discovered that Vim was not properly limiting the length of
substitution expression strings, which could lead to excessive memory
consumption. An attacker could possibly use this issue to cause a denial
of service. (CVE-2023-2610)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI-Generated Steganography]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/06/ai-generated-steganography.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/06/ai-generated-steganography.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T11:18:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2210.14889">New research</a> suggests that AIs can produce perfectly secure steganographic images:</p>
<blockquote><p><b>Abstract:</b> Steganography is the practice of encoding secret information into innocuous content in such a manner that an adversarial third party would not realize that there is hidden meaning. While this problem has classically been studied in security literature, recent advances in generative models have led to a shared interest among security and machine learning researchers in developing scalable steganography techniques. In this work, we show that a steganography procedure is perfectly secure under Cachin (1998)&#8217;s information theoretic-model of steganography if and only if it is induced by a coupling. Furthermore, we show that, among perfectly secure procedures, a procedure is maximally efficient if and only if it is induced by a minimum entropy coupling. These insights yield what are, to the best of our knowledge, the first steganography algorithms to achieve perfect security guarantees with non-trivial efficiency; additionally, these algorithms are highly scalable. To provide empirical validation, we compare a minimum entropy coupling-based approach to three modern baselines&#8212;arithmetic coding, Meteor, and adaptive dynamic grouping&#8212;using GPT-2, WaveRNN, and Image Transformer as communication channels. We find that the minimum entropy coupling-based approach achieves superior encoding efficiency, despite its stronger security constraints. In aggregate, these results suggest that it may be natural to view information-theoretic steganography through the lens of minimum entropy coupling...</p></blockquote>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intellihartx Informs 490k Patients of GoAnywhere-Related Data Breach]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=33941</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/intellihartx-informs-490k-patients-of-goanywhere-related-data-breach/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T11:03:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intellihartx says the personal information of roughly 490,000 individuals was compromised in the GoAnywhere zero-day attack earlier this year.
The post Intellihartx Informs 490k Patients of GoAnywhere-Related Data Breach appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Arghire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Software Supply Chain: The Golden Container Ship]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=33943</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/software-supply-chain-the-golden-container-ship/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By having a golden image you will put a process in place that allows you to quickly take action when a vulnerability is found within your organization.
The post Software Supply Chain: The Golden Container Ship appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Honea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New MOVEit Vulnerabilities Found as More Zero-Day Attack Victims Come Forward]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=33939</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/new-moveit-vulnerabilities-found-as-more-zero-day-attack-victims-come-forward/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T10:26:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers discover new MOVEit vulnerabilities related to the zero-day, just as more organizations hit by the attack are coming forward.
The post New MOVEit Vulnerabilities Found as More Zero-Day Attack Victims Come Forward appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eduard Kovacs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Now? The Rise of Attack Surface Management]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/why-now-rise-of-attack-surface.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/why-now-rise-of-attack-surface.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T10:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The term "attack surface management" (ASM) went from unknown to ubiquitous in the cybersecurity space over the past few years. Gartner and Forrester have both highlighted the importance of ASM recently, multiple solution providers have emerged in the space, and investment and acquisition activity have seen an uptick. 
Many concepts come and go in cybersecurity, but attack surface management]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybercriminals Using Powerful BatCloak Engine to Make Malware Fully Undetectable]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/cybercriminals-using-powerful-batcloak.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/cybercriminals-using-powerful-batcloak.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T10:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A fully undetectable (FUD) malware obfuscation engine named BatCloak is being used to deploy various malware strains since September 2022, while persistently evading antivirus detection.
The samples grant "threat actors the ability to load numerous malware families and exploits with ease through highly obfuscated batch files," Trend Micro researchers said.
About 79.6% of the total 784 artifacts]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Swiss Fear Government Data Stolen in Cyberattack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=33938</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/swiss-fear-government-data-stolen-in-cyberattack/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T09:59:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Switzerland said government operational data might have been stolen in a ransomware attack on a technology firm that provides software for several departments.
The post Swiss Fear Government Data Stolen in Cyberattack appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AFP</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fortinet Patches Critical FortiGate SSL VPN Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=33936</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/fortinet-patches-critical-fortigate-ssl-vpn-vulnerability/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T08:27:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fortinet has patched CVE-2023-27997, a critical FortiGate SSL VPN vulnerability that can be exploited for unauthenticated remote code execution. 
The post Fortinet Patches Critical FortiGate SSL VPN Vulnerability appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eduard Kovacs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Password Reset Hack Exposed in Honda's E-Commerce Platform, Dealers Data at Risk]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/password-reset-hack-exposed-in-hondas-e.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/password-reset-hack-exposed-in-hondas-e.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T08:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security vulnerabilities discovered in Honda's e-commerce platform could have been exploited to gain unrestricted access to sensitive dealer information.
"Broken/missing access controls made it possible to access all data on the platform, even when logged in as a test account," security researcher Eaton Zveare said in a report published last week.
The platform is designed for the sale of power]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beware: 1,000+ Fake Cryptocurrency Sites Trap Users in Bogus Rewards Scheme]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/beware-1000-fake-cryptocurrency-sites.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/beware-1000-fake-cryptocurrency-sites.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T07:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A previously undetected cryptocurrency scam has leveraged a constellation of over 1,000 fraudulent websites to ensnare users into a bogus rewards scheme since at least January 2021.
"This massive campaign has likely resulted in thousands of people being scammed worldwide," Trend Micro researchers said in a report published last week, linking it to a Russian-speaking threat actor named "Impulse]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical RCE Flaw Discovered in Fortinet FortiGate Firewalls - Patch Now!]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/critical-rce-flaw-discovered-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/critical-rce-flaw-discovered-in.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T06:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fortinet has released patches to address a critical security flaw in its FortiGate firewalls that could be abused by a threat actor to achieve remote code execution.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2023-27997, is "reachable pre-authentication, on every SSL VPN appliance," Lexfo Security researcher Charles Fol, who discovered and reported the flaw, said in a tweet over the weekend.
Details]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple's Safari Private Browsing Now Automatically Removes Tracking Parameters in URLs]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/apples-safari-private-browsing-now.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/apples-safari-private-browsing-now.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T04:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple is introducing major updates to Safari Private Browsing, offering users better protections against third-party trackers as they browse the web.
"Advanced tracking and fingerprinting protections go even further to help prevent websites from using the latest techniques to track or identify a user's device," the iPhone maker said.
"Private Browsing now locks when not in use, allowing a user]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6153-1: Jupyter Core vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6153-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6153-1"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T00:23:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was discovered that Jupyter Core executed untrusted files in the current
working directory. An attacker could possibly use this issue to execute
arbitrary code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New SPECTRALVIPER Backdoor Targeting Vietnamese Public Companies]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/new-spectralviper-backdoor-targeting.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/new-spectralviper-backdoor-targeting.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-10T12:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vietnamese public companies have been targeted as part of an ongoing campaign that deploys a novel backdoor called SPECTRALVIPER.
"SPECTRALVIPER is a heavily obfuscated, previously undisclosed, x64 backdoor that brings PE loading and injection, file upload and download, file and directory manipulation, and token impersonation capabilities," Elastic Security Labs said in a Friday report.
The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Critical MOVEit Transfer SQL Injection Vulnerabilities Discovered - Patch Now!]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/new-critical-moveit-transfer-sql.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/new-critical-moveit-transfer-sql.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-10T08:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Progress Software, the company behind the MOVEit Transfer application, has released patches to address brand new SQL injection vulnerabilities affecting the file transfer solution that could enable the theft of sensitive information.
"Multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities have been identified in the MOVEit Transfer web application that could allow an unauthenticated attacker to gain]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Passkeys See Fresh Momentum With New Pilot Programs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/apple-and-google-expand-support-for-passkeys</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/apple-and-google-expand-support-for-passkeys"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T23:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple adds API that will enable sharing of passkeys across platforms, and Google offers passkey authentication in beta for Google Workspace and Google Cloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey Schwartz, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friday Squid Blogging: Light-Emitting Squid]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/06/friday-squid-blogging-light-emitting-squid.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/06/friday-squid-blogging-light-emitting-squid.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T21:05:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s a <a href="https://nautil.us/the-mystery-of-the-largest-light-in-the-sea-308189/"><i>Taningia danae</i></a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>Their arms are lined with two rows of sharp retractable hooks. And, like most deep-sea squid, they are adorned with light organs called photophores. They have some on the underside of their mantle. There are more facing upward, near one of their eyes. But it’s the photophores at the tip of two stubby arms that are truly unique. The size and shape of lemons­&#8212;each nestled within a retractable lid like an eyeball in a socket­&#8212;they are by far the largest photophores known to science.</p></blockquote>
<p>As usual, you can also use this squid post to talk about the security stories in the news that I haven’t covered...</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOS Attacks Dominate, but System Intrusions Cause Most Pain]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/dos-attacks-dominate-but-system-intrusions-cause-most-pain</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/dos-attacks-dominate-but-system-intrusions-cause-most-pain"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T21:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the latest Verizon "Data Breach Investigations Report," denial-of-service attacks are the most common type of security incident, but when it comes to breaches, nearly four-in-ten attackers compromise systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Lemos, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brand-New Security Bugs Affect All MOVEit Transfer Versions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/brand-new-security-bugs-affect-all-moveit-transfer-versions</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/brand-new-security-bugs-affect-all-moveit-transfer-versions"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T20:45:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Progress has issued a second patch for additional SQL flaws that are distinct from the zero-day that the Cl0p ransomware gang is exploiting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Asylum Ambuscade' Cyberattackers Blend Financial Heists & Cyber Espionage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/asylum-ambuscade-cyberattackers-financial-cyber-espionage</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/asylum-ambuscade-cyberattackers-financial-cyber-espionage"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T20:12:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a rare mix of motivations, the cyberattack group has been linked to both financial cybercrime and political spying efforts on governments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tara Seals, Managing Editor, News, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 Elite Communication Skills to Help Security Pros Get Projects Funded]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge/3-elite-communication-skills-to-help-security-pros-get-projects-funded</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge/3-elite-communication-skills-to-help-security-pros-get-projects-funded"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T19:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's not enough to know how to better protect the enterprise — you have to be able to convince decision-makers that your plans are necessary.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Shelton, CEO, Green Shoe Consulting</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cl0P Gang Sat on Exploit for MOVEit Flaw for Nearly 2 Years]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/cl0p-gang-exploit-moveit-flaw-2-years</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/cl0p-gang-exploit-moveit-flaw-2-years"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T16:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over that time, the group carried multiple tests to see if the exploit worked and to identify potential victims. It was like "turning the doorknob" to check for access, a researcher says.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Uncovers Banking AitM Phishing and BEC Attacks Targeting Financial Giants]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/microsoft-uncovers-banking-aitm.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/microsoft-uncovers-banking-aitm.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T15:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Banking and financial services organizations are the targets of a new multi-stage adversary-in-the-middle (AitM) phishing and business email compromise (BEC) attack, Microsoft has revealed.
"The attack originated from a compromised trusted vendor and transitioned into a series of AiTM attacks and follow-on BEC activity spanning multiple organizations," the tech giant disclosed in a Thursday]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South African Female Students Offered Cyber Scholarship]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/south-african-female-students-cyber-scholarships</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/south-african-female-students-cyber-scholarships"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T15:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Women of color are being offered a scholarship opportunity in South Africa — the offer will cover costs for pursuing a cyber career and encourage greater diversity of those studying cybersecurity courses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Other News: AI Regulation, Layoffs, US Aerospace Attacks, Post-Quantum Encryption]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=33932</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/in-other-news-ai-regulation-layoffs-us-aerospace-attacks-post-quantum-encryption/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T15:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity news that you may have missed this week: AI regulation, layoffs, US aerospace malware attacks, and post-quantum encryption. 
The post In Other News: AI Regulation, Layoffs, US Aerospace Attacks, Post-Quantum Encryption appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eduard Kovacs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Tips for Modernizing Your Security Operations Center Strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/5-tips-for-modernizing-your-security-operations-center-strategy</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/5-tips-for-modernizing-your-security-operations-center-strategy"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A solid, dependable SOC strategy that is scalable in the face of various security threats is essential to reduce cybersecurity risks to your business.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hollister, CISO, LogRhythm; VP, LogRhythm Labs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asylum Ambuscade: A Cybercrime Group with Espionage Ambitions]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/asylum-ambuscade-cybercrime-group-with.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/asylum-ambuscade-cybercrime-group-with.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T13:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actor known as Asylum Ambuscade has been observed straddling cybercrime and cyber espionage operations since at least early 2020.
"It is a crimeware group that targets bank customers and cryptocurrency traders in various regions, including North America and Europe," ESET said in an analysis published Thursday. "Asylum Ambuscade also does espionage against government entities in Europe]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Continuous Monitoring and Threat Intel Can Help Prevent Ransomware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/microsoft/how-continuous-monitoring-and-threat-intel-can-help-prevent-ransomware</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/microsoft/how-continuous-monitoring-and-threat-intel-can-help-prevent-ransomware"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T13:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security teams should be empowered with the right amount of intelligence to track new and emerging threats and connect that intel to historical data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Microsoft Security, Microsoft</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blackpoint Raises $190 Million to Help MSPs Combat Cyber Threats]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=33931</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/blackpoint-raises-190-million-to-help-msps-combat-cyber-threats/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T12:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blackpoint Cyber raises $190 million in a growth funding round led by Bain Capital Tech Opportunities.
The post Blackpoint Raises $190 Million to Help MSPs Combat Cyber Threats appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Arghire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Introduces SAIF, a Framework for Secure AI Development and Use]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=33929</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/google-introduces-saif-a-framework-for-secure-ai-development-and-use/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Google SAIF (Secure AI Framework) is designed to provide a security framework or ecosystem for the development, use and protection of AI systems.
The post Google Introduces SAIF, a Framework for Secure AI Development and Use appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Townsend</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Reasons Why Access Management is the Key to Securing the Modern Workplace]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/5-reasons-why-access-management-is-key.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/5-reasons-why-access-management-is-key.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T11:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The way we work has undergone a dramatic transformation in recent years. We now operate within digital ecosystems, where remote work and the reliance on a multitude of digital tools is the norm rather than the exception. This shift – as you likely know from your own life – has led to superhuman levels of productivity that we wouldn't ever want to give up. But moving fast comes at a cost. And for]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Operation Triangulation: Zero-Click iPhone Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/06/operation-triangulation-zero-click-iphone-malware.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/06/operation-triangulation-zero-click-iphone-malware.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T11:12:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Kaspersky is <a href="https://securelist.com/operation-triangulation/109842/">reporting</a> a zero-click iOS exploit in the wild:</p>
<blockquote><p>Mobile device backups contain a partial copy of the filesystem, including some of the user data and service databases. The timestamps of the files, folders and the database records allow to roughly reconstruct the events happening to the device. The mvt-ios utility produces a sorted timeline of events into a file called &#8220;timeline.csv,&#8221; similar to a super-timeline used by conventional digital forensic tools.</p>
<p>Using this timeline, we were able to identify specific artifacts that indicate the compromise. This allowed to move the research forward, and to reconstruct the general infection sequence:...</p></blockquote>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stealth Soldier: A New Custom Backdoor Targets North Africa with Espionage Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/stealth-soldier-new-custom-backdoor.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/stealth-soldier-new-custom-backdoor.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T05:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new custom backdoor dubbed Stealth Soldier has been deployed as part of a set of highly-targeted espionage attacks in North Africa.
"Stealth Soldier malware is an undocumented backdoor that primarily operates surveillance functions such as file exfiltration, screen and microphone recording, keystroke logging and stealing browser information," cybersecurity company Check Point said in a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[City of Dallas Still Clawing Back Weeks After Cyber Incident]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/ics-ot/city-of-dallas-clawing-back-to-recovery-following-cyber-incident</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/ics-ot/city-of-dallas-clawing-back-to-recovery-following-cyber-incident"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Texas city's networks have returned to 90% functionality following the May 3 Royal ransomware attack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6152-1: Linux kernel (GKE) regression]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6152-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6152-1"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T22:48:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was discovered that NFS client's access cache implementation in the
Linux kernel caused a severe NFS performance degradation in certain
conditions. This updated makes the NFS file-access stale cache behavior
to be optional.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6151-1: Linux kernel (Xilinx ZynqMP) vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6151-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6151-1"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T22:16:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was discovered that the System V IPC implementation in the Linux kernel
did not properly handle large shared memory counts. A local attacker could
use this to cause a denial of service (memory exhaustion). (CVE-2021-3669)

It was discovered that the KVM VMX implementation in the Linux kernel did
not properly handle indirect branch prediction isolation between L1 and L2
VMs. An attacker in a guest VM could use this to expose sensitive
information from the host OS or other guest VMs. (CVE-2022-2196)

Gerald Lee discovered that the USB Gadget file system implementation in the
Linux kernel contained a race condition, leading to a use-after-free
vulnerability in some situations. A local attacker could use this to cause
a denial of service (system crash) or possibly execute arbitrary code.
(CVE-2022-4382)

It was discovered that the RNDIS USB driver in the Linux kernel contained
an integer overflow vulnerability. A local attacker with physical access
could plug in a malicious USB device to cause a denial of service (system
crash) or possibly execute arbitrary code. (CVE-2023-23559)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6150-1: Linux kernel vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6150-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6150-1"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T21:55:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Patryk Sondej and Piotr Krysiuk discovered that a race condition existed in
the netfilter subsystem of the Linux kernel when processing batch requests,
leading to a use-after-free vulnerability. A local attacker could use this
to cause a denial of service (system crash) or possibly execute arbitrary
code. (CVE-2023-32233)

Gwangun Jung discovered that the Quick Fair Queueing scheduler
implementation in the Linux kernel contained an out-of-bounds write
vulnerability. A local attacker could use this to cause a denial of service
(system crash) or possibly execute arbitrary code. (CVE-2023-31436)

Reima Ishii discovered that the nested KVM implementation for Intel x86
processors in the Linux kernel did not properly validate control registers
in certain situations. An attacker in a guest VM could use this to cause a
denial of service (guest crash). (CVE-2023-30456)

It was discovered that the Broadcom FullMAC USB WiFi driver in the Linux
kernel did not properly perform data buffer size validation in some
situations. A physically proximate attacker could use this to craft a
malicious USB device that when inserted, could cause a denial of service
(system crash) or possibly expose sensitive information. (CVE-2023-1380)

Jean-Baptiste Cayrou discovered that the shiftfs file system in the Ubuntu
Linux kernel contained a race condition when handling inode locking in some
situations. A local attacker could use this to cause a denial of service
(kernel deadlock). (CVE-2023-2612)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuSecure Awarded US Army Contract for Post-Quantum Cybersecurity Solutions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/risk/qusecure-awarded-us-army-contract-for-post-quantum-cybersecurity-solutions</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/risk/qusecure-awarded-us-army-contract-for-post-quantum-cybersecurity-solutions"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T21:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[United States Army with QuSecure advances toward a quantum-resilient future protecting the country from today and tomorrow's cybersecurity threats.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybercrooks Scrape OpenAI API Keys to Pirate GPT-4]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/cybercrooks-scrape-openai-keys-pirate-gpt-4</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/cybercrooks-scrape-openai-keys-pirate-gpt-4"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T21:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With more than 50,000 publicly leaked OpenAI keys on GitHub alone, OpenAI developer accounts are the third-most exposed in the world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity Institute to Open in Saudi Arabia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/cybersecurity-institute-set-for-saudi-arabia</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/cybersecurity-institute-set-for-saudi-arabia"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T20:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Global Cybersecurity Forum branch, which will be in Riyadh, is meant to enable the exchange of ideas and facilitate international projects and partnerships.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Barracuda Warns ESG Appliances Need Urgent Rip & Replace]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/barracuda-warns-all-esg-appliances-need-urgent-rip-and-replace-</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/barracuda-warns-all-esg-appliances-need-urgent-rip-and-replace-"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T18:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Patching, wiping ESG devices not enough to deny threat actor access following compromise, Barracuda says.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Becky Bracken, Editor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Growing Cyber Threats of Generative AI: Who's Accountable?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/growing-cyber-threats-of-generative-ai-who-is-accountable</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/growing-cyber-threats-of-generative-ai-who-is-accountable"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the wrong hands, malicious actors can use chatbots to unleash sophisticated cyberattacks that could have devastating consequences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zia Muhammad, Ph.D. Scholar, North Dakota State University</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sophisticated 'Impulse Project' Crypto Scam Sprawls With 1,000 Affiliate Sites]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/sophisticated-crypto-scam-sprawls-1000-affiliate-sites</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/sophisticated-crypto-scam-sprawls-1000-affiliate-sites"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T15:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ready-to-defraud turnkey services from Russia's Impulse Team are offered on the cyber underground and have built a campaign that has operated undetected dating back to 2016.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Becky Bracken, Editor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Experts Unveil Exploit for Recent Windows Vulnerability Under Active Exploitation]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/experts-unveil-poc-exploit-for-recent.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/experts-unveil-poc-exploit-for-recent.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T14:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Details have emerged about a now-patched actively exploited security flaw in Microsoft Windows that could be abused by a threat actor to gain elevated privileges on affected systems.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2023-29336, is rated 7.8 for severity and concerns an elevation of privilege bug in the Win32k component.
"An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could gain]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6149-1: Linux kernel vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6149-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6149-1"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T14:43:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Patryk Sondej and Piotr Krysiuk discovered that a race condition existed in
the netfilter subsystem of the Linux kernel when processing batch requests,
leading to a use-after-free vulnerability. A local attacker could use this
to cause a denial of service (system crash) or possibly execute arbitrary
code. (CVE-2023-32233)

Gwangun Jung discovered that the Quick Fair Queueing scheduler
implementation in the Linux kernel contained an out-of-bounds write
vulnerability. A local attacker could use this to cause a denial of service
(system crash) or possibly execute arbitrary code. (CVE-2023-31436)

Reima Ishii discovered that the nested KVM implementation for Intel x86
processors in the Linux kernel did not properly validate control registers
in certain situations. An attacker in a guest VM could use this to cause a
denial of service (guest crash). (CVE-2023-30456)

It was discovered that the Broadcom FullMAC USB WiFi driver in the Linux
kernel did not properly perform data buffer size validation in some
situations. A physically proximate attacker could use this to craft a
malicious USB device that when inserted, could cause a denial of service
(system crash) or possibly expose sensitive information. (CVE-2023-1380)

It was discovered that the Human Interface Device (HID) support driver in
the Linux kernel contained a type confusion vulnerability in some
situations. A local attacker could use this to cause a denial of service
(system crash). (CVE-2023-1073)

Wei Chen discovered that the DVB USB AZ6027 driver in the Linux kernel
contained a null pointer dereference when handling certain messages from
user space. A local attacker could use this to cause a denial of service
(system crash). (CVE-2023-28328)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fighting AI-Powered Fraud: Let the Battle of the Machines Begin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/fighting-ai-powered-fraud-let-the-battle-of-the-machines-begin</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/fighting-ai-powered-fraud-let-the-battle-of-the-machines-begin"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As cybercriminals tap the power of machine learning and generative AI to outwit fraud-detection systems, online fraud-prevention technologies must evolve accordingly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dr. Ananth Gundabattula, Co-Founder, Darwinium</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clop Ransomware Gang Likely Aware of MOVEit Transfer Vulnerability Since 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/clop-ransomware-gang-likely-exploiting.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/clop-ransomware-gang-likely-exploiting.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T13:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) and Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) have published a joint advisory regarding the active exploitation of a recently disclosed critical flaw in Progress Software's MOVEit Transfer application to drop ransomware.
"The Cl0p Ransomware Gang, also known as TA505, reportedly began exploiting a previously unknown SQL injection]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Easily Exploitable Microsoft Visual Studio Bug Opens Developers to Takeover]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/researchers-warn-of-easily-exploitable-spoofing-bug-in-visual-studio</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/researchers-warn-of-easily-exploitable-spoofing-bug-in-visual-studio"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T13:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bug is very dangerous and impacts a big swath of the developer community, researchers warn.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[60K+ Android Apps Have Delivered Adware Undetected for Months]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/60k-android-apps-adware-undetected-months</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/60k-android-apps-adware-undetected-months"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T12:18:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A campaign targeting mainly US users disguised malware in fake security software, game cracks, cheats, free Netflix, and other "modded" apps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Montalbano, Contributor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Releases Two Industrial Control Systems Advisories]]></title>
        <id>/node/18303</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/06/08/cisa-releases-two-industrial-control-systems-advisories"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CISA released two Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisories on June 8, 2023. These advisories provide timely information about current security issues, vulnerabilities, and exploits surrounding ICS. 
ICSA-23-159-01 ​Atlas Copco Power Focus 6000 
ICSA-23-159-02 ​Sensormatic Electronics Illustra Pro Gen 4
CISA encourages users and administrators to review the newly released ICS advisories for technical details and mitigations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VMware Releases Security Update for Aria Operations for Networks]]></title>
        <id>/node/18299</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/06/08/vmware-releases-security-update-aria-operations-networks"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VMware has released a security update to address multiple vulnerabilities in Aria Operations for Networks (Formerly vRealize Network Insight). The vulnerabilities were evaluated to fall within the critical severity range, as a malicious actor with network access may be able to perform a command injection attack resulting in remote code execution. Patches have been made available to remediate the vulnerabilities found in VMWare products. 
VMSA-2023-0012 and apply the necessary updates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paragon Solutions Spyware: Graphite]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/06/paragon-solutions-spyware-graphite.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/06/paragon-solutions-spyware-graphite.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T11:30:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Paragon Solutions is yet another <a href="https://www.ft.com/content/11cb394d-a13e-4826-b580-823b9367fedb">Israeli spyware company</a>. Their product is called &#8220;Graphite,&#8221; and is a lot like NSO Group&#8217;s Pegasus. And Paragon is working with what seems to be US approval:</p>
<blockquote><p>American approval, even if indirect, has been at the heart of Paragon&#8217;s strategy. The company sought a list of allied nations that the US wouldn&#8217;t object to seeing deploy Graphite. People with knowledge of the matter suggested 35 countries are on that list, though the exact nations involved could not be determined. Most were in the EU and some in Asia, the people said...</p></blockquote>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Improve Your API Security Posture]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/how-to-improve-your-api-security-posture.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/how-to-improve-your-api-security-posture.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T11:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[APIs, more formally known as application programming interfaces, empower apps and microservices to communicate and share data. However, this level of connectivity doesn't come without major risks. Hackers can exploit vulnerabilities in APIs to gain unauthorized access to sensitive data or even take control of the entire system. Therefore, it's essential to have a robust API security posture to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hey Yara, find some vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>/blog/2023/06/hey-yara-find-some-vulnerabilities/</id>
        <link href="https://msrc-blog.microsoft.com/blog/2023/06/hey-yara-find-some-vulnerabilities/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intro Intro Finding vulnerabilities in software is no easy task by itself. Doing this at cloud scale is very challenging to perform manually, and we use tools to help us identify patterns or vulnerability signatures. Yara is one of those tools.
Yara is a very popular tool with Blue teams, malware researchers, and for good reason.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Microsoft Security Response Center</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Urgent Security Updates: Cisco and VMware Address Critical Vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/urgent-security-updates-cisco-and.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/urgent-security-updates-cisco-and.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T05:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VMware has released security updates to fix a trio of flaws in Aria Operations for Networks that could result in information disclosure and remote code execution.
The most critical of the three vulnerabilities is a command injection vulnerability tracked as CVE-2023-20887 (CVSS score: 9.8) that could allow a malicious actor with network access to achieve remote code execution.
Also patched by]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kimsuky Targets Think Tanks and News Media with Social Engineering Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/kimsuky-targets-think-tanks-and-news.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/kimsuky-targets-think-tanks-and-news.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T04:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The North Korean nation-state threat actor known as Kimsuky has been linked to a social engineering campaign targeting experts in North Korean affairs with the goal of stealing Google credentials and delivering reconnaissance malware.
"Further, Kimsuky's objective extends to the theft of subscription credentials from NK News," cybersecurity firm SentinelOne said in a report shared with The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Barracuda Urges Immediate Replacement of Hacked ESG Appliances]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/barracuda-urges-immediate-replacement.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/barracuda-urges-immediate-replacement.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T03:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enterprise security company Barracuda is now urging customers who were impacted by a recently disclosed zero-day flaw in its Email Security Gateway (ESG) appliances to immediately replace them.
"Impacted ESG appliances must be immediately replaced regardless of patch version level," the company said in an update, adding its "remediation recommendation at this time is full replacement of the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BioCatch Strengthens Collaboration With Microsoft Cloud for Financial Services]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/biocatch-strengthens-collaboration-with-microsoft-cloud-for-financial-services</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/biocatch-strengthens-collaboration-with-microsoft-cloud-for-financial-services"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T22:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Collaboration delivers end-to-end intelligent banking cloud platform with online fraud detection powered by next-generation behavioral biometrics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BeyondID Launches Initiative to Accelerate Zero Trust With Okta Identity Engine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/beyondid-launches-initiative-to-accelerate-zero-trust-with-okta-identity-engine</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/beyondid-launches-initiative-to-accelerate-zero-trust-with-okta-identity-engine"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T21:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OIE upgrade roadmap helps organizations become more secure; saves time, resources.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Radiflow's CIARA 4.0 Delivers Actionable Insights to Simplify the Management of OT Cyber-Risk at Industrial Facilities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/ics-ot/radiflow-s-ciara-4-0-delivers-actionable-insights-to-simplify-the-management-of-ot-cyber-risk-at-industrial-facilities</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/ics-ot/radiflow-s-ciara-4-0-delivers-actionable-insights-to-simplify-the-management-of-ot-cyber-risk-at-industrial-facilities"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T21:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CIARA V4.0 boosts compliance with security regulations and best practices while providing effective mitigation guidance. "CISOs are doing more with less, making it challenging to understand their current standing across the OT Cybersecurity landscape," said Ilan Barda, Radiflow CEO and co-founder.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Minecraft Malware Spreading Through Mods, Plug-ins]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/minecraft-malware-spreading-mods-plugins</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/minecraft-malware-spreading-mods-plugins"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T21:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A worm virus called "fracturizer" has been embedded in modpacks from various sites, including CurseForge and CraftBukkit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cl0p Claims the MOVEit Attack; Here's How the Gang Did It]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/cl0p-claims-moveit-attack-how-gang-did-it</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/cl0p-claims-moveit-attack-how-gang-did-it"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T20:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A researcher guides Dark Reading through the most important bits of Cl0p's latest exploit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defenders Buckle Up for a Future of Detecting Deepfakes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/the-cyber-future/defenders-buckle-up-future-detecting-deepfakes</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/the-cyber-future/defenders-buckle-up-future-detecting-deepfakes"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T20:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today technology companies have high success rates against generative AI-created voices and videos, but future detection will be much more difficult.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Lemos, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cl0p Cybercrime Gang Delivers Ultimatum After Payroll Breach]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/ics-ot/clop-cybercrime-gang-delivers-ultimatum-after-payroll-breach</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/ics-ot/clop-cybercrime-gang-delivers-ultimatum-after-payroll-breach"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T19:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Experts and researchers warn individuals and organizations that the cybercrime group is not to be trusted in their demands.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Fined $20M For Xbox Child Data Collection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/risk/microsoft-fined-20m-xbox-child-data-collection</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/risk/microsoft-fined-20m-xbox-child-data-collection"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T19:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The FTC has demanded additional data privacy protections for kids using Xbox gaming systems, extending COPPA protections.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cyber Essentialism & 'Doing Less With Less']]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/cyber-essentialism-doing-less-with-less</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/cyber-essentialism-doing-less-with-less"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T17:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity benefits from a focus on the vital few chores rather than the trivial many. Find the "right things" to encourage strategic thinking, then move the culture needle to promote that policy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Johnson, Co-Founder and CTO, Obsidian Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI: Sextortionist Campaigns Use Deepfakes to Target Children, Adults]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/fbi-sextortionist-campaigns-deepfakes-children-adults</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/fbi-sextortionist-campaigns-deepfakes-children-adults"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T14:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors are lifting public images and videos from the Internet, altering them, and posting them online in a new wave of sextortion campaigns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Montalbano, Contributor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Case for a Federal Cyber-Insurance Backstop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/the-case-for-a-federal-cyber-insurance-backstop</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/the-case-for-a-federal-cyber-insurance-backstop"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By stepping in to provide aid, the federal government could help protect companies, insurers, and the economy from the impact of a widespread, catastrophic cyberattack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Monica Shokrai, Head of Business Risk &amp; Insurance, Google Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft to Pay $20 Million Penalty for Illegally Collecting Kids' Data on Xbox]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/microsoft-to-pay-20-million-penalty-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/microsoft-to-pay-20-million-penalty-for.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T13:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has agreed to pay a penalty of $20 million to settle U.S. Federal Trade Commission (FTC) charges that the company illegally collected and retained the data of children who signed up to use its Xbox video game console without their parents' knowledge or consent.
"Our proposed order makes it easier for parents to protect their children's privacy on Xbox, and limits what information]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Adds One Known Exploited Vulnerability to Catalog]]></title>
        <id>/node/18296</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/06/07/cisa-adds-one-known-exploited-vulnerability-catalog"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CISA has added one new vulnerability to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog, based on evidence of active exploitation.
CVE-2023-3079 Google Chromium V8 Type Confusion Vulnerability
These types of vulnerabilities are frequent attack vectors for malicious cyber actors and pose significant risks to the federal enterprise. Note: To view other newly added vulnerabilities in the catalog, click on the arrow in the "Date Added to Catalog" column—which will sort by descending dates.
Binding Operational Directive (BOD) 22-01: Reducing the Significant Risk of Known Exploited Vulnerabilities established the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog as a living list of known Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVEs) that carry significant risk to the federal enterprise. BOD 22-01 requires Federal Civilian Executive Branch (FCEB) agencies to remediate identified vulnerabilities by the due date to protect FCEB networks against active threats. See the BOD 22-01 Fact Sheet for more information.
Although BOD 22-01 only applies to FCEB agencies, CISA strongly urges all organizations to reduce their exposure to cyberattacks by prioritizing timely remediation of Catalog vulnerabilities as part of their vulnerability management practice. CISA will continue to add vulnerabilities to the catalog that meet the specified criteria.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla Releases Security Updates for Multiple Products]]></title>
        <id>/node/18297</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/06/07/mozilla-releases-security-updates-multiple-products"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla has released security updates to address vulnerabilities for Firefox 114 and Firefox ESR 102.12. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities to take control of an affected system.
CISA encourages users and administrators to review Mozilla’s security advisories for Firefox 114 and Firefox ESR 102.12 for more information and apply the necessary updates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA and FBI Release #StopRansomware: CL0P Ransomware Gang Exploits MOVEit Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>/node/18294</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/06/07/cisa-and-fbi-release-stopransomware-cl0p-ransomware-gang-exploits-moveit-vulnerability"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CISA and FBI released a joint Cybersecurity Advisory (CSA) CL0P Ransomware Gang Exploits MOVEit Vulnerability in response to a recent vulnerability exploitation attributed to CL0P Ransomware Gang. This joint guide provides indicators of compromise (IOCs) and tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs) identified through FBI investigations as recently as May this year. Additionally, it provides immediate actions to help reduce the impact of CL0P ransomware. 
The CL0P Ransomware Gang, also known as TA505, reportedly began exploiting a previously unknown SQL injection vulnerability in Progress Software's managed file transfer (MFT) solution known as MOVEit Transfer. Internet- facing MOVEit Transfer web applications were infected with a web shell named LEMURLOOT, which was then used to steal data from underlying MOVEit Transfer databases.
CISA and FBI encourage information technology (IT) network defenders to review the MOVEit Transfer Advisory and implement the recommended mitigations to reduce the risk of compromise. This joint CSA is part of an ongoing #StopRansomware effort to publish advisories for network defenders that detail various ransomware variants and ransomware threat actors. These #StopRansomware advisories include recently and historically observed TTPs and IOCs to help organizations protect against ransomware. Visit stopransomware.gov to see all #StopRansomware advisories and to learn more about other ransomware threats and no-cost resources.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco Touts New AI-Based Security, SSE Features]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/cisco-touts-new-ai-based-security-sse-features</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/cisco-touts-new-ai-based-security-sse-features"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco laid out its plans for artificial intelligence (AI) and a vision for unified cloud security during Cisco Live 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Winning the Mind Game: The Role of the Ransomware Negotiator]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/winning-mind-game-role-of-ransomware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/winning-mind-game-role-of-ransomware.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T11:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get exclusive insights from a real ransomware negotiator who shares authentic stories from network hostage situations and how he managed them.
The Ransomware Industry
Ransomware is an industry. As such, it has its own business logic: organizations pay money, in crypto-currency, in order to regain control over their systems and data.
This industry's landscape is made up of approximately 10-20]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Attorneys Are Harming Cybersecurity Incident Response]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/06/how-attorneys-are-harming-cybersecurity-incident-response.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/06/how-attorneys-are-harming-cybersecurity-incident-response.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T11:06:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>New paper: &#8220;<a href="https://www.usenix.org/system/files/sec23fall-prepub-292-woods.pdf">Lessons Lost: Incident Response in the Age of Cyber Insurance and Breach Attorneys</a>&#8220;:</p>
<blockquote><p><b>Abstract:</b> Incident Response (IR) allows victim firms to detect, contain, and recover from security incidents. It should also help the wider community avoid similar attacks in the future. In pursuit of these goals, technical practitioners are increasingly influenced by stakeholders like cyber insurers and lawyers. This paper explores these impacts via a multi-stage, mixed methods research design that involved 69 expert interviews, data on commercial relationships, and an online validation workshop. The first stage of our study established 11 stylized facts that describe how cyber insurance sends work to a small numbers of IR firms, drives down the fee paid, and appoints lawyers to direct technical investigators. The second stage showed that lawyers when directing incident response often: introduce legalistic contractual and communication steps that slow-down incident response; advise IR practitioners not to write down remediation steps or to produce formal reports; and restrict access to any documents produced...</p></blockquote>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Key to Zero Trust Identity Is Automation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/the-key-to-zero-trust-identity-is-automation</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/the-key-to-zero-trust-identity-is-automation"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T11:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a zero-trust world, a trusted identity is the key that unlocks access for people and devices to enter your enterprise’s key networks, systems, and resources.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New PowerDrop Malware Targeting U.S. Aerospace Industry]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/new-powerdrop-malware-targeting-us.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/new-powerdrop-malware-targeting-us.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T04:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An unknown threat actor has been observed targeting the U.S. aerospace industry with a new PowerShell-based malware called PowerDrop.
"PowerDrop uses advanced techniques to evade detection such as deception, encoding, and encryption," according to Adlumin, which found the malware implanted in an unnamed domestic aerospace defense contractor in May 2023.
"The name is derived from the tool,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Verizon DBIR: Social Engineering Breaches Double, Leading to Spiraling Ransomware Costs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/verizon-dbir-social-engineering-breaches-spiraling-ransomware-costs</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/verizon-dbir-social-engineering-breaches-spiraling-ransomware-costs"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T22:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware continues its runaway growth with median payments reaching $50,000 per incident.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tara Seals, Managing Editor, News, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Spot a Different Kind of Magecart Card-Skimming Campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/different-kind-magecart-card-skimming-campaign</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/different-kind-magecart-card-skimming-campaign"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T21:55:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In addition to injecting a card skimmer into target Magento, WooCommerce, Shopify, and WordPress sites, the threat actor is also hijacking targeted domains to deliver the malware to other sites.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Preps $425M Payment for LinkedIn GDPR Violations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/microsoft-425m-payment-linkedin-gdpr-violations</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/microsoft-425m-payment-linkedin-gdpr-violations"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T21:18:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company plans on disputing these fines once a final decision is made, but warned shareholders that it set aside the funds to pay it, nonetheless.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[With SEC Rule Changes on the Horizon, Research Reveals Only 14% of CISOs Have Traits Desired for Cyber Expert Board Positions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/with-sec-rule-changes-on-the-horizon-new-research-reveals-only-14-of-cisos-have-traits-desired-for-cyber-expert-board-positions</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/with-sec-rule-changes-on-the-horizon-new-research-reveals-only-14-of-cisos-have-traits-desired-for-cyber-expert-board-positions"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T21:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ILTA and Conversant Group Release Cybersecurity Benchmarking Survey of the Legal Industry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/ilta-and-conversant-group-release-cybersecurity-benchmarking-survey-of-the-legal-industry</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/ilta-and-conversant-group-release-cybersecurity-benchmarking-survey-of-the-legal-industry"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T21:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joint research highlights disconnect between legal IT and recommended cybersecurity practices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[#StopRansomware: CL0P Ransomware Gang Exploits CVE-2023-34362 MOVEit Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>/node/18295</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/cybersecurity-advisories/aa23-158a"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T20:58:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUMMARY
Note: this joint Cybersecurity Advisory (CSA) is part of an ongoing #StopRansomware effort to publish advisories for network defenders that detail various ransomware variants and ransomware threat actors. These #StopRansomware advisories include recently and historically observed tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs) and indicators of compromise (IOCs) to help organizations protect against ransomware. Visit stopransomware.gov to see all #StopRansomware advisories and to learn more about other ransomware threats and no-cost resources.
Actions to take today to mitigate cyber threats from CL0P ransomware: 
Take an inventory of assets and data, identifying authorized and unauthorized devices and software.
Grant admin privileges and access only when necessary, establishing a softwa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netskope Intelligent SSE Selected by Transdev to Secure and Connect its Hybrid Workforce]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/remote-workforce/netskope-intelligent-sse-selected-by-transdev-to-secure-and-connect-its-hybrid-workforce</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/remote-workforce/netskope-intelligent-sse-selected-by-transdev-to-secure-and-connect-its-hybrid-workforce"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T19:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Implementation is part of Transdev's Cloud-First approach to better manage technological obsolescence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MAR-10365227-3.v1 - Impacket 3]]></title>
        <id>/node/18293</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/analysis-reports/ar22-277c"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T18:44:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notification
This report is provided "as is" for informational purposes only. The Department of Homeland Security (DHS) does not provide any warranties of any kind regarding any information contained herein. The DHS does not endorse any commercial product or service referenced in this bulletin or otherwise.
This document is marked TLP:CLEAR--Disclosure is not limited. Sources may use TLP:CLEAR when information carries minimal or no foreseeable risk of misuse, in accordance with applicable rules and procedures for public release. Subject to standard copyright rules, TLP:CLEAR information may be distributed without restriction. For more information on the Traffic Light Protocol (TLP), see http://www.cisa.gov/tlp.
Summary
Description
This Malware Analysis Report (MAR) is the result of analyti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MAR-10365227-2.v1 - Impacket 2]]></title>
        <id>/node/18292</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/analysis-reports/ar22-277b"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T18:22:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notification
This report is provided "as is" for informational purposes only. The Department of Homeland Security (DHS) does not provide any warranties of any kind regarding any information contained herein. The DHS does not endorse any commercial product or service referenced in this bulletin or otherwise.
This document is marked TLP:CLEAR--Disclosure is not limited. Sources may use TLP:CLEAR when information carries minimal or no foreseeable risk of misuse, in accordance with applicable rules and procedures for public release. Subject to standard copyright rules, TLP:CLEAR information may be distributed without restriction. For more information on the Traffic Light Protocol (TLP), see http://www.cisa.gov/tlp.
Summary
Description
This Malware Analysis Report (MAR) is the result of analyti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Malware Campaign Leveraging Satacom Downloader to Steal Cryptocurrency]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/new-malware-campaign-leveraging-satacom.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/new-malware-campaign-leveraging-satacom.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T18:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent malware campaign has been found to leverage Satacom downloader as a conduit to deploy stealthy malware capable of siphoning cryptocurrency using a rogue extension for Chromium-based browsers.
"The main purpose of the malware that is dropped by the Satacom downloader is to steal BTC from the victim's account by performing web injections into targeted cryptocurrency websites," Kaspersky]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MAR-10365227-1.v1 - Impacket]]></title>
        <id>/node/18291</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/analysis-reports/ar22-277a"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T17:42:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notification
This report is provided "as is" for informational purposes only. The Department of Homeland Security (DHS) does not provide any warranties of any kind regarding any information contained herein. The DHS does not endorse any commercial product or service referenced in this bulletin or otherwise.
This document is marked TLP:CLEAR--Disclosure is not limited. Sources may use TLP:CLEAR when information carries minimal or no foreseeable risk of misuse, in accordance with applicable rules and procedures for public release. Subject to standard copyright rules, TLP:CLEAR information may be distributed without restriction. For more information on the Traffic Light Protocol (TLP), see http://www.cisa.gov/tlp.
Summary
Description
This Malware Analysis Report (MAR) is the result of analyti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Filling the Gaps: How to Secure the Future of Hybrid Work]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/filling-the-gaps-how-to-secure-the-future-of-hybrid-work</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/filling-the-gaps-how-to-secure-the-future-of-hybrid-work"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By enhancing remote management and adopting hardware-enforced security, productivity can continue without inviting extra cyber-risk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Pratt, Global Head of Security for Personal Systems, HP Inc.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Over 60K Adware Apps Posing as Cracked Versions of Popular Apps Target Android Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/over-60k-adware-apps-posing-as-cracked.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/over-60k-adware-apps-posing-as-cracked.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T13:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thousands of adware apps for Android have been found to masquerade as cracks or modded versions of popular applications to serve unwanted ads to users as part of a campaign ongoing since October 2022.
"The campaign is designed to aggressively push adware to Android devices with the purpose to drive revenue," Bitdefender said in a technical report shared with The Hacker News. "However, the threat]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Aerospace Contractor Hacked With 'PowerDrop' Backdoor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/us-aerospace-contractor-hacked-powerdrop-backdoor</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/us-aerospace-contractor-hacked-powerdrop-backdoor"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers used a little to do a lot, cracking a high-value target with hardly more than the living-off-the-land tools (PowerShell especially) found on any standard Windows computer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Releases Two Industrial Control Systems Advisories]]></title>
        <id>/node/18284</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/06/06/cisa-releases-two-industrial-control-systems-advisories"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CISA released two Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisories on June 6, 2023. These advisories provide timely information about current security issues, vulnerabilities, and exploits surrounding ICS. 
ICSA-23-157-01 Delta Electronics CNCSoft-B DOPSoft
ICSA-23-157-02 Mitsubishi Electric MELSEC iQ-R Series/iQ-F Series
CISA encourages users and administrators to review the newly released ICS advisories for technical details and mitigations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA and Partners Release Joint Guide to Securing Remote Access Software]]></title>
        <id>/node/18287</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/06/06/cisa-and-partners-release-joint-guide-securing-remote-access-software"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, CISA, Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI), the National Security Agency (NSA), Multi-State Information Sharing and Analysis Center (MS-ISAC), and the Israel National Cyber Directorate (INCD) released the Guide to Securing Remote Access Software. This new joint guide is the result of a collaborative effort to provide an overview of legitimate uses of remote access software, as well as common exploitations and associated tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs), and how to detect and defend against malicious actors abusing this software. 
Remote access software provides organizations with a broad array of capabilities to maintain and improve information technology (IT), operational technology (OT), and industrial control system (ICS) services; however, malicious actors often exploit this software for easy and broad access to victim systems. 
joint guide for recommendations and best practices to implement in alignment with their specific cybersecurity requirements to better detect and defend against exploitation. Additionally, please refer to the additional information below on guidance for MSPs and small- and mid-sized businesses and on malicious use of remote monitoring and management software in using remote software and implementing mitigations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT Hallucinations Open Developers to Supply Chain Malware Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/chatgpt-hallucinations-developers-supply-chain-malware-attacks</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/chatgpt-hallucinations-developers-supply-chain-malware-attacks"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attackers could exploit a common AI experience — false recommendations — to spread malicious code via developers that use ChatGPT to create software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Montalbano, Contributor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Reasons Why IT Security Tools Don't Work For OT]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/5-reasons-why-it-security-tools-dont.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/5-reasons-why-it-security-tools-dont.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T11:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attacks on critical infrastructure and other OT systems are on the rise as digital transformation and OT/IT convergence continue to accelerate. Water treatment facilities, energy providers, factories, and chemical plants — the infrastructure that undergirds our daily lives could all be at risk. Disrupting or manipulating OT systems stands to pose real physical harm to citizens, environments, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Snowden Ten Years Later]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/06/snowden-ten-years-later.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/06/snowden-ten-years-later.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T11:17:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In 2013 and 2014, I wrote extensively about new revelations regarding NSA surveillance based on the documents provided by Edward Snowden. But I had a more personal involvement as well.</p>
<p>I wrote the essay below in September 2013. The <i>New Yorker</i> agreed to publish it, but the <i>Guardian</i> asked me not to. It was scared of UK law enforcement, and worried that this essay would reflect badly on it. And given that the UK police would raid its offices in July 2014, it had legitimate cause to be worried.</p>
<p>Now, ten years later, I offer this as a time capsule of what those early months of Snowden were like...</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zero-Day Alert: Google Issues Patch for New Chrome Vulnerability - Update Now!]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/zero-day-alert-google-issues-patch-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/zero-day-alert-google-issues-patch-for.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T10:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google on Monday released security updates to patch a high-severity flaw in its Chrome web browser that it said is being actively exploited in the wild.
Tracked as CVE-2023-3079, the vulnerability has been described as a type confusion bug in the V8 JavaScript engine. Clement Lecigne of Google's Threat Analysis Group (TAG) has been credited with reporting the issue on June 1, 2023.
"Type]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cyclops Ransomware Gang Offers Go-Based Info Stealer to Cybercriminals]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/cyclops-ransomware-gang-offers-go-based.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/cyclops-ransomware-gang-offers-go-based.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T06:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors associated with the Cyclops ransomware have been observed offering an information stealer malware that's designed to capture sensitive data from infected hosts.
"The threat actor behind this [ransomware-as-a-service] promotes its offering on forums," Uptycs said in a new report. "There it requests a share of profits from those engaging in malicious activities using its malware."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese PostalFurious Gang Strikes UAE Users with Sneaky SMS Phishing Scheme]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/chinese-postalfurious-gang-strikes-uae.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/chinese-postalfurious-gang-strikes-uae.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T04:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Chinese-speaking phishing gang dubbed PostalFurious has been linked to a new SMS campaign that's targeting users in the U.A.E. by masquerading as postal services and toll operators, per Group-IB.
The fraudulent scheme entails sending users bogus text messages asking them to pay a vehicle trip fee to avoid additional fines. The messages also contain a shortened URL to conceal the actual]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zyxel Firewalls Under Attack! Urgent Patching Required]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/zyxel-firewalls-under-attack-urgent.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/zyxel-firewalls-under-attack-urgent.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T04:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) on Monday placed two recently disclosed flaws in Zyxel firewalls to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, based on evidence of active exploitation.
The vulnerabilities, tracked as CVE-2023-33009 and CVE-2023-33010, are buffer overflow vulnerabilities that could enable an unauthenticated attacker to cause a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Sift Launches Relevance Detection as GPT-4-Powered Asset Discovery and Classification Solution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/red-sift-launches-relevance-detection-as-gpt-4-powered-asset-discovery-and-classification-solution</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/red-sift-launches-relevance-detection-as-gpt-4-powered-asset-discovery-and-classification-solution"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T21:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New AI feature enhances OnDOMAIN's capabilities to secure unknown vulnerabilities and strengthen network security posture.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Links MOVEit Attack to Cl0p as British Airways, BBC Fall]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/microsoft-links-moveit-attack-cl0p-british-airways-fall</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/microsoft-links-moveit-attack-cl0p-british-airways-fall"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T21:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some billion-dollar organizations have already been identified as victims of the prolific ransomware group's latest exploit, amidst ongoing attacks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2.5M Impacted by Enzo Biochem Data Leak After Ransomware Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/2-5m-impacted-by-enzo-biochem-data-leak-after-ransomware-attack</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/2-5m-impacted-by-enzo-biochem-data-leak-after-ransomware-attack"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T21:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the leak of information such as Social Security numbers, in addition to other protected information, 600,000 of the nearly 2.5 million affected are at risk for identity theft.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gigabyte Slams Backdoor Shut With Attack-Killing BIOS Update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/gigabyte-backdoor-attack-killing-bios-update</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/gigabyte-backdoor-attack-killing-bios-update"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T20:41:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A firmware update for hundreds of Gigabyte PC models gets rid of a backdoor capability that could be hijacked by cybercriminals, the company says.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moonlighter Satellite Offers In-Orbit Target for Space Hackers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/ics-ot/moonlighter-satellite-in-orbit-target-space-hackers</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/ics-ot/moonlighter-satellite-in-orbit-target-space-hackers"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T17:14:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Moonlighter, which offers red teams a chance at operational disruption, will be up for pwning at in August, timed with DEF CON.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don't Overlook Twitter's Trove of Threat Intel for Enterprise Cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/twitters-trove-threat-intel-enterprise-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/twitters-trove-threat-intel-enterprise-security"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T16:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Social media data can provide critical clues to help get ahead of the next cyberattack, experts say.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Becky Bracken, Editor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mass Exploitation of Zero-Day Bug in MOVEit File Transfer Underway]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/mass-exploitation-0-day-bug-imoveit-file-transfer-underway</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/mass-exploitation-0-day-bug-imoveit-file-transfer-underway"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T15:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With shades of the GoAnywhere attacks, a cyber threat actor linked to FIN11 is leveraging a bug in the widely used managed file transfer product to steal data from organizations in multiple countries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerability Summary for the Week of May 29, 2023]]></title>
        <id>/node/18279</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/bulletins/sb23-156"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T14:57:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CISA Vulnerability Bulletin provides a summary of new vulnerabilities that have been recorded by the National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) National Vulnerability Database (NVD) in the past week. NVD is sponsored by CISA. In some cases, the vulnerabilities in the bulletin may not yet have assigned CVSS scores. Please visit NVD for updated vulnerability entries, which include CVSS scores once they are available.
Vulnerabilities are based on the Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVE) vulnerability naming standard and are organized according to severity, determined by the Common Vulnerability Scoring System (CVSS) standard. The division of high, medium, and low severities correspond to the following scores:
High: vulnerabilities with a CVSS base score of 7.0–10.0
Medium…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After 'Inception' Attack, New Due Diligence Requirements Are Needed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/after-inception-attack-new-due-diligence-requirements-are-needed</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/after-inception-attack-new-due-diligence-requirements-are-needed"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To stem supply chain attacks, forging a new dynamic of shared cybersecurity hygiene accountability is the right thing to do.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carlos Morales, Senior Vice President of Solutions, Vercara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Varonis: Reducing Insider Threats Through Improved Data Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/risk/varonis-reducing-insider-threats-through-improved-data-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/risk/varonis-reducing-insider-threats-through-improved-data-security"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this Fast Chat segment, Dark Reading's Terry Sweeney and Varonis co-founder and CEO Yaki Faitelson discuss why we’re still seeing internal data breaches.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terry Sweeney, Contributing Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft: Lace Tempest Hackers Behind Active Exploitation of MOVEit Transfer App]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/microsoft-lace-tempest-hackers-behind.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/microsoft-lace-tempest-hackers-behind.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T12:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has officially linked the ongoing active exploitation of a critical flaw in the Progress Software MOVEit Transfer application to a threat actor it tracks as Lace Tempest.
"Exploitation is often followed by deployment of a web shell with data exfiltration capabilities," the Microsoft Threat Intelligence team said in a series of tweets today. "CVE-2023-34362 allows attackers to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Adds Two Known Exploited Vulnerabilities to Catalog]]></title>
        <id>/node/18277</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/06/05/cisa-adds-two-known-exploited-vulnerabilities-catalog"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CISA has added two new vulnerabilities to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog, based on evidence of active exploitation.
CVE-2023-33009 Zyxel Multiple Firewalls Buffer Overflow Vulnerability
CVE-2023-33010 Zyxel Multiple Firewalls Buffer Overflow Vulnerability
These types of vulnerabilities are frequent attack vectors for malicious cyber actors and pose significant risks to the federal enterprise. Note: To view other newly added vulnerabilities in the catalog, click on the arrow in the "Date Added to Catalog" column—which will sort by descending dates.
Binding Operational Directive (BOD) 22-01: Reducing the Significant Risk of Known Exploited Vulnerabilities established the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog as a living list of known Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVEs) that carry significant risk to the federal enterprise. BOD 22-01 requires Federal Civilian Executive Branch (FCEB) agencies to remediate identified vulnerabilities by the due date to protect FCEB networks against active threats. See the BOD 22-01 Fact Sheet for more information.
Although BOD 22-01 only applies to FCEB agencies, CISA strongly urges all organizations to reduce their exposure to cyberattacks by prioritizing timely remediation of Catalog vulnerabilities as part of their vulnerability management practice. CISA will continue to add vulnerabilities to the catalog that meet the specified criteria.
This product is provided subject to this Notification and this Privacy & Use policy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Annual Report: 2024 Plans and Priorities for SaaS Security]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/the-annual-report-2024-plans-and.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/the-annual-report-2024-plans-and.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T11:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over 55% of security executives report that they have experienced a SaaS security incident in the past two years — ranging from data leaks and data breaches to SaaS ransomware and malicious apps (as seen in figures 1 and 2). 
Figure 1. How many organizations have experienced a SaaS security incident within the past two years
The SaaS Security Survey Report: Plans and Priorities for 2024,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Software-Defined Car]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/06/the-software-defined-car.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/06/the-software-defined-car.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T11:14:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Developers are starting to <a href="https://arstechnica.com/cars/2023/05/throw-out-all-those-black-boxes-and-say-hello-to-the-software-defined-car/">talk about</a> the software-defined car.</p>
<blockquote><p>For decades, features have accumulated like cruft in new vehicles: a box here to control the antilock brakes, a module there to run the cruise control radar, and so on. Now engineers and designers are rationalizing the way they go about building new models, taking advantage of much more powerful hardware to consolidate all those discrete functions into a small number of domain controllers.</p>
<p>The behavior of new cars is increasingly defined by software, too. This is merely the progression of a trend that began at the end of the 1970s with the introduction of the first electronic engine control units; today, code controls a car&#8217;s engine and transmission (or its electric motors and battery pack), the steering, brakes, suspension, interior and exterior lighting, and more, depending on how new (and how expensive) it is. And those systems are being leveraged for convenience or safety features like adaptive cruise control, lane keeping, remote parking, and so on...</p></blockquote>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magento, WooCommerce, WordPress, and Shopify Exploited in Web Skimmer Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/magento-woocommerce-wordpress-and.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/magento-woocommerce-wordpress-and.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T06:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have unearthed a new ongoing Magecart-style web skimmer campaign that's designed to steal personally identifiable information (PII) and credit card data from e-commerce websites.
A noteworthy aspect that sets it apart from other Magecart campaigns is that the hijacked sites further serve as "makeshift" command-and-control (C2) servers, using the cover to facilitate the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Name That Edge Toon: Spring Chickens]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge/name-that-edge-toon-spring-chickens</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge/name-that-edge-toon-spring-chickens"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T05:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Come up with a clever caption, and our panel of experts will reward the winner with a $25 Amazon gift card.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Klossner, Cartoonist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brazilian Cybercriminals Using LOLBaS and CMD Scripts to Drain Bank Accounts]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/brazilian-cybercriminals-using-lolbas.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/brazilian-cybercriminals-using-lolbas.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T04:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An unknown cybercrime threat actor has been observed targeting Spanish- and Portuguese-speaking victims to compromise online banking accounts in Mexico, Peru, and Portugal.
"This threat actor employs tactics such as LOLBaS (living-off-the-land binaries and scripts), along with CMD-based scripts to carry out its malicious activities," the BlackBerry Research and Intelligence Team said in a report]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alarming Surge in TrueBot Activity Revealed with New Delivery Vectors]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/alarming-surge-in-truebot-activity.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/alarming-surge-in-truebot-activity.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T04:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A surge in TrueBot activity was observed in May 2023, cybersecurity researchers disclosed.
"TrueBot is a downloader trojan botnet that uses command and control servers to collect information on compromised systems and uses that compromised system as a launching point for further attacks," VMware's Fae Carlisle said.
Active since at least 2017, TrueBot is linked to a group known as Silence that's]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Linux Ransomware Strain BlackSuit Shows Striking Similarities to Royal]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/new-linux-ransomware-strain-blacksuit.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/new-linux-ransomware-strain-blacksuit.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-03T08:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An analysis of the Linux variant of a new ransomware strain called BlackSuit has covered significant similarities with another ransomware family called Royal.
Trend Micro, which examined an x64 VMware ESXi version targeting Linux machines, said it identified an "extremely high degree of similarity" between Royal and BlackSuit.
"In fact, they're nearly identical, with 98% similarities in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Security Tops Concerns for Cybersecurity Leaders: EC-Council's Certified CISO Hall of Fame Report 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/cloud-security-tops-concerns-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/cloud-security-tops-concerns-for.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-03T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A survey of global cybersecurity leaders through the 2023 Certified CISO Hall of Fame Report commissioned by the EC-Council identified 4 primary areas of grave concern: cloud security, data security, security governance, and lack of cybersecurity talent.
EC-Council, the global leader in cybersecurity education and training, released its Certified Chief Information Security Officer Hall of Fame]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTC Slams Amazon with $30.8M Fine for Privacy Violations Involving Alexa and Ring]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/ftc-slams-amazon-with-308m-fine-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/ftc-slams-amazon-with-308m-fine-for.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-03T08:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Federal Trade Commission (FTC) has fined Amazon a cumulative $30.8 million over a series of privacy lapses regarding its Alexa assistant and Ring security cameras.
This comprises a $25 million penalty for breaching children's privacy laws by retaining their Alexa voice recordings for indefinite time periods and preventing parents from exercising their deletion rights.
"Amazon's history]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friday Squid Blogging: Squid Chromolithographs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/06/friday-squid-blogging-squid-chromolithographs.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/06/friday-squid-blogging-squid-chromolithographs.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T21:13:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Beautiful <a href="https://publicdomainreview.org/collection/verany-cephalopods">illustrations</a>.</p>
<p>As usual, you can also use this squid post to talk about the security stories in the news that I haven’t covered.</p>
<p>Read my blog posting guidelines <a href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2017/03/commenting_poli.html">here</a>.</p>
<p>EDITED TO ADD (6/4): Slashdot <a href="https://news.slashdot.org/story/23/06/04/006250/big-tech-isnt-prepared-for-ais-next-chapter-open-source">thread</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PyPI's 2FA Requirements Don't Go Far Enough, Researchers Say]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/pypi-2fa-requirements-dont-go-far-enough</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/pypi-2fa-requirements-dont-go-far-enough"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T20:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Python Package Index will require developers to better secure their accounts as cyberattacks ramp up, but protecting the software supply chain will take more than that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tara Seals, Managing Editor, News, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['PostalFurious' SMS Attacks Target UAE Citizens for Data Theft]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/postalfurious-sms-attacks-target-uae-citizens-data-theft</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/postalfurious-sms-attacks-target-uae-citizens-data-theft"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T19:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SMS campaigns targeting members of the public in the United Arab Emirates have been detected.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Raywood, Senior Editor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Picture-in-Picture' Obfuscation Spoofs Delta, Kohl's for Credential Harvesting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/picture-in-picture-obfuscation-spoofs-delta-kohls-credential-harvesting</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/picture-in-picture-obfuscation-spoofs-delta-kohls-credential-harvesting"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T16:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent campaign tricks victims into visiting credential harvesting sites by hiding malicious URLs behind photos advertising deals from trusted brands.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Eddy, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Streamers Ditch Netflix for Dark Web After Password Sharing Ban]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/streamers-netflix-dark-web-password-sharing-ban</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/streamers-netflix-dark-web-password-sharing-ban"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T15:51:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Disgruntled users are pursuing offers for "full Netflix access" at steeply discounted rates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open-Source LLMs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/06/open-source-llms.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/06/open-source-llms.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T14:21:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In February, Meta released its large language model: LLaMA. Unlike OpenAI and its ChatGPT, Meta didn&#8217;t just give the world a chat window to play with. Instead, it released the code into the open-source community, and shortly thereafter the model itself was leaked. Researchers and programmers immediately started modifying it, improving it, and getting it to do things no one else anticipated. And their results have been immediate, innovative, and an indication of how the future of this technology is going to play out. Training speeds have hugely increased, and the size of the models themselves has shrunk to the point that you can create and run them on a laptop. The world of AI research has dramatically changed...</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Want Sustainable Security? Find Middle Ground Between Tech & Education]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/want-sustainable-security-find-the-middle-ground-between-technology-and-education</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/want-sustainable-security-find-the-middle-ground-between-technology-and-education"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The winning recipe for sustainable security combines strategic user education and tactical automation of well-constructed processes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Johanna Baum, CEO &amp; Founder, Strategic Security Solutions (S3)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Zero-Days, iMessage Used in 4-Year, Ongoing Spying Effort]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/apple-zero-days-imessage-4-year-spying-ios</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/apple-zero-days-imessage-4-year-spying-ios"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T13:51:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Russia's FSB intelligence agency says the zero-click attacks range far beyond Kaspersky, and it has blamed them on the United States' NSA. Those allegations are thus far uncorroborated.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How CISOs Can Manage the Intersection of Security, Privacy, And Trust]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/microsoft/how-cisos-can-manage-the-intersection-of-security-privacy-and-trust</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/microsoft/how-cisos-can-manage-the-intersection-of-security-privacy-and-trust"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T13:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Integrating a subject rights request tool with security and compliance solutions can help identify potential data conflicts more efficiently and with greater accuracy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Microsoft Security, Microsoft</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Botnet Malware 'Horabot' Targets Spanish-Speaking Users in Latin America]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/new-botnet-malware-horabot-targets.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/new-botnet-malware-horabot-targets.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T12:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spanish-speaking users in Latin America have been at the receiving end of a new botnet malware dubbed Horabot since at least November 2020.
"Horabot enables the threat actor to control the victim's Outlook mailbox, exfiltrate contacts' email addresses, and send phishing emails with malicious HTML attachments to all addresses in the victim's mailbox," Cisco Talos researcher Chetan Raghuprasad]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Adds One Known Exploited Vulnerability to Catalog]]></title>
        <id>/node/18272</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/06/02/cisa-adds-one-known-exploited-vulnerability-catalog"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CISA has added one new vulnerability to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog, based on evidence of active exploitation.
CVE-2023-34362 Progress MOVEit Transfer SQL Injection Vulnerability
These types of vulnerabilities are frequent attack vectors for malicious cyber actors and pose significant risks to the federal enterprise. Note: To view other newly added vulnerabilities in the catalog, click on the arrow in the "Date Added to Catalog" column—which will sort by descending dates.
Binding Operational Directive (BOD) 22-01: Reducing the Significant Risk of Known Exploited Vulnerabilities established the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog as a living list of known Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVEs) that carry significant risk to the federal enterprise. BOD 22-01 requires Federal Civilian Executive Branch (FCEB) agencies to remediate identified vulnerabilities by the due date to protect FCEB networks against active threats. See the BOD 22-01 Fact Sheet for more information.
Although BOD 22-01 only applies to FCEB agencies, CISA strongly urges all organizations to reduce their exposure to cyberattacks by prioritizing timely remediation of Catalog vulnerabilities as part of their vulnerability management practice. CISA will continue to add vulnerabilities to the catalog that meet the specified criteria.
This product is provided subject to this Notification and this Privacy & Use policy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Importance of Managing Your Data Security Posture]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/the-importance-of-managing-your-data.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/the-importance-of-managing-your-data.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T10:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data security is reinventing itself. As new data security posture management solutions come to market, organizations are increasingly recognizing the opportunity to provide evidence-based security that proves how their data is being protected. But what exactly is data security posture, and how do you manage it? 
Data security posture management (DSPM) became mainstream following the publication]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camaro Dragon Strikes with New TinyNote Backdoor for Intelligence Gathering]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/camaro-dragon-strikes-with-new-tinynote.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/camaro-dragon-strikes-with-new-tinynote.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T10:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Chinese nation-state group known as Camaro Dragon has been linked to yet another backdoor that's designed to meet its intelligence-gathering goals.
Israeli cybersecurity firm Check Point, which dubbed the Go-based malware TinyNote, said it functions as a first-stage payload capable of "basic machine enumeration and command execution via PowerShell or Goroutines."
What the malware lacks in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korea's Kimsuky Group Mimics Key Figures in Targeted Cyber Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/north-koreas-kimsuky-group-mimics-key.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/north-koreas-kimsuky-group-mimics-key.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. and South Korean intelligence agencies have issued a new alert warning of North Korean cyber actors' use of social engineering tactics to strike think tanks, academia, and news media sectors.
The "sustained information gathering efforts" have been attributed to a state-sponsored cluster dubbed Kimsuky, which is also known by the names APT43, ARCHIPELAGO, Black Banshee, Emerald Sleet (]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MOVEit Transfer Under Attack: Zero-Day Vulnerability Actively Being Exploited]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/moveit-transfer-under-attack-zero-day.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/moveit-transfer-under-attack-zero-day.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T03:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A critical flaw in Progress Software's in MOVEit Transfer managed file transfer application has come under widespread exploitation in the wild to take over vulnerable systems.
The shortcoming, which is assigned the CVE identifier CVE-2023-34362, relates to a severe SQL injection vulnerability that could lead to escalated privileges and potential unauthorized access to the environment.
"An SQL]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DNB Strengthens its Network Security Posture and Productivity With Ericsson Security Manager Solution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/dnb-strengthens-its-network-security-posture-and-productivity-with-ericsson-security-manager-solution</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/dnb-strengthens-its-network-security-posture-and-productivity-with-ericsson-security-manager-solution"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T21:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cyversity and United Airlines to Provide Cybersecurity Training Scholarships to Cyversity Members]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/cyversity-and-united-airlines-to-provide-cybersecurity-training-scholarships-to-cyversity-members</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/cyversity-and-united-airlines-to-provide-cybersecurity-training-scholarships-to-cyversity-members"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T21:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Program designed to equip women and underrepresented individuals with the necessary skills and knowledge to succeed in cybersecurity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tel Aviv Stock Exchange Selects CardinalOps to Reduce Risk of Breaches Due to Undetected Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/risk/tel-aviv-stock-exchange-selects-cardinalops-to-reduce-risk-of-breaches-due-to-undetected-attacks</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/risk/tel-aviv-stock-exchange-selects-cardinalops-to-reduce-risk-of-breaches-due-to-undetected-attacks"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T20:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enables financial services firm to operationalize MITRE ATT&CK with Splunk and eliminate detection coverage gaps based on organizational risk and priorities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Pays $30.8M to Settle Ring Spying & Alexa Privacy Lawsuits]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/ics-ot/amazon-ring-and-alexa-pay-30-8m-to-settle-privacy-lawsuits</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/ics-ot/amazon-ring-and-alexa-pay-30-8m-to-settle-privacy-lawsuits"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T19:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The global e-commerce company will pay millions of dollars in two separate lawsuits because of privacy and security violations, the FTC says.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jetpack WordPress Plug-in API Bug Triggers Mass Updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/jetpack-wordpress-plugin-api-bug-mass-updates</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/jetpack-wordpress-plugin-api-bug-mass-updates"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T18:44:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An audit uncovers an API-related security vulnerability dating back to Jetpack version 2.0 released in 2012 — and it affects millions of websites.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Do I Reduce Security Tool Sprawl in My Environment?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge-ask-the-experts/how-do-i-reduce-security-tool-sprawl-in-my-environment</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge-ask-the-experts/how-do-i-reduce-security-tool-sprawl-in-my-environment"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T18:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to tool consolidation, focus on platforms over products.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yotam Segev, Co-Founder and CEO, Cyera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sustained 'Red Deer' Phishing Attacks Impersonate Israel Post, Drop RATs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/sustained-red-deer-phishing-attacks-israel-post-rats</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/sustained-red-deer-phishing-attacks-israel-post-rats"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T17:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The "missed package" phishing messages, likely the work of a hacking-for-hire group, bounds into inboxes, bearing ASyncRAT.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Raywood, Senior Editor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Drive Deficiency Allows Attackers to Exfiltrate Workspace Data Without a Trace]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/google-drive-deficiency-exfiltrate-workspace-data</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/google-drive-deficiency-exfiltrate-workspace-data"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T17:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No activity logging in the free subscription for Google's Web-based productivity suite exposes enterprises to insider and other threats, researchers say.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Montalbano, Contributor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where SBOMs Stand Today]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/where-sboms-stand-today</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/where-sboms-stand-today"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's been two years since Executive Order 14028. By using SBOMs as a standard, organizations can manage software risks, protect their reputation, and improve their cybersecurity posture.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liran Tancman, CEO &amp; Co-Founder, Rezilion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Novel PyPI Malware Uses Compiled Python Bytecode to Evade Detection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/novel-pypi-malware-compiled-python-bytecode-evade-detection</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/novel-pypi-malware-compiled-python-bytecode-evade-detection"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T16:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an already fraught environment surrounding the popular Python programming language software package manager, hackers are coming up with new ways to sneak malicious goodies past cybersecurity buffers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evasive QBot Malware Leverages Short-lived Residential IPs for Dynamic Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/evasive-qbot-malware-leverages-short.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/evasive-qbot-malware-leverages-short.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T16:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An analysis of the "evasive and tenacious" malware known as QBot has revealed that 25% of its command-and-control (C2) servers are merely active for a single day.
What's more, 50% of the servers don't remain active for more than a week, indicating the use of an adaptable and dynamic C2 infrastructure, Lumen Black Lotus Labs said in a report shared with The Hacker News.
"This botnet has adapted]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biometric Bypass: BrutePrint Makes Short Work of Fingerprint Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/bruteprint-short-work-fingerprint-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/bruteprint-short-work-fingerprint-security"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T15:50:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bugs in the biometric protections on Android phones and iPhones allow the limit on the number of tries to unlock the devices with a fingerprint can be bypassed, allowing automated brute-force attacks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Lemos, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Zero-Click Hack Targets iOS Users with Stealthy Root-Privilege Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/new-zero-click-hack-targets-ios-users.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/new-zero-click-hack-targets-ios-users.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T15:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A previously unknown advanced persistent threat (APT) is targeting iOS devices as part of a sophisticated and long-running mobile campaign dubbed Operation Triangulation that began in 2019.
"The targets are infected using zero-click exploits via the iMessage platform, and the malware runs with root privileges, gaining complete control over the device and user data," Kaspersky said.
The Russian]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unmasking XE Group: Experts Reveal Identity of Suspected Cybercrime Kingpin]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/unmasking-xe-group-experts-reveal.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/unmasking-xe-group-experts-reveal.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T14:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have unmasked the identity of one of the individuals who is believed to be associated with the e-crime actor known as XE Group.
According to Menlo Security, which pieced together the information from different online sources, "Nguyen Huu Tai, who also goes by the names Joe Nguyen and Thanh Nguyen, has the strongest likelihood of being involved with the XE Group."
XE]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SolarWinds Transforms Brand to Signify Ongoing Evolution, Portfolio Expansion, and Customer Empowerment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/solarwinds-transforms-brand-to-signify-ongoing-evolution-portfolio-expansion-and-customer-empowerment</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/solarwinds-transforms-brand-to-signify-ongoing-evolution-portfolio-expansion-and-customer-empowerment"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T13:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Refreshed version of iconic SolarWinds logo and vibrant new brand color palette honor company’s historic success while highlighting future vision.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top macOS Malware Threats: Here Are 6 to Watch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/top-macos-malware-threats-proliferate</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/top-macos-malware-threats-proliferate"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple's growing market share — in a shrinking PC market — and the growing use of Golang for malware development is pushing a gradual increase in malicious tools targeting macOS environments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dark Reading Launches Inaugural CISO Advisory Board]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/dark-reading-launches-inaugural-ciso-advisory-board</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/dark-reading-launches-inaugural-ciso-advisory-board"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T12:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ten chief information security officers from a variety of verticals will provide valuable insights to Dark Reading on what they see as the industry's most pressing issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelly Jackson Higgins, Editor-in-Chief, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malicious PyPI Packages Using Compiled Python Code to Bypass Detection]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/malicious-pypi-packages-using-compiled.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/malicious-pypi-packages-using-compiled.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T12:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have discovered a novel attack on the Python Package Index (PyPI) repository that employs compiled Python code to sidestep detection by application security tools.
"It may be the first supply chain attack to take advantage of the fact that Python bytecode (PYC) files can be directly executed," ReversingLabs analyst Karlo Zanki said in a report shared with The Hacker News.
The package]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Wazuh Improves IT Hygiene for Cyber Security Resilience]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/how-wazuh-improves-it-hygiene-for-cyber.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/how-wazuh-improves-it-hygiene-for-cyber.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T11:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IT hygiene is a security best practice that ensures that digital assets in an organization's environment are secure and running properly. Good IT hygiene includes vulnerability management, security configuration assessments, maintaining asset and system inventories, and comprehensive visibility into the activities occurring in an environment.
As technology advances and the tools used by]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On the Catastrophic Risk of AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/06/on-the-catastrophic-risk-of-ai.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/06/on-the-catastrophic-risk-of-ai.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T11:17:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Earlier this week, I signed on to a short <a href="https://www.safe.ai/statement-on-ai-risk">group statement</a>, coordinated by the Center for AI Safety:</p>
<blockquote><p>Mitigating the risk of extinction from AI should be a global priority alongside other societal-scale risks such as pandemics and nuclear war.</p></blockquote>
<p><a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/05/30/technology/ai-threat-warning.html">The</a> <a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/5/30/23742005/ai-risk-warning-22-word-statement-google-deepmind-openai">press</a> <a href="https://apnews.com/article/artificial-intelligence-risk-of-extinction-ai-54ea8aadc60d1503e5a65878219aad43">coverage</a> <a href="https://www.wired.com/story/runaway-ai-extinction-statement/">has</a> <a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-65746524">been</a> extensive, and surprising to me. The <i>New York Times</i> headline is &#8220;A.I. Poses &#8216;Risk of Extinction,&#8217; Industry Leaders Warn.&#8221; <i>BBC</i>: &#8220;Artificial intelligence could lead to extinction, experts warn.&#8221; Other headlines are similar.</p>
<p>I actually don&#8217;t think that AI poses a risk to human extinction. I think it poses a similar risk to pandemics and nuclear war&#8212;which is to say, a risk worth taking seriously, but not something to panic over. Which is what I thought the statement said...</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improved BlackCat Ransomware Strikes with Lightning Speed and Stealthy Tactics]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/improved-blackcat-ransomware-strikes.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/improved-blackcat-ransomware-strikes.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T09:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actors behind BlackCat ransomware have come up with an improved variant that prioritizes speed and stealth in an attempt to bypass security guardrails and achieve their goals.
The new version, dubbed Sphynx and announced in February 2023, packs a "number of updated capabilities that strengthen the group's efforts to evade detection," IBM Security X-Force said in a new analysis.
The "]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[N. Korean ScarCruft Hackers Exploit LNK Files to Spread RokRAT]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/n-korean-scarcruft-hackers-exploit.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/n-korean-scarcruft-hackers-exploit.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T06:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have offered a closer look at the RokRAT remote access trojan that's employed by the North Korean state-sponsored actor known as ScarCruft.
"RokRAT is a sophisticated remote access trojan (RAT) that has been observed as a critical component within the attack chain, enabling the threat actors to gain unauthorized access, exfiltrate sensitive information, and potentially]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Active Mirai Botnet Variant Exploiting Zyxel Devices for DDoS Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/active-mirai-botnet-variant-exploiting.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/active-mirai-botnet-variant-exploiting.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T04:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has added a recently patched critical security flaw in Zyxel gear to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, citing evidence of active exploitation.
Tracked as CVE-2023-28771 (CVSS score: 9.8), the issue relates to a command injection flaw impacting different firewall models that could enable an unauthenticated attacker]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Charlotte, CrowdStrike's New Generative AI Assistant]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/meet-charlotte-crowdstrike-s-new-generative-ai-assistant</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/meet-charlotte-crowdstrike-s-new-generative-ai-assistant"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Charlotte AI is the latest security-based generative AI assistant to hit the market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yet Another Toyota Cloud Data Breach Jeopardizes Thousands of Customers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/ics-ot/toyota-cloud-data-breach-jeopardizes-thousands-customers</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/ics-ot/toyota-cloud-data-breach-jeopardizes-thousands-customers"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T21:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The newly found misconfigured cloud services are discovered just two weeks after an initial data breach affecting millions came to light.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Cloud Services Encourage Better Login Security? Netflix's Accidental Model]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/can-service-providers-encourage-better-login-security-netflix-accidental-model</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/can-service-providers-encourage-better-login-security-netflix-accidental-model"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T20:30:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix's unpopular password-sharing policy change had a positive cybersecurity silver lining. Can more B2C service providers nudge their users toward secure authentication?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MacOS 'Migraine' Bug: Big Headache for Device System Integrity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/macos-migraine-bug-headache-device-system-integrity</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/macos-migraine-bug-headache-device-system-integrity"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T20:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft says the vulnerability could allow cyberattackers with root access to bypass security protections and install malware.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ways to Help Cybersecurity's Essential Workers Avoid Burnout]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge-articles/ways-to-help-cybersecurity-s-essential-workers-avoid-burnout</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge-articles/ways-to-help-cybersecurity-s-essential-workers-avoid-burnout"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T19:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To support and retain the people who protect assets against bad actors, organizations should create a more defensible environment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kris Lovejoy, Global Security and Resilience Practice Leader, Kyndryl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Apple's RSRs Reveal About Mac Patch Management]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/what-apple-rsrs-reveal-about-mac-patch-management</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/what-apple-rsrs-reveal-about-mac-patch-management"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple's Rapid Security Response updates are designed to patch critical security vulnerabilities, but how much good can they do when patching is a weeks-long process?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Investment May Be Down, but Cybersecurity Remains a Hot Sector]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/investment-may-be-down-cybersecurity-remains-hot</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/investment-may-be-down-cybersecurity-remains-hot"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's still a great deal of capital available for innovative companies helping businesses secure their IT environments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave DeWalt, Founder &amp; CEO, NightDragon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Checkmarx Announces GenAI-powered AppSec Platform, Empowering Developers and AppSec Teams to Find and Fix Vulnerabilities Faster]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/checkmarx-announces-genai-powered-appsec-platform-empowering-developers-and-appsec-teams-to-find-and-fix-vulnerabilities-faster</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/checkmarx-announces-genai-powered-appsec-platform-empowering-developers-and-appsec-teams-to-find-and-fix-vulnerabilities-faster"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Powered by GPT-4, innovative new AI-driven capabilities lower application security (AppSec) risk and help security teams "shift everywhere" with speed and accuracy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New eID Scheme Gives EU Citizens Easy Access to Public Services Online]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/new-eid-scheme-gives-eu-citizens-easy-access-to-public-services-online</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/new-eid-scheme-gives-eu-citizens-easy-access-to-public-services-online"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T16:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The European Commission voted a new electronic identification scheme that creates new opportunities for EU citizens and businesses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mirai Variant Opens Tenda, Zyxel Gear to RCE, DDoS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/mirai-variant-tenda-zyxel-rce-ddos</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/mirai-variant-tenda-zyxel-rce-ddos"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T15:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have observed several cyberattacks leveraging a botnet called IZ1H9, which exploits vulnerabilities in exposed devices and servers running on Linux.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Montalbano, Contributor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Focus Security Efforts on Choke Points, Not Visibility]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/focus-security-efforts-on-choke-points-not-visibility</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/focus-security-efforts-on-choke-points-not-visibility"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By finding the places where attack paths converge, you can slash multiple exposures in one fix for more efficient remediation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Menachem Shafran, Senior Vice President of Product and Innovation, XM Cyber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce 'Ghost Sites' Expose Sensitive Corporate Data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/salesforce-ghost-sites-expose-sensitive-corporate-data</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/salesforce-ghost-sites-expose-sensitive-corporate-data"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some companies have moved on from using Salesforce. But without remembering to fully deactivate their clouds, Salesforce won't move on from them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spotlight on 2023 Dan Kaminsky Fellow: Dr. Gus Andrews]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge/spotlight-on-2023-dan-kaminsky-fellow-dr-gus-andrews</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge/spotlight-on-2023-dan-kaminsky-fellow-dr-gus-andrews"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T01:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the second Kaminsky Fellow, Andrews will study the use of threat intelligence to track campaigns against the human rights community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ericka Chickowski, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Human-Assisted CAPTCHA-Cracking Services Supercharge Shopper Bots]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/human-assisted-captcha-cracking-services-supercharge-shopper-bots</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/human-assisted-captcha-cracking-services-supercharge-shopper-bots"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T21:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-demand human solvers are now augmenting automated website cyberattacks, offering a better way around tougher anti-bot puzzles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[421M Spyware Apps Downloaded Through Google Play]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/421-spyware-apps-downloaded-google-play</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/421-spyware-apps-downloaded-google-play"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T21:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Trojan SDK snuck past Google Play protections to infest 101 Android applications, bent on exfiltrating infected device data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Undetected Attacks Against Middle East Targets Conducted Since 2020]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/undetected-attacks-against-middle-east-conducted</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/undetected-attacks-against-middle-east-conducted"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Targeted attacks against Saudi Arabia and other Middle East nations have been detected with a tool that's been in the wild since 2020.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Raywood, Senior Editor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[9M Dental Patients Affected by LockBit Attack on MCNA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/9-million-dental-patients-affected-lockbit-attack-mcna</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/9-million-dental-patients-affected-lockbit-attack-mcna"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T16:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The government-sponsored dental and oral healthcare provider warned its customers that a March attack exposed sensitive data, some of which was leaked online by the ransomware group.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Montalbano, Contributor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerability Summary for the Week of May 22, 2023]]></title>
        <id>/node/18243</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/bulletins/sb23-150"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T16:03:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CISA Vulnerability Bulletin provides a summary of new vulnerabilities that have been recorded by the National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) National Vulnerability Database (NVD) in the past week. NVD is sponsored by CISA. In some cases, the vulnerabilities in the bulletin may not yet have assigned CVSS scores. Please visit NVD for updated vulnerability entries, which include CVSS scores once they are available.
Vulnerabilities are based on the Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVE) vulnerability naming standard and are organized according to severity, determined by the Common Vulnerability Scoring System (CVSS) standard. The division of high, medium, and low severities correspond to the following scores:
High: vulnerabilities with a CVSS base score of 7.0–10.0
Entrie…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pentagon Leaks Emphasize the Need for a Trusted Workforce]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/pentagon-leaks-emphasize-the-need-for-a-trusted-workforce</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/pentagon-leaks-emphasize-the-need-for-a-trusted-workforce"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tightening access controls and security clearance alone won't prevent insider threat risks motivated by lack of trust or loyalty.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kellie Roessler, Insider Risk Advocate &amp; Author, DTEX Insider Intelligence &amp; Investigations (i3) Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Cyberattacks Revealed in New Threat Intelligence Report]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/top-cyberattacks-revealed-in-new-threat-intelligence-report</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/top-cyberattacks-revealed-in-new-threat-intelligence-report"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New report provides actionable intelligence about attacks, threat actors, and campaigns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2 Lenses for Examining the Safety of Open Source Software]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/2-lenses-examining-safety-open-source-software</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/2-lenses-examining-safety-open-source-software"/>
        <updated>2023-05-26T21:03:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Improving the security of open source repositories while keeping malicious components out requires a combination of technology and people.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Lemos, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[People's Republic of China State-Sponsored Cyber Actor Living off the Land to Evade Detection]]></title>
        <id>/node/18218</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/cybersecurity-advisories/aa23-144a"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T18:06:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summary
The United States and international cybersecurity authorities are issuing this joint Cybersecurity Advisory (CSA) to highlight a recently discovered cluster of activity of interest associated with a People’s Republic of China (PRC) state-sponsored cyber actor, also known as Volt Typhoon. Private sector partners have identified that this activity affects networks across U.S. critical infrastructure sectors, and the authoring agencies believe the actor could apply the same techniques against these and other sectors worldwide.
This advisory from the United States National Security Agency (NSA), the U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA), the U.S. Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI), the Australian Signals Directorate’s Australian Cyber Security Centre (ACSC), t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerability Summary for the Week of May 15, 2023]]></title>
        <id>/node/18205</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/bulletins/sb23-142"/>
        <updated>2023-05-22T13:37:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CISA Vulnerability Bulletin provides a summary of new vulnerabilities that have been recorded by the National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) National Vulnerability Database (NVD) in the past week. NVD is sponsored by CISA. In some cases, the vulnerabilities in the bulletin may not yet have assigned CVSS scores. Please visit NVD for updated vulnerability entries, which include CVSS scores once they are available.
Vulnerabilities are based on the Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVE) vulnerability naming standard and are organized according to severity, determined by the Common Vulnerability Scoring System (CVSS) standard. The division of high, medium, and low severities correspond to the following scores:
High: vulnerabilities with a CVSS base score of 7.0–10.0
Entrie…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing The BlueHat Podcast: Listen and Subscribe Now!]]></title>
        <id>/blog/2023/05/announcing-the-bluehat-podcast-listen-and-subscribe-now/</id>
        <link href="https://msrc-blog.microsoft.com/blog/2023/05/announcing-the-bluehat-podcast-listen-and-subscribe-now/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-17T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Available today on all major podcast platforms is The BlueHat Podcast, a new series of security research focused conversations, continuing the themes from the BlueHat 2023 conference (session recordings available to watch here).
Since 2005, BlueHat has been where the security research community, and Microsoft, come together as peers: to debate, discuss, share, challenge, celebrate and learn.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Microsoft Security Response Center</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[#StopRansomware: BianLian Ransomware Group]]></title>
        <id>/node/18174</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/cybersecurity-advisories/aa23-136a"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T16:29:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summary
Note: This joint Cybersecurity Advisory (CSA) is part of an ongoing #StopRansomware effort to publish advisories for network defenders that detail various ransomware variants and ransomware threat actors. These #StopRansomware advisories include recently and historically observed tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs) and indicators of compromise (IOCs) to help organizations protect against ransomware. Visit stopransomware.gov to see all #StopRansomware advisories and learn more about other ransomware threats and no-cost resources.
The Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI), Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA), and Australian Cyber Security Centre (ACSC) are releasing this joint Cybersecurity Advisory to disseminate known BianLian ransomware and data extortio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerability Summary for the Week of May 8, 2023]]></title>
        <id>/node/18173</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/bulletins/sb23-135"/>
        <updated>2023-05-15T12:09:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CISA Vulnerability Bulletin provides a summary of new vulnerabilities that have been recorded by the National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) National Vulnerability Database (NVD) in the past week. NVD is sponsored by CISA. In some cases, the vulnerabilities in the bulletin may not yet have assigned CVSS scores. Please visit NVD for updated vulnerability entries, which include CVSS scores once they are available.
Vulnerabilities are based on the Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVE) vulnerability naming standard and are organized according to severity, determined by the Common Vulnerability Scoring System (CVSS) standard. The division of high, medium, and low severities correspond to the following scores:
High: vulnerabilities with a CVSS base score of 7.0–10.0

High …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>