<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://ehsanedalat.github.io/securitynews/index.html</id>
    <title>News | S&amp;P Homepage</title>
    <updated>2023-10-29T01:11:10.156Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://ehsanedalat.github.io/securitynews/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://ehsanedalat.github.io/securitynews/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Uncover Wiretapping of XMPP-Based Instant Messaging Service]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/researchers-uncover-wiretapping-of-xmpp.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/researchers-uncover-wiretapping-of-xmpp.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-28T07:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New findings have shed light on what's said to be a lawful attempt to covertly intercept traffic originating from jabber[.]ru (aka xmpp[.]ru), an XMPP-based instant messaging service, via servers hosted on Hetzner and Linode (a subsidiary of Akamai) in Germany.
"The attacker has issued several new TLS certificates using Let's Encrypt service which were used to hijack encrypted STARTTLS]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Tips for Security Awareness Training That Hits the Target]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge/10-tips-for-security-awareness-training-that-hits-the-target</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge/10-tips-for-security-awareness-training-that-hits-the-target"/>
        <updated>2023-10-28T00:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Try these tricks for devising an education program that gets employees invested — and stays with them after the training is over.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Goodchild, Senior Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friday Squid Blogging: On the Ugliness of Squid Fishing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/10/friday-squid-blogging-on-the-ugliness-of-squid-fishing.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/10/friday-squid-blogging-on-the-ugliness-of-squid-fishing.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T21:13:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>And <a href="https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2023/10/16/the-crimes-behind-the-seafood-you-eat">seafood in general</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>A squid ship is a bustling, bright, messy place. The scene on deck looks like a mechanic&#8217;s garage where an oil change has gone terribly wrong. Scores of fishing lines extend into the water, each bearing specialized hooks operated by automated reels. When they pull a squid on board, it squirts warm, viscous ink, which coats the walls and floors. Deep-sea squid have high levels of ammonia, which they use for buoyancy, and a smell hangs in the air. The hardest labor generally happens at night, from 5 P.M. until 7 A.M. Hundreds of bowling-ball-size light bulbs hang on racks on both sides of the vessel, enticing the squid up from the depths. The blinding glow of the bulbs, visible more than a hundred miles away, makes the surrounding blackness feel otherworldly...</p></blockquote>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Safari Side-Channel Attack Enables Browser Theft]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/safari-side-channel-attack-enables-browser-theft</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/safari-side-channel-attack-enables-browser-theft"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T20:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The "iLeakage" attack affects all recent iPhone, iPad, and MacBook models, allowing attackers to peruse your Gmail inbox, steal your Instagram password, or scrutinize your YouTube history.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Octo Tempest Group Threatens Physical Violence as Social Engineering Tactic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/octo-tempest-group-threatens-physical-violence-social-engineering-tactic</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/octo-tempest-group-threatens-physical-violence-social-engineering-tactic"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T19:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The financially motivated English-speaking threat actors use advanced social engineering techniques, SIM swapping, and even threats of violence to breach targets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Eddy, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Securing Cloud Identities to Protect Assets and Minimize Risk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge/securing-cloud-identities-to-protect-assets-and-minimize-risk</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge/securing-cloud-identities-to-protect-assets-and-minimize-risk"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T18:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Preventative security should be driven by data and risk assessment, not compliance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glen Pendley, Chief Technology Officer, Tenable</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understand the True Cost of a UEM Before Making the Switch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/understand-the-true-cost-of-a-uem-before-making-the-switch</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/understand-the-true-cost-of-a-uem-before-making-the-switch"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When investing in a unified endpoint management solution, prioritize the needs of your network and users ahead of brand names. This Tech Tip focuses on questions to ask.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chuck Brooks, President, Brooks Consulting International; Adjunct Professor, Georgetown University</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacktivist Activity Related to Gaza Conflict Dwindles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/hacktivist-activity-related-to-gaza-conflict-dwindles</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/hacktivist-activity-related-to-gaza-conflict-dwindles"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T16:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Groups have fallen silent after bold claims of action at the start of the conflict.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Healey-Driscoll Awards $2.3M to CyberTrust Massachusetts to Strengthen Municipal Cybersecurity Efforts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/healey-driscoll-administration-awards-2-3-million-to-cybertrust-massachusetts-to-strengthen-municipal-cybersecurity-efforts-statewide</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/healey-driscoll-administration-awards-2-3-million-to-cybertrust-massachusetts-to-strengthen-municipal-cybersecurity-efforts-statewide"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T15:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[N. Korean Lazarus Group Targets Software Vendor Using Known Flaws]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/n-korean-lazarus-group-targets-software.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/n-korean-lazarus-group-targets-software.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T14:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The North Korea-aligned Lazarus Group has been attributed as behind a new campaign in which an unnamed software vendor was compromised through the exploitation of known security flaws in another high-profile software.
The attack sequences, according to Kaspersky, culminated in the deployment of malware families such as SIGNBT and LPEClient, a known hacking tool used by the threat actor for]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Other News: Ex-NSA Employee Spying for Russia, EU Threat Landscape, Cyber Education Funding]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=35466</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/in-other-news-ex-nsa-employee-spying-for-russia-eu-threat-landscape-cyber-education-funding/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T14:31:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Noteworthy stories that might have slipped under the radar: Ex-NSA employee spying for Russia, EU threat landscape report, cyber education funding
The post In Other News: Ex-NSA Employee Spying for Russia, EU Threat Landscape, Cyber Education Funding appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SecurityWeek News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced ‘StripedFly’ Malware With 1 Million Infections Shows Similarities to NSA-Linked Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=35463</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/advanced-stripedfly-malware-with-1-million-infections-shows-similarities-to-nsa-malware/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T14:12:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The StripedFly malware has APT-like capabilities, but remained unnoticed for five years, posing as a cryptocurrency miner.
The post Advanced ‘StripedFly’ Malware With 1 Million Infections Shows Similarities to NSA-Linked Tools appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Arghire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Lurks in the Dark: Taking Aim at Shadow AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/what-lurks-in-the-dark-taking-aim-at-shadow-ai</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/what-lurks-in-the-dark-taking-aim-at-shadow-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Generative artificial intelligence tools have unleashed a new era of terror to CISOs still battling longstanding shadow IT security risks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Won, Chief Product Officer, 1Password</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[F5 Warns of Critical Remote Code Execution Vulnerability in BIG-IP]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=35462</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/f5-warns-of-critical-remote-code-execution-vulnerability-in-big-ip/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T13:54:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A critical-severity vulnerability in F5 BIG-IP CVE-2023-46747 allows unauthenticated attackers to execute code remotely.
The post F5 Warns of Critical Remote Code Execution Vulnerability in BIG-IP appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Arghire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Updates Guidance for Addressing Cisco IOS XE Web UI Vulnerabilities With Additional Releases]]></title>
        <id>/node/19065</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/10/27/cisa-updates-guidance-addressing-cisco-ios-xe-web-ui-vulnerabilities-additional-releases"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, CISA updated its guidance addressing two vulnerabilities, CVE-2023-20198 and CVE-2023-20273, affecting Cisco’s Internetworking Operating System (IOS) XE Software Web User Interface (UI).
The guidance now notes that Cisco has fixed these vulnerabilities for the 17.6 Cisco IOS XE software release train with the 17.6.6a update. According to Cisco's Security Advisory: Multiple Vulnerabilities in Cisco IOS XE Software Web UI Feature, fixes are still to be determined for the following Cisco IOS XE software release trains: 17.3, 16.12 (Catalyst 3650 and 3850 only). Cisco previously published the fixed release for 17.9, which is 17.9.4a, on Oct. 22. CISA urges organizations with the 17.9 and 17.6 Cisco IOS XE software release train to immediately update to the 17.9.4a and 17.6.6a releases, respectively.
CISA urges organizations to review:
CISA’s updated guidance
Cisco Security Advisory: Multiple Vulnerabilities in Cisco IOS XE Software Web UI Feature
Cisco Product Support: Software Fix Availability for Cisco IOS XE Software Web UI Privilege Escalation Vulnerability - CVE-2023-20198
Cisco Talos Threat Advisory: Active exploitation of Cisco IOS XE Software Web Management User Interface vulnerabilities
CISA has added CVE-2023-20198 (on Oct. 16, 2023) and CVE-2023-20273 (on Oct. 23, 2023) to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog, which, per Binding Operational Directive (BOD) 22-01: Reducing the Significant Risk of Known Exploited Vulnerabilities, requires Federal Civilian Executive Branch (FCEB) agencies to remediate identified vulnerabilities by the specified due date to protect FCEB networks against active threats.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Announces Launch of Logging Made Easy]]></title>
        <id>/node/19060</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/10/27/cisa-announces-launch-logging-made-easy"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, CISA announces the launch of a new version of Logging Made Easy (LME), a straightforward log management solution for Windows-based devices that can be downloaded and self-installed for free. CISA’s version reimagines technology developed by the United Kingdom’s National Cyber Security Centre (NCSC), making it available to a wider audience.
Log management makes systems more secure. Until now, it has been a heavy lift for many targeted organizations, especially those with limited resources. CISA’s LME is a turnkey solution for public and private organizations seeking to strengthen their cybersecurity while reducing their log management burden.
As CISA’s newest shared services product offering, LME builds upon the success of the NCSC's log management solution, which was decommissioned in March 2023. CISA urges organizations to secure their Windows-based devices today by downloading the free LME technical solution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Messaging Service Wiretap Discovered through Expired TLS Cert]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/10/messaging-service-wiretap-discovered-through-expired-tls-cert.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/10/messaging-service-wiretap-discovered-through-expired-tls-cert.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T11:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Fascinating <a href="https://therecord.media/jabber-ru-alleged-government-wiretap-expired-tls-certificate">story</a> of a covert wiretap that was discovered because of an expired TLS certificate:</p>
<blockquote><p>The suspected man-in-the-middle attack was identified when the administrator of jabber.ru, the largest Russian XMPP service, received a notification that one of the servers’ certificates had expired.</p>
<p>However, jabber.ru found no expired certificates on the server, ­ as explained in <a href="https://notes.valdikss.org.ru/jabber.ru-mitm/">a blog post</a> by ValdikSS, a pseudonymous anti-censorship researcher based in Russia who collaborated on the investigation.</p>
<p>The expired certificate was instead discovered on a single port being used by the service to establish an encrypted Transport Layer Security (TLS) connection with users. Before it had expired, it would have allowed someone to decrypt the traffic being exchanged over the service...</p></blockquote>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Keep Your Business Running in a Contested Environment]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/how-to-keep-your-business-running-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/how-to-keep-your-business-running-in.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T10:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When organizations start incorporating cybersecurity regulations and cyber incident reporting requirements into their security protocols, it's essential for them to establish comprehensive plans for preparation, mitigation, and response to potential threats.
At the heart of your business lies your operational technology and critical systems. This places them at the forefront of cybercriminal]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Expands Its Bug Bounty Program to Tackle Artificial Intelligence Threats]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/google-expands-its-bug-bounty-program.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/google-expands-its-bug-bounty-program.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T10:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has announced that it's expanding its Vulnerability Rewards Program (VRP) to compensate researchers for finding attack scenarios tailored to generative artificial intelligence (AI) systems in an effort to bolster AI safety and security.
"Generative AI raises new and different concerns than traditional digital security, such as the potential for unfair bias, model manipulation or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UN Chief Appoints 39-Member Panel to Advise on International Governance of Artificial Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=35461</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/un-chief-appoints-39-member-panel-to-advise-on-international-governance-of-artificial-intelligence/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.N. Secretary-General António Guterres assembled a global advisory panel to report on international governance of artificial intelligence and its risks, challenges and key opportunities.
The post UN Chief Appoints 39-Member Panel to Advise on International Governance of Artificial Intelligence appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Associated Press</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[F5 Issues Warning: BIG-IP Vulnerability Allows Remote Code Execution]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/f5-issues-warning-big-ip-vulnerability.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/f5-issues-warning-big-ip-vulnerability.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-27T04:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[F5 has alerted customers of a critical security vulnerability impacting BIG-IP that could result in unauthenticated remote code execution.
The issue, rooted in the configuration utility component, has been assigned the CVE identifier CVE-2023-46747, and carries a CVSS score of 9.8 out of a maximum of 10.
"This vulnerability may allow an unauthenticated attacker with network access to the BIG-IP]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMBs Need to Balance Cybersecurity Needs and Resources]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge/how-smbs-can-balance-cybersecurity-needs-and-resources</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge/how-smbs-can-balance-cybersecurity-needs-and-resources"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T23:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Small and midsize businesses face the same cyberattacks as enterprises, but with fewer resources. Here's how to protect a company that has leaner means.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sue Poremba, Contributing Writer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SonicWall Data Confirms That Ransomware Is Still the Enterprise's Biggest Fear]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/sonicwall-data-confirms-that-ransomware-is-still-the-enterprise-s-biggest-fear</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/sonicwall-data-confirms-that-ransomware-is-still-the-enterprise-s-biggest-fear"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IriusRisk Brings Threat Modeling to Machine Learning Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/iriusrisk-brings-threat-modeling-to-machine-learning</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/iriusrisk-brings-threat-modeling-to-machine-learning"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The newly launched AI & ML Security Library allows developers to analyze the code used in machine learning systems to identify and address risks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fahmida Y. Rashid, Managing Editor, Features, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cranium Announces $25 Million in Series A Funding to Secure AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/cranium-announces-25-million-in-series-a-funding-to-secure-ai</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/cranium-announces-25-million-in-series-a-funding-to-secure-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lumen Q3 DDoS Report: Banking Was the Most Targeted Industry for the First Time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/lumen-q3-ddos-report-banking-was-the-most-targeted-industry-for-the-first-time</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/lumen-q3-ddos-report-banking-was-the-most-targeted-industry-for-the-first-time"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T21:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WatchGuard Launches MDR Service, Helps MSPs Accelerate Cybersecurity Service Delivery]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/watchguard-launches-mdr-service-helps-msps-accelerate-cybersecurity-service-delivery</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/watchguard-launches-mdr-service-helps-msps-accelerate-cybersecurity-service-delivery"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T21:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malwarebytes Announces Consumer Identity Theft Protection Solution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/remote-workforce/malwarebytes-announces-consumer-identity-theft-protection-solution</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/remote-workforce/malwarebytes-announces-consumer-identity-theft-protection-solution"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[70% of Crypto Companies Report Deepfake Fraud Rise]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/70-of-crypto-companies-report-deepfake-fraud-rise</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/70-of-crypto-companies-report-deepfake-fraud-rise"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Darktrace Unveils Cloud-Native Security Solution Using AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/darktrace-unveils-cloud-native-security-solution-using-ai</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/darktrace-unveils-cloud-native-security-solution-using-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rockwell's Verve Buy Enlivens Critical Infrastructure Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/ics-ot/rockwell-verve-buy-critical-infrastructure-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/ics-ot/rockwell-verve-buy-critical-infrastructure-security"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T19:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The industrial automation giant agrees to buy Verve Industrial Protection, joining in an ICS trend of bringing cybersecurity capabilities in-house to keep up with attackers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Lemos, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iran APT Targets the Mediterranean With Watering-Hole Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/iran-apt-targets-mediterranean-watering-hole-attacks</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/iran-apt-targets-mediterranean-watering-hole-attacks"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T19:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nation-state hackers are using hybrids to ensnare those in the maritime, shipping, and logistics industries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft: 0ktapus Cyberattackers Evolve to 'Most Dangerous' Status]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/remote-workforce/microsoft-0ktapus-cyberattackers-evolve-most-dangerous-status</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/remote-workforce/microsoft-0ktapus-cyberattackers-evolve-most-dangerous-status"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T18:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The English-speaking cyberattack group behind the MGM and Caesars Entertainment attacks is adding unique capabilities and gaining in sophistication. Prepare now, Microsoft says.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tara Seals, Managing Editor, News, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Mirth Connect Vulnerability Could Expose Sensitive Healthcare Data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=35458</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/critical-mirth-connect-vulnerability-could-expose-sensitive-healthcare-data/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T18:06:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mirth Connect versions prior to 4.4.1 are vulnerable to CVE-2023-43208, a bypass for an RCE vulnerability.
The post Critical Mirth Connect Vulnerability Could Expose Sensitive Healthcare Data appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Arghire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Longer Support Periods Raise the Bar for Mobile Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/omdia/longer-support-periods-raise-bar-mobile-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/omdia/longer-support-periods-raise-bar-mobile-security"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Google's announcement of seven years of support, other smartphone makers risk falling behind.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hollie Hennessy, Senior Analyst, IoT Cybersecurity, Omdia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iLeakage: New Safari Exploit Impacts Apple iPhones and Macs with A- and M-Series CPUs]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/ileakage-new-safari-exploit-impacts.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/ileakage-new-safari-exploit-impacts.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T16:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A group of academics has devised a novel side-channel attack dubbed iLeakage that exploits a weakness in the A- and M-series CPUs running on Apple iOS, iPadOS, and macOS devices, enabling the extraction of sensitive information from the Safari web browser.
"An attacker can induce Safari to render an arbitrary webpage, subsequently recovering sensitive information present within it using]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Earn $350k on Second Day at Pwn2Own Toronto 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=35457</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/hackers-earn-350k-on-second-day-at-pwn2own-toronto-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T16:32:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smart speakers, printers, routers, NAS devices, and mobile phones were hacked on the second day at Pwn2Own Toronto 2023.
The post Hackers Earn $350k on Second Day at Pwn2Own Toronto 2023 appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Arghire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Security Firm Cranium Raises $25 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=35456</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/ai-security-firm-cranium-raises-25-million/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T16:23:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI cybersecurity firm Cranium has raised $25 million in Series A funding, which brings the total investment in the company to $32 million.
The post AI Security Firm Cranium Raises $25 Million appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eduard Kovacs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Key Learnings from “Big Game” Ransomware Campaigns]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=35455</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/key-learnings-from-big-game-ransomware-campaigns/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T15:59:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are key steps every organization should take to leverage threat and event data across the lifecycle of a cyber incident. 
The post Key Learnings from “Big Game” Ransomware Campaigns appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marc Solomon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nigerian Cybercrime Hub Shut Down With 6 Arrests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/nigerian-cybercrime-hub-shut-down-with-6-arrests</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/nigerian-cybercrime-hub-shut-down-with-6-arrests"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T15:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cybercrime recruitment and mentoring hub conducted a variety of cybercrimes including business email compromise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kansas Court System Down Nearly 2 Weeks in ‘Security Incident’ That Has Hallmarks of Ransomware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=35454</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/kansas-court-system-down-nearly-2-weeks-in-security-incident-that-has-hallmarks-of-ransomware/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T15:48:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kansas is calling a massive computer outage that’s kept most of the state’s courts offline for 2 weeks a “security incident” and experts say it's likely ransomware.
The post Kansas Court System Down Nearly 2 Weeks in ‘Security Incident’ That Has Hallmarks of Ransomware appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Associated Press</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA, HHS Release Cybersecurity Healthcare Toolkit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=35453</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/cisa-hhs-release-cybersecurity-healthcare-toolkit/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T15:38:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CISA and the HHS have released resources for healthcare and public health organizations to improve their security.
The post CISA, HHS Release Cybersecurity Healthcare Toolkit appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Arghire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Would a Government Shutdown Mean for Cybersecurity?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/what-would-government-shutdown-mean-for-cybersecurity</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/what-would-government-shutdown-mean-for-cybersecurity"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Companies are advised to act now to protect networks while federal employee paychecks are still forthcoming. Public agencies are updating contingency plans before the November extension ends, while cyber stalkers get an extra month to plan, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Gorham, COO, OPSWAT</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Warns as Scattered Spider Expands from SIM Swaps to Ransomware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/microsoft-warns-as-scattered-spider.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/microsoft-warns-as-scattered-spider.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T13:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The prolific threat actor known as Scattered Spider has been observed impersonating newly hired employees in targeted firms as a ploy to blend into normal on-hire processes and takeover accounts and breach organizations across the world.
Microsoft, which disclosed the activities of the financially motivated hacking crew, described the adversary as "one of the most dangerous financial criminal]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Complex Spy Platform StripedFly Bites 1M Victims]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/complex-spy-platform-stripedfly-bites-1m-victims-disguised-as-a-cryptominer</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/complex-spy-platform-stripedfly-bites-1m-victims-disguised-as-a-cryptominer"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T13:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sophisticated Windows and Linux malware for stealing data and conducting cyber espionage has flown under the radar, disguised as a cryptominer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Montalbano, Contributor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Record-Breaking 100 Million RPS DDoS Attack Exploits HTTP/2 Rapid Reset Flaw]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/record-breaking-100-million-rps-ddos.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/record-breaking-100-million-rps-ddos.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare on Thursday said it mitigated thousands of hyper-volumetric HTTP distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attacks that exploited a recently disclosed flaw called HTTP/2 Rapid Reset, 89 of which exceeded 100 million requests per second (RPS).
"The campaign contributed to an overall increase of 65% in HTTP DDoS attack traffic in Q3 compared to the previous quarter," the web infrastructure]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6454-1: Linux kernel vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6454-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6454-1"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T12:36:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kyle Zeng discovered that the netfilter subsystem in the Linux kernel
contained a race condition in IP set operations in certain situations. A
local attacker could use this to cause a denial of service (system crash).
(CVE-2023-42756)

Alex Birnberg discovered that the netfilter subsystem in the Linux kernel
did not properly validate register length, leading to an out-of- bounds
write vulnerability. A local attacker could possibly use this to cause a
denial of service (system crash). (CVE-2023-4881)

It was discovered that the Quick Fair Queueing scheduler implementation in
the Linux kernel did not properly handle network packets in certain
conditions, leading to a use after free vulnerability. A local attacker
could use this to cause a denial of service (system crash) or possibly
execute arbitrary code. (CVE-2023-4921)

Kevin Rich discovered that the netfilter subsystem in the Linux kernel did
not properly handle removal of rules from chain bindings in certain
circumstances, leading to a use-after-free vulnerability. A local attacker
could possibly use this to cause a denial of service (system crash) or
execute arbitrary code. (CVE-2023-5197)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Adds One Known Exploited Vulnerability to Catalog]]></title>
        <id>/node/19055</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/10/26/cisa-adds-one-known-exploited-vulnerability-catalog"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CISA has added one new vulnerability to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog, based on evidence of active exploitation.
CVE-2023-5631 Roundcube Webmail Persistent Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability
These types of vulnerabilities are frequent attack vectors for malicious cyber actors and pose significant risks to the federal enterprise. Note: To view other newly added vulnerabilities in the catalog, click on the arrow in the "Date Added to Catalog" column—which will sort by descending dates.
Binding Operational Directive (BOD) 22-01: Reducing the Significant Risk of Known Exploited Vulnerabilities established the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog as a living list of known Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVEs) that carry significant risk to the federal enterprise. BOD 22-01 requires Federal Civilian Executive Branch (FCEB) agencies to remediate identified vulnerabilities by the due date to protect FCEB networks against active threats. See the BOD 22-01 Fact Sheet for more information.
Although BOD 22-01 only applies to FCEB agencies, CISA strongly urges all organizations to reduce their exposure to cyberattacks by prioritizing timely remediation of Catalog vulnerabilities as part of their vulnerability management practice. CISA will continue to add vulnerabilities to the catalog that meet the specified criteria.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Releases Security Advisories for Multiple Products]]></title>
        <id>/node/19053</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/10/26/apple-releases-security-advisories-multiple-products"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple has released security updates to address vulnerabilities in multiple products. A cyber threat actor could exploit some of these vulnerabilities to take control of an affected device.
CISA encourages users and administrators to review the following advisories and apply the necessary updates:
iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1
iOS 16.7.2 and iPadOS 16.7.2
iOS 15.8 and iPadOS 15.8
macOS Sonoma 14.1
macOS Ventura 13.6.1
macOS Monterey 12.7.1
tvOS 17.1
watchOS 10.1
Safari 17.1]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Releases Nine Industrial Control Systems Advisories]]></title>
        <id>/node/19056</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/10/26/cisa-releases-nine-industrial-control-systems-advisories"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CISA released nine Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisories on October 26, 2023. These advisories provide timely information about current security issues, vulnerabilities, and exploits surrounding ICS.
ICSA-23-299-01 Dingtian DT-R002
ICSA-23-299-02 Centralite Pearl Thermostat
ICSA-23-299-03 Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt, Graphite, Xenon, Argon, Lithium
ICSA-23-299-04 Rockwell Automation Arena
ICSA-23-299-05 Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk View Site Edition
ICSA-23-299-06 Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk Services Platform
ICSA-23-299-07 Sielco PolyEco FM Transmitter
ICSA-23-299-08 Sielco Radio Link and Analog FM Transmitters
ICSMA-23-194-01 BD Alaris System with Guardrails Suite MX (Update A)
 
CISA encourages users and administrators to review the newly released ICS advisories for technical details and mitigations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VMware Releases Security Advisory for vCenter Server]]></title>
        <id>/node/19054</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/10/26/vmware-releases-security-advisory-vcenter-server"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VMware released a security advisory for vulnerabilities (CVE-2023-34048, CVE-2023-34056) affecting the VMware vCenter Server. A remote cyber actor could exploit one of these vulnerabilities to take control of an affected system.
CISA encourages users and administrators to review the VMware vCenter Server Out-of-Bounds Write Vulnerability advisory and apply the necessary updates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Danger of Forgotten Pixels on Websites: A New Case Study]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/the-danger-of-forgotten-pixels-on.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/the-danger-of-forgotten-pixels-on.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T11:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While cyberattacks on websites receive much attention, there are often unaddressed risks that can lead to businesses facing lawsuits and privacy violations even in the absence of hacking incidents. A new case study highlights one of these more common cases. 
Download the full case study here.
It's a scenario that could have affected any type of company, from healthcare to finance, e-commerce to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6446-3: Linux kernel (Oracle) vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6446-3</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6446-3"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T11:50:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ross Lagerwall discovered that the Xen netback backend driver in the Linux
kernel did not properly handle certain unusual packets from a
paravirtualized network frontend, leading to a buffer overflow. An attacker
in a guest VM could use this to cause a denial of service (host system
crash) or possibly execute arbitrary code. (CVE-2023-34319)

Bien Pham discovered that the netfiler subsystem in the Linux kernel
contained a race condition, leading to a use-after-free vulnerability. A
local user could use this to cause a denial of service (system crash) or
possibly execute arbitrary code. (CVE-2023-4244)

Kyle Zeng discovered that the networking stack implementation in the Linux
kernel did not properly validate skb object size in certain conditions. An
attacker could use this cause a denial o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New NSA Information from (and About) Snowden]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/10/new-nsa-information-from-and-about-snowden.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/10/new-nsa-information-from-and-about-snowden.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T11:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Interesting <a href="https://www.computerweekly.com/news/366554957/Why-only-1-of-the-Snowden-Archive-will-ever-be-published">article</a> about the Snowden documents, including comments from former <i>Guardian</i> editor Ewen MacAskill</p>
<blockquote><p>MacAskill, who shared the Pulitzer Prize for Public Service with Glenn Greenwald and Laura Poitras for their journalistic work on the Snowden files, retired from <i>The Guardian</i> in 2018. He told <i>Computer Weekly</i> that:</p>
<ul>
<li>As far as he knows, a copy of the documents is still locked in the New York Times office. Although the files are in the <i>New York Times</i> office, <i>The Guardian</i> retains responsibility for them.</li>
<li>As to why the <i>New York Times</i> has not published them in a decade, MacAskill maintains &#8220;this is a complicated issue.&#8221; &#8220;There is, at the very least, a case to be made for keeping them for future generations of historians,&#8221; he said...</li></ul></blockquote>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iranian Group Tortoiseshell Launches New Wave of IMAPLoader Malware Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/iranian-group-tortoiseshell-launches.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/iranian-group-tortoiseshell-launches.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T07:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Iranian threat actor known as Tortoiseshell has been attributed to a new wave of watering hole attacks that are designed to deploy a malware dubbed IMAPLoader.
"IMAPLoader is a .NET malware that has the ability to fingerprint victim systems using native Windows utilities and acts as a downloader for further payloads," the PwC Threat Intelligence team said in a Wednesday analysis.
"It uses]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Flaw in NextGen's Mirth Connect Could Expose Healthcare Data]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/critical-flaw-in-nextgens-mirth-connect.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/critical-flaw-in-nextgens-mirth-connect.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T05:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Users of Mirth Connect, an open-source data integration platform from NextGen HealthCare, are being urged to update to the latest version following the discovery of an unauthenticated remote code execution vulnerability.
Tracked as CVE-2023-43208, the vulnerability has been addressed in version 4.4.1 released on October 6, 2023.
"This is an easily exploitable, unauthenticated remote code]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YoroTrooper: Researchers Warn of Kazakhstan's Stealthy Cyber Espionage Group]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/yorotrooper-researchers-warn-of.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/yorotrooper-researchers-warn-of.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-26T04:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A relatively new threat actor known as YoroTrooper is likely made up of operators originating from Kazakhstan.
The assessment, which comes from Cisco Talos, is based on their fluency in Kazakh and Russian, use of Tenge to pay for operating infrastructure, and very limited targeting of Kazakhstani entities, barring the government's Anti-Corruption Agency.
"YoroTrooper attempts to obfuscate the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BHI Energy Releases Details of Akira Ransomware Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/bhi-energy-releases-details-of-akira-ransomware-attack</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/bhi-energy-releases-details-of-akira-ransomware-attack"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T23:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actor exfiltrated 690GB of uncompressed data, or 767,035 files.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As Citrix Urges Its Clients to Patch, Researchers Release an Exploit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/citrix-urges-clients-patch-researchers-release-exploit</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/citrix-urges-clients-patch-researchers-release-exploit"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T19:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the race over Citrix's latest vulnerability, the bad guys have a huge head start, with broad implications for businesses and critical infrastructure providers worldwide.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Virtual Alarm: VMware Issues Major Security Advisory]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/vmware-issues-alarming-security-advisory</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/vmware-issues-alarming-security-advisory"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T19:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VMware vCenter Servers need immediate patch against critical RCE bug as race against threat actors begins.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Becky Bracken, Editor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kazakh Attackers, Disguised as Azerbaijanis, Hit Former Soviet States]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/kazakh-attackers-disguised-as-azerbaijanis-hit-former-soviet-states</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/kazakh-attackers-disguised-as-azerbaijanis-hit-former-soviet-states"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The YoroTrooper group claims to be from Azerbaijan and even routes its phishing traffic through the former Soviet republic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity Awareness Doesn't Cut It; It's Time to Focus on Behavior]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/cybersecurity-awareness-doesnt-cut-it-focus-on-behavior</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/cybersecurity-awareness-doesnt-cut-it-focus-on-behavior"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have too much cybersecurity awareness. It's time to implement repeatable, real-world practice that ingrains positive habits and security behaviors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Russell Spitler, Co-Founder &amp; CEO, Nudge Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6453-1: X.Org X Server vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6453-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6453-1"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T16:57:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan-Niklas Sohn discovered that the X.Org X Server incorrectly handled
prepending values to certain properties. An attacker could possibly use
this issue to cause the X Server to crash, execute arbitrary code, or
escalate privileges. (CVE-2023-5367)

Sri discovered that the X.Org X Server incorrectly handled detroying
windows in certain legacy multi-screen setups. An attacker could possibly
use this issue to cause the X Server to crash, execute arbitrary code, or
escalate privileges. (CVE-2023-5380)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6452-1: Vim vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6452-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6452-1"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T16:47:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was discovered that Vim could be made to divide by zero. An attacker
could possibly use this issue to cause a denial of service. This issue
only affected Ubuntu 23.04. (CVE-2023-3896)

It was discovered that Vim did not properly manage memory. An attacker
could possibly use this issue to cause a denial of service or execute
arbitrary code. (CVE-2023-4733, CVE-2023-4750)

It was discovered that Vim contained an arithmetic overflow. An attacker
could possibly use this issue to cause a denial of service. This issue
only affected Ubuntu 22.04 LTS, Ubuntu 23.04, and Ubuntu 23.10.
(CVE-2023-4734)

It was discovered that Vim could be made to write out of bounds. An
attacker could possibly use this issue to cause a denial of service or
execute arbitrary code. (CVE-2023-4735, CVE-2023-5344)

It …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Winter Vivern APT Blasts Webmail Zero-Day Bug With One-Click Exploit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/winter-vivern-blasts-webmail-0day-one-click-exploit</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/winter-vivern-blasts-webmail-0day-one-click-exploit"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T15:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A campaign targeting European governmental organizations and a think tank shows consistency from the low-profile threat group, which has ties to Belarus and Russia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Montalbano, Contributor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Cybersecurity Framework for Mitigating Risks to Satellite Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/risk/cybersecurity-framework-mitigating-risks-satellite-systems</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/risk/cybersecurity-framework-mitigating-risks-satellite-systems"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cyber threats on satellite technology will persist and evolve. We need a comprehensive cybersecurity framework to protect them from attackers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rebecca Herold, IEEE Member</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nation State Hackers Exploiting Zero-Day in Roundcube Webmail Software]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/nation-state-hackers-exploiting-zero.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/nation-state-hackers-exploiting-zero.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T13:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actor known as Winter Vivern has been observed exploiting a zero-day flaw in Roundcube webmail software on October 11, 2023, to harvest email messages from victims' accounts.
"Winter Vivern has stepped up its operations by using a zero-day vulnerability in Roundcube," ESET security researcher Matthieu Faou said in a new report published today. Previously, it was using known]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical OAuth Flaws Uncovered in Grammarly, Vidio, and Bukalapak Platforms]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/critical-oauth-flaws-uncovered-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/critical-oauth-flaws-uncovered-in.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T13:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Critical security flaws have been disclosed in the Open Authorization (OAuth) implementation of popular online services such as Grammarly, Vidio, and Bukalapak, building upon previous shortcomings uncovered in Booking[.]com and Expo.
The weaknesses, now addressed by the respective companies following responsible disclosure between February and April 2023, could have allowed malicious actors to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6440-3: Linux kernel (HWE) vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6440-3</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6440-3"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T12:43:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seth Jenkins discovered that the Linux kernel did not properly perform
address randomization for a per-cpu memory management structure. A local
attacker could use this to expose sensitive information (kernel memory) or
in conjunction with another kernel vulnerability. (CVE-2023-0597)

It was discovered that the IPv6 implementation in the Linux kernel
contained a high rate of hash collisions in connection lookup table. A
remote attacker could use this to cause a denial of service (excessive CPU
consumption). (CVE-2023-1206)

Yu Hao and Weiteng Chen discovered that the Bluetooth HCI UART driver in
the Linux kernel contained a race condition, leading to a null pointer
dereference vulnerability. A local attacker could use this to cause a
denial of service (system crash). (CVE-2023-31083)

Ross…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6435-2: OpenSSL vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6435-2</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6435-2"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T12:40:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6435-1 fixed vulnerabilities in OpenSSL. This update
provides the corresponding updates for Ubuntu 20.04 LTS.

Original advisory details:

 It was discovered that OpenSSL incorrectly handled excessively large
 Diffie-Hellman parameters. An attacker could possibly use this issue
 to cause a denial of service. (CVE-2023-3446)
 
 Bernd Edlinger discovered that OpenSSL incorrectly handled excessively
 large Diffie-Hellman parameters. An attacker could possibly use this
 issue to cause a denial of service. (CVE-2023-3817)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla Releases Security Advisories for Multiple Products]]></title>
        <id>/node/19039</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/10/25/mozilla-releases-security-advisories-multiple-products"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla has released security updates to address vulnerabilities in Firefox and Thunderbird. A cyber threat actor could exploit one of these vulnerabilities to take control of an affected system.
CISA encourages users and administrators to review the following Mozilla advisories for more information and apply the necessary updates:
Security Vulnerabilities fixed in Firefox for iOS 119
Security Vulnerabilities fixed in Thunderbird 115.4.1
Security Vulnerabilities fixed in Firefox ESR 115.4
Security Vulnerabilities fixed in Firefox 119]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rise of S3 Ransomware: How to Identify and Combat It]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/the-rise-of-s3-ransomware-how-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/the-rise-of-s3-ransomware-how-to.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T11:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's digital landscape, around 60% of corporate data now resides in the cloud, with Amazon S3 standing as the backbone of data storage for many major corporations. 
Despite S3 being a secure service from a reputable provider, its pivotal role in handling vast amounts of sensitive data (customer personal information, financial data, intellectual property, etc.), provides a juicy target for]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is Soft-Launching Security Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/10/microsoft-is-soft-launching-security-copilot.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/10/microsoft-is-soft-launching-security-copilot.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T11:07:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Microsoft has <a href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-announces-security-copilot-early-access-program/">announced</a> an early access program for its LLM-based security chatbot assistant: Security Copilot.</p>
<p>I am curious whether this thing is actually useful.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Act Now: VMware Releases Patch for Critical vCenter Server RCE Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/act-now-vmware-releases-patch-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/act-now-vmware-releases-patch-for.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T10:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VMware has released security updates to address a critical flaw in the vCenter Server that could result in remote code execution on affected systems.
The issue, tracked as CVE-2023-34048 (CVSS score: 9.8), has been described as an out-of-bounds write vulnerability in the implementation of the DCE/RPC protocol.
"A malicious actor with network access to vCenter Server may trigger an out-of-bounds]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malvertising Campaign Targets Brazil's PIX Payment System with GoPIX Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/malvertising-campaign-targets-brazils.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/malvertising-campaign-targets-brazils.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T09:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The popularity of Brazil's PIX instant payment system has made it a lucrative target for threat actors looking to generate illicit profits using a new malware called GoPIX.
Kaspersky, which has been tracking the active campaign since December 2022, said the attacks are pulled off using malicious ads that are served when potential victims search for "WhatsApp web" on search engines.
"The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alert: PoC Exploits Released for Citrix and VMware Vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/alert-poc-exploits-released-for-citrix.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/alert-poc-exploits-released-for-citrix.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T04:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Virtualization services provider VMware has alerted customers to the existence of a proof-of-concept (PoC) exploit for a recently patched security flaw in Aria Operations for Logs.
Tracked as CVE-2023-34051 (CVSS score: 8.1), the high-severity vulnerability relates to a case of authentication bypass that could lead to remote code execution.
"An unauthenticated, malicious actor can inject files]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6438-2: .Net regressions]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6438-2</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6438-2"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T03:44:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6438-1 fixed vulnerabilities in .Net. It was discovered that the fix
for [CVE-2023-36799](https://ubuntu.com/security/CVE-2023-36799) was incomplete. This update fixes the problem.

Original advisory details:

 Kevin Jones discovered that .NET did not properly process certain
 X.509 certificates. An attacker could possibly use this issue to
 cause a denial of service. (CVE-2023-36799)
 
 It was discovered that the .NET Kestrel web server did not properly
 handle HTTP/2 requests. A remote attacker could possibly use this
 issue to cause a denial of service. (CVE-2023-44487)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6362-2: .Net regressions]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6362-2</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6362-2"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T03:26:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6362-1 fixed vulnerabilities in .Net. It was discovered that the fix
for [CVE-2023-36799](https://ubuntu.com/security/CVE-2023-36799) was incomplete. This update fixes the problem.

Original advisory details:

 Kevin Jones discovered that .NET did not properly process certain
 X.509 certificates. An attacker could possibly use this issue to
 cause a denial of service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Cybersecurity Awareness Month, Don't Lose Sight of Human Risk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/microsoft/this-cybersecurity-awareness-month-don-t-lose-sight-of-human-risk</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/microsoft/this-cybersecurity-awareness-month-don-t-lose-sight-of-human-risk"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Organizations should focus on four key areas to advance employee education and "cyber smartness."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Microsoft Security, Microsoft</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tines Report Finds More than Half of Security Professionals Likely To Switch Jobs Next Year]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/tines-report-finds-more-than-half-of-security-professionals-likely-to-switch-jobs-next-year</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/tines-report-finds-more-than-half-of-security-professionals-likely-to-switch-jobs-next-year"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2023 Ransomware Attacks Up More Than 95% Over 2022, According to Corvus Insurance Q3 Report]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/2023-ransomware-attacks-up-more-than-95-over-2022-according-to-corvus-insurance-q3-report</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/2023-ransomware-attacks-up-more-than-95-over-2022-according-to-corvus-insurance-q3-report"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T20:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accenture Expands Cybersecurity Services Capabilities in Latin America With Acquisition of MNEMO Mexico]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/accenture-expands-cybersecurity-services-capabilities-in-latin-america-with-acquisition-of-mnemo-mexico</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/accenture-expands-cybersecurity-services-capabilities-in-latin-america-with-acquisition-of-mnemo-mexico"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T20:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1Password Becomes Latest Victim of Okta Customer Service Breach]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/remote-workforce/1password-latest-victim-okta-customer-service-breach</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/remote-workforce/1password-latest-victim-okta-customer-service-breach"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T20:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Okta's IAM platform finds itself in cyberattackers' sights once again, as threat actors mount a supply chain attack targeting Okta customer support engagements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Rhysida, a New Ransomware Strain That Deletes Itself]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/meet-rhysida-a-new-ransomware-strain-that-deletes-itself</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/meet-rhysida-a-new-ransomware-strain-that-deletes-itself"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Emerging RaaS operation uses Rhysida ransomware paired with a wicked infostealer called Lumar, researchers warn.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former NSA Employee Faces Life in Prison After Espionage Attempt]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/risk/former-nsa-employee-faces-life-in-prison-after-espionage-attempt</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/risk/former-nsa-employee-faces-life-in-prison-after-espionage-attempt"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T19:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ex-employee claimed that he believed the shared information would benefit Russia and harm the US.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6451-1: ncurses vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6451-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6451-1"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T19:21:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was discovered that ncurses could be made to read out of bounds.
An attacker could possibly use this issue to cause a denial of service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do Small Companies Need Fractional AppSec Teams Akin to Virtual CISOs?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge-articles/do-small-companies-need-fractional-appsec-teams-much-like-vcisos-</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge-articles/do-small-companies-need-fractional-appsec-teams-much-like-vcisos-"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T17:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zatik takes a fractional approach to AppSec leadership to help small firms access the expertise they need to build secure-by-design software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ericka Chickowski, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strengthening Oman's Economic Backbone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/strengthening-omans-economic-backbone</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/strengthening-omans-economic-backbone"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a new regulatory framework to better secure Oman's banking system against future attacks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diamaka Aniagolu, Cybersecurity Writer &amp; Content Strategist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cyberattacks on Kenya Drop in Third Quarter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/cyber-attacks-on-kenya-drop-in-third-quarter</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/cyber-attacks-on-kenya-drop-in-third-quarter"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T16:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[National response team attributes reduction to a cyber workforce with better training.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6450-1: OpenSSL vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6450-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6450-1"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T16:14:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tony Battersby discovered that OpenSSL incorrectly handled key and
initialization vector (IV) lengths. This could lead to truncation issues
and result in loss of confidentiality for some symmetric cipher modes.
(CVE-2023-5363)

Juerg Wullschleger discovered that OpenSSL incorrectly handled the AES-SIV
cipher. This could lead to empty data entries being ignored, resulting in
certain applications being misled. This issue only affected Ubuntu 22.04
LTS and Ubuntu 23.04. (CVE-2023-2975)

It was discovered that OpenSSL incorrectly handled checking excessively
long DH keys or parameters. A remote attacker could possibly use this issue
to cause OpenSSL to consume resources, leading to a denial of service. This
issue only affected Ubuntu 22.04 LTS and Ubuntu 23.04. (CVE-2023-3446,
CVE-2023-3817)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israeli-Hamas Conflict Spells Opportunity for Online Scammers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/israeli-hamas-conflict-spells-opportunity-for-online-scammers</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/israeli-hamas-conflict-spells-opportunity-for-online-scammers"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T16:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the conflict in the Middle East rages, malicious actors look to exploit the situation with bogus charity sites encouraging donations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Eddy, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It's Time to Establish the NATO of Cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/its-time-to-establish-the-nato-of-cybersecurity</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/its-time-to-establish-the-nato-of-cybersecurity"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybercriminals already operate across borders. Nations must do the same to protect their critical infrastructure, people, and technology from threats foreign and domestic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Asaf Kochan, Co-Founder and President, Sentra, and Former Commander of Unit 8200</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Log in with...' Feature Allows Full Online Account Takeover for Millions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/remote-workforce/oauth-log-in-full-account-takeover-millions</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/remote-workforce/oauth-log-in-full-account-takeover-millions"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hundreds of millions of users of Grammarly, Vidio, and the Indonesian e-commerce giant Bukalapak are at risk for financial fraud and credential theft due to OAuth misfires — and other online services likely have the same problems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Montalbano, Contributor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-NSA Employee Pleads Guilty to Leaking Classified Data to Russia]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/ex-nsa-employee-pleads-guilty-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/ex-nsa-employee-pleads-guilty-to.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A former employee of the U.S. National Security Agency (NSA) has pleaded guilty to charges accusing him of attempting to transmit classified defense information to Russia.
Jareh Sebastian Dalke, 31, served as an Information Systems Security Designer for the NSA from June 6, 2022, to July 1, 2022, where he had Top Secret clearance to access sensitive documents. The latest development comes more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Releases One Industrial Control Systems Advisory]]></title>
        <id>/node/19030</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/10/24/cisa-releases-one-industrial-control-systems-advisory"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CISA released one Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisory on October 24, 2023. This advisory provides timely information about current security issues, vulnerabilities, and exploits surrounding ICS. 
ICSA-23-297-01 Rockwell Automation Stratix 5800 and Stratix 5200
CISA encourages users and administrators to review the newly released ICS advisory for technical details and mitigations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EPA Won’t Force Water Utilities to Audit Their Cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/10/epa-wont-force-water-utilities-to-audit-their-cybersecurity.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/10/epa-wont-force-water-utilities-to-audit-their-cybersecurity.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T11:02:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The industry <a href="https://www.engadget.com/the-epa-wont-force-water-utilities-to-inspect-their-cyber-defenses-232301497.html">pushed back</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>Despite the EPA&#8217;s willingness to provide training and technical support to help states and public water system organizations implement cybersecurity surveys, the move garnered opposition from both GOP state attorneys and trade groups.</p>
<p>Republican state attorneys that were against the new proposed policies said that the call for new inspections could overwhelm state regulators. The attorney generals of Arkansas, Iowa and <a href="https://www.courtlistener.com/docket/67221180/state-of-missouri-v-epa/">Missouri</a> all sued the EPA&#8212;claiming the agency had no authority to set these requirements. This led to the EPA&#8217;s proposal being ...</p></blockquote>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[34 Cybercriminals Arrested in Spain for Multi-Million Dollar Online Scams]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/34-cybercriminals-arrested-in-spain-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/34-cybercriminals-arrested-in-spain-for.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spanish law enforcement officials have announced the arrest of 34 members of a criminal group that carried out various online scams, netting the gang about €3 million ($3.2 million) in illegal profits.
Authorities conducted searches across 16 locations Madrid, Malaga, Huelva, Alicante, and Murcia, seizing two simulated firearms, a katana sword, a baseball bat, €80,000 in cash, four high-end]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Make API Management Less Scary for Your Organization]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/make-api-management-less-scary-for-your.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/make-api-management-less-scary-for-your.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T10:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While application development has evolved rapidly, the API management suites used to access these services remain a spooky reminder of a different era. Introducing new API management infrastructure with these legacy models still poses challenges for organizations as they modernize. Transitioning from monolithic architectures to agile microservices empowers developers to make quick changes. Using]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iOS Zero-Day Attacks: Experts Uncover Deeper Insights into Operation Triangulation]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/operation-triangulation-experts-uncover.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/operation-triangulation-experts-uncover.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T08:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The TriangleDB implant used to target Apple iOS devices packs in at least four different modules to record microphone, extract iCloud Keychain, steal data from SQLite databases used by various apps, and estimate the victim's location.
The new findings come from Kaspersky, which detailed the great lengths the adversary behind the campaign, dubbed Operation Triangulation, went to conceal and cover]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Backdoor Implanted on Hacked Cisco Devices Modified to Evade Detection]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/backdoor-implant-on-hacked-cisco.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/backdoor-implant-on-hacked-cisco.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T06:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The backdoor implanted on Cisco devices by exploiting a pair of zero-day flaws in IOS XE software has been modified by the threat actor so as to escape visibility via previous fingerprinting methods.
"Investigated network traffic to a compromised device has shown that the threat actor has upgraded the implant to do an extra header check," NCC Group's Fox-IT team said. "Thus, for a lot of devices]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1Password Detects Suspicious Activity Following Okta Support Breach]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/1password-detects-suspicious-activity.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/1password-detects-suspicious-activity.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T04:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Popular password management solution 1Password said it detected suspicious activity on its Okta instance on September 29 following the support system breach, but reiterated that no user data was accessed.
"We immediately terminated the activity, investigated, and found no compromise of user data or other sensitive systems, either employee-facing or user-facing," Pedro Canahuati, 1Password CTO,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cyberattackers Alter Implant on 30K Compromised Cisco IOS XE Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/remote-workforce/cyberattackers-alter-implant-30k-compromised-cisco-ios-xe-devices</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/remote-workforce/cyberattackers-alter-implant-30k-compromised-cisco-ios-xe-devices"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T20:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A seemingly sharp drop in the number of compromised Cisco IOS XE devices visible on the Internet led to a flurry of speculation over the weekend — but it turns out the malicious implants were just hiding.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Valve's 2FA Mandate for Game Developers Shows SMS Stickiness]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/valve-2fa-mandate-game-developers-sms-stickiness</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/valve-2fa-mandate-game-developers-sms-stickiness"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T20:25:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite warnings that sending one-time passwords via text messages is a flawed security measure, companies continue to roll out the approach, especially in consumer-facing applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Lemos, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hola Espana: 'Grandoreiro' Trojan Targets Global Banking Customers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/grandoreiro-trojan-targets-global-banking-customers</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/grandoreiro-trojan-targets-global-banking-customers"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T20:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brasileiro cybercrime has been on the rise. Now, one campaign targeting bank customers has reached beyond the Americas, into Europe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[City of Philadelphia Releases Cyber-Breach Notice]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/city-of-philadelphia-releases-cyber-breach-notice</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/city-of-philadelphia-releases-cyber-breach-notice"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T19:25:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The investigation is ongoing, and the city will contact those who may have potentially been affected by the breach, it said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How State and Local Governments Can Serve Citizens More Securely]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge/how-state-and-local-governments-can-serve-citizens-more-securely</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge/how-state-and-local-governments-can-serve-citizens-more-securely"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T19:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top 10 priorities of state CIOs underscore the importance of securing applications and APIs in complex environments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joshua Goldfarb, Security and Fraud Architect, F5</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ragnar Locker Ransomware Boss Arrested in Paris]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/ragnar-locker-ransomware-boss-arrested-paris</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/ragnar-locker-ransomware-boss-arrested-paris"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T18:53:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cops track down ransomware developer and seize Ragnar Locker infrastructure and data-leak site, Europol says.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malicious Apps Spoof Israeli Attack Detectors: Conflict Goes Mobile]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/malicious-apps-impersonate-israeli-attack-detectors-conflict-mobile</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/malicious-apps-impersonate-israeli-attack-detectors-conflict-mobile"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T18:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A spoofed version of an Israeli rocket-attack alerting app is targeting Android devices, in a campaign that shows how cyber-espionage attacks are shifting to individual, everyday citizens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Raywood, Senior Editor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Freelance Market Flooded With North Korean IT Actors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/careers-and-people/freelance-market-flooded-with-north-korean-it-actors</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/careers-and-people/freelance-market-flooded-with-north-korean-it-actors"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T17:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Organizations should be careful that the workers they hire on a freelance and temporary basis are not operatives working to funnel money to North Korea's WMD program, US DOJ says.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telling Small Businesses to Buy Cyber Insurance Isn't Enough]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/risk/telling-small-businesses-to-buy-cyber-insurance-isnt-enough</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/risk/telling-small-businesses-to-buy-cyber-insurance-isnt-enough"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To protect themselves from threats, companies also need proactive cybersecurity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zia Muhammad, Ph.D. Scholar, North Dakota State University</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Updates Guidance for Addressing Cisco IOS XE Web UI Vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>/node/19024</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/10/23/cisa-updates-guidance-addressing-cisco-ios-xe-web-ui-vulnerabilities"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, CISA updated its guidance addressing two vulnerabilities, CVE-2023-20198 and CVE-2023-20273, affecting Cisco’s Internetworking Operating System (IOS) XE Software Web User Interface (UI).
The guidance now notes that Cisco has fixed these vulnerabilities for the 17.9 Cisco IOS XE software release train with the 17.9.4a update. According to Cisco's Security Advisory: Multiple Vulnerabilities in Cisco IOS XE Software Web UI Feature, fixes are still to be determined for the following Cisco IOS XE software release trains: 17.6, 17.3, 16.12 (Catalyst 3650 and 3850 only). CISA urges organizations with the 17.9 Cisco IOS XE software release train to immediately update to the 17.9.4a release.
CISA urges organizations to review:
CISA’s updated guidance
Cisco Security Advisory: Multiple Vulnerabilities in Cisco IOS XE Software Web UI Feature
Cisco Talos Threat Advisory: Active exploitation of Cisco IOS XE Software Web Management User Interface vulnerabilities
CISA has added CVE-2023-20198 and CVE-2023-20273 to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog, which, per Binding Operational Directive (BOD) 22-01: Reducing the Significant Risk of Known Exploited Vulnerabilities, requires Federal Civilian Executive Branch (FCEB) agencies to remediate identified vulnerabilities by the specified due date to protect FCEB networks against active threats.
Note: The Cisco Security Advisory initially pointed to another vulnerability as part of this activity. However, as stated in the Cisco Talos Threat Advisory, Cisco has since determined that the vulnerability “CVE-2021-1435 that had previously been mentioned is no longer assessed to be associated with this activity.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Adds One Known Exploited Vulnerability to Catalog]]></title>
        <id>/node/19025</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/10/23/cisa-adds-one-known-exploited-vulnerability-catalog"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CISA has added one new vulnerability to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog, based on evidence of active exploitation.
CVE-2023-20273 Cisco IOS XE Web UI Command Injection Vulnerability
These types of vulnerabilities are frequent attack vectors for malicious cyber actors and pose significant risks to the federal enterprise. Note: To view other newly added vulnerabilities in the catalog, click on the arrow in the "Date Added to Catalog" column—which will sort by descending dates.
Binding Operational Directive (BOD) 22-01: Reducing the Significant Risk of Known Exploited Vulnerabilities established the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog as a living list of known Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVEs) that carry significant risk to the federal enterprise. BOD 22-01 requires Federal Civilian Executive Branch (FCEB) agencies to remediate identified vulnerabilities by the due date to protect FCEB networks against active threats. See the BOD 22-01 Fact Sheet for more information.
Although BOD 22-01 only applies to FCEB agencies, CISA strongly urges all organizations to reduce their exposure to cyberattacks by prioritizing timely remediation of Catalog vulnerabilities as part of their vulnerability management practice. CISA will continue to add vulnerabilities to the catalog that meet the specified criteria.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who's Experimenting with AI Tools in Your Organization?]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/whos-experimenting-with-ai-tools-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/whos-experimenting-with-ai-tools-in.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T11:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the record-setting growth of consumer-focused AI productivity tools like ChatGPT, artificial intelligence—formerly the realm of data science and engineering teams—has become a resource available to every employee. 
From a productivity perspective, that’s fantastic. Unfortunately for IT and security teams, it also means you may have hundreds of people in your organization using a new tool in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DoNot Team's New Firebird Backdoor Hits Pakistan and Afghanistan]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/donot-teams-new-firebird-backdoor-hits.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/donot-teams-new-firebird-backdoor-hits.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T11:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actor known as DoNot Team has been linked to the use of a novel .NET-based backdoor called Firebird targeting a handful of victims in Pakistan and Afghanistan.
Cybersecurity company Kaspersky, which disclosed the findings in its APT trends report Q3 2023, said the attack chains are also configured to deliver a downloader named CSVtyrei, so named for its resemblance to Vtyrei.
"Some]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerability Summary for the Week of October 16, 2023]]></title>
        <id>/node/19016</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/bulletins/sb23-296"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T11:17:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[High Vulnerabilities

Primary
Description
Published
CVSS Score
Source & Patch Info

1e -- platform
Affected 1E Platform versions have a Blind SQL Injection vulnerability that can lead to arbitrary code execution. Application of the relevant hotfix remediates this issue. for v8.1.2 apply hotfix Q23166 for v8.4.1 apply hotfix Q23164 for v9.0.1 apply hotfix Q23169 SaaS implementations on v23.7.1 will automatically have hotfix Q23173 applied. Customers with SaaS versions below this are urged to upgrade urgently - please contact 1E to arrange this
2023-10-13
9.8
CVE-2023-45162
MISC

advantech -- webaccess
Advantech WebAccess version 9.1.3 contains an exposure of sensitive information to an unauthorized actor vulnerability that could leak user credentials.
2023-10-17
7.5
CVE-2023-4215
MISC

apac…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Child Exploitation and the Crypto Wars]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/10/child-exploitation-and-the-crypto-wars.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/10/child-exploitation-and-the-crypto-wars.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T11:08:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Susan Landau published an <a href="https://www.lawfaremedia.org/article/the-shapeshifting-crypto-wars">excellent essay</a> on the current justification for the government breaking end-to-end-encryption: child sexual abuse and exploitation (CSAE). She puts the debate into historical context, discusses the problem of CSAE, and explains why breaking encryption isn&#8217;t the solution.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quasar RAT Leverages DLL Side-Loading to Fly Under the Radar]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/quasar-rat-leverages-dll-side-loading.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/quasar-rat-leverages-dll-side-loading.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T07:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The open-source remote access trojan known as Quasar RAT has been observed leveraging DLL side-loading to fly under the radar and stealthily siphon data from compromised Windows hosts.
"This technique capitalizes on the inherent trust these files command within the Windows environment," Uptycs researchers Tejaswini Sandapolla and Karthickkumar Kathiresan said in a report published last week,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FedRAMP Rev. 5: How Cloud Service Providers Can Prepare]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/risk/fedramp-rev-5-how-cloud-service-providers-can-prepare</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/risk/fedramp-rev-5-how-cloud-service-providers-can-prepare"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What cloud service providers need to know to prepare for FedRAMP Baselines Rev. 5, as documented in the new Transition Guide.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europol Dismantles Ragnar Locker Ransomware Infrastructure, Nabs Key Developer]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/europol-dismantles-ragnar-locker.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/europol-dismantles-ragnar-locker.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T13:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Europol on Friday announced the takedown of the infrastructure associated with Ragnar Locker ransomware, alongside the arrest of a "key target" in France.
"In an action carried out between 16 and 20 October, searches were conducted in Czechia, Spain, and Latvia," the agency said. "The main perpetrator, suspected of being a developer of the Ragnar group, has been brought in front of the examining]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Okta's Support System Breach Exposes Customer Data to Unidentified Threat Actors]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/oktas-support-system-breach-exposes.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/oktas-support-system-breach-exposes.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T08:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Identity services provider Okta on Friday disclosed a new security incident that allowed unidentified threat actors to leverage stolen credentials to access its support case management system.

"The threat actor was able to view files uploaded by certain Okta customers as part of recent support cases," David Bradbury, Okta's chief security officer, said. "It should be noted that the Okta]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco Zero-Day Exploited to Implant Malicious Lua Backdoor on Thousands of Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/cisco-zero-day-exploited-to-implant.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/cisco-zero-day-exploited-to-implant.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T03:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco has warned of a new zero-day flaw in IOS XE that has been actively exploited by an unknown threat actor to deploy a malicious Lua-based implant on susceptible devices.
Tracked as CVE-2023-20273 (CVSS score: 7.2), the issue relates to a privilege escalation flaw in the web UI feature and is said to have been used alongside CVE-2023-20198 (CVSS score: 10.0) as part of an exploit chain.
"The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[9 Innovative Ways to Boost Security Hygiene for Cyber Awareness Month]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge/9-innovative-ways-boost-security-hygiene-cybersecurity-awareness-month</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge/9-innovative-ways-boost-security-hygiene-cybersecurity-awareness-month"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T00:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If we really want to move the dial on security habits, it's time to think beyond phishing tests. Our panel of CISOs and other security heavy-hitters offer expert tips that go beyond the obvious.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tara Seals, Managing Editor, News, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More Okta Customers Hacked]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/more-okta-customers-hacked-through-support-service</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/more-okta-customers-hacked-through-support-service"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T21:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attackers compromised customer support files containing cookies and session tokens, which could result in malicious impersonation of valid Okta users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Snooze to Enthuse: Making Security Awareness Training 'Sticky']]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge/from-snooze-to-enthuse-security-awareness-training-that-sticks</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge/from-snooze-to-enthuse-security-awareness-training-that-sticks"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T21:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most companies offer some kind of awareness training these days. But how much of those lessons are employees actually retaining?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Goodchild, Senior Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friday Squid Blogging: Why There Are No Giant Squid in Aquariums]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/10/friday-squid-blogging-why-there-are-no-giant-squid-in-aquariums.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/10/friday-squid-blogging-why-there-are-no-giant-squid-in-aquariums.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T21:03:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>They&#8217;re too big and we <a href="https://www.iflscience.com/want-to-see-a-giant-squid-in-an-aquarium-heres-why-you-never-will-71011">can&#8217;t recreate</a> their habitat.</p>
<p>As usual, you can also use this squid post to talk about the security stories in the news that I haven’t covered.</p>
<p>Read my blog posting guidelines <a href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2017/03/commenting_poli.html">here</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical SolarWinds RCE Bugs Enable Unauthorized Network Takeover]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/critical-solarwinds-rce-bugs-enable-unauthorized-network-takeover</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/critical-solarwinds-rce-bugs-enable-unauthorized-network-takeover"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T20:27:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SolarWinds' access controls contain five high-severity and three critical-severity security vulnerabilities that need to be patched yesterday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco Finds New Zero-Day Bug, Pledges Patches in Days]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/cisco-zero-day-bug-patches-in-days</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/cisco-zero-day-bug-patches-in-days"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T20:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A patch for the max-severity zero-day bug tracked as CVE-2023-20198 is coming soon, but the bug has already led to the compromise of tens of thousands of Cisco devices. And now, there's a new unpatched threat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Becky Bracken, Editor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DoD Gets Closer to Nominating Cyber Policy Chief]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/dod-closer-nominating-cyber-policy-chief</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/dod-closer-nominating-cyber-policy-chief"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T18:48:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Though there is speculation regarding potential candidates, the Department of Defense will likely not nominate someone in the near term.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ducktail Infostealer, DarkGate RAT Linked to Same Threat Actors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/ducktail-infostealer-darkgate-rat-linked-to-same-threat-actors</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/ducktail-infostealer-darkgate-rat-linked-to-same-threat-actors"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T18:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vietnamese cybercrime groups are using multiple different MaaS infostealers and RATs to target the digital marketing sector.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Eddy, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SIM Card Ownership Slashed in Burkina Faso]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/sim-card-ownership-slashed-in-burkina-faso</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/sim-card-ownership-slashed-in-burkina-faso"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T18:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Users could hold up to five SIM cards previously, but now they can only have two; it's a move that the government says is intended to cut down mobile spam levels.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Change From Within: 3 Cybersecurity Transformation Traps for CISOs to Avoid]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/change-from-within-3-cybersecurity-transformation-traps-for-cisos-to-avoid</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/change-from-within-3-cybersecurity-transformation-traps-for-cisos-to-avoid"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To make cybersecurity an organizationwide priority, CISOs must avoid these common input, empathy, and alignment obstacles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernard Brantley, CISO, Corelight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malvertisers Using Google Ads to Target Users Searching for Popular Software]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/malvertisers-using-google-ads-to-target.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/malvertisers-using-google-ads-to-target.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T13:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Details have emerged about a malvertising campaign that leverages Google Ads to direct users searching for popular software to fictitious landing pages and distribute next-stage payloads.
Malwarebytes, which discovered the activity, said it's "unique in its way to fingerprint users and distribute time sensitive payloads."
The attack singles out users searching for Notepad++ and PDF converters to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vietnamese Hackers Target U.K., U.S., and India with DarkGate Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/vietnamese-hackers-target-uk-us-and.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/vietnamese-hackers-target-uk-us-and.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T13:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attacks leveraging the DarkGate commodity malware targeting entities in the U.K., the U.S., and India have been linked to Vietnamese actors associated with the use of the infamous Ducktail stealer.
"The overlap of tools and campaigns is very likely due to the effects of a cybercrime marketplace," WithSecure said in a report published today. "Threat actors are able to acquire and use multiple]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are Your Exception Expectations?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/google-cloud-security/what-are-your-exception-expectations</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/google-cloud-security/what-are-your-exception-expectations"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity exceptions are a fact of life in most organizations, but there's work that should be done to make sure those exceptions are justified and worth the risk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Martz, Manager, Google Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unleashing the Power of the Internet of Things and Cyber Security]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/unleashing-power-of-internet-of-things.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/unleashing-power-of-internet-of-things.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T11:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Due to the rapid evolution of technology, the Internet of Things (IoT) is changing the way business is conducted around the world. This advancement and the power of the IoT have been nothing short of transformational in making data-driven decisions, accelerating efficiencies, and streamlining operations to meet the demands of a competitive global marketplace.
IoT At a Crossroads
IoT, in its most]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI and US Election Rules]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/10/ai-and-us-election-rules.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/10/ai-and-us-election-rules.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T11:10:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>If an AI breaks the rules for you, does that count as breaking the rules? This is the essential question being taken up by the Federal Election Commission this month, and public input is needed to curtail the potential for AI to take US campaigns (even more) off the rails.</p>
<p>At issue is whether candidates using AI to create deepfaked media for political advertisements should be considered fraud or legitimate electioneering. That is, is it allowable to use <a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/6/8/23753626/deepfake-political-attack-ad-ron-desantis-donald-trump-anthony-fauci">AI image generators</a> to create photorealistic images depicting Trump hugging Anthony Fauci? And is it allowable to use ...</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ExelaStealer: A New Low-Cost Cybercrime Weapon Emerges]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/exelastealer-new-low-cost-cybercrime.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/exelastealer-new-low-cost-cybercrime.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T09:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new information stealer named ExelaStealer has become the latest entrant to an already crowded landscape filled with various off-the-shelf malware designed to capture sensitive data from compromised Windows systems.
"ExelaStealer is a largely open-source infostealer with paid customizations available from the threat actor," Fortinet FortiGuard Labs researcher James Slaughter said in a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. DoJ Cracks Down on North Korean IT Scammers Defrauding Global Businesses]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/us-doj-cracks-down-on-north-korean-it_20.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/us-doj-cracks-down-on-north-korean-it_20.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T05:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. government has announced the seizure of 17 website domains used by North Korean information technology (IT) workers as part of an illicit scheme to defraud businesses across the world, evade sanctions, and fund the country's ballistic missile program.
The Department of Justice (DoJ) said the U.S. confiscated approximately $1.5 million of the revenue that these IT workers collected from]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI 'Will Have a Significant Impact on Energy Industry,' EPRI Tells Congress]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/ai-will-have-a-significant-impact-on-energy-industry-epri-tells-congress</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/ai-will-have-a-significant-impact-on-energy-industry-epri-tells-congress"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T21:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Norton Boosts Security and Privacy With Enhanced Password Manager and AntiTrack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/norton-boosts-security-and-privacy-with-enhanced-password-manager-and-antitrack</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/norton-boosts-security-and-privacy-with-enhanced-password-manager-and-antitrack"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T21:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spec Secures $15M Series A Funding, Accelerating Innovation in Fraud Defense]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/spec-secures-15m-series-a-funding-accelerating-innovation-in-fraud-defense</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/spec-secures-15m-series-a-funding-accelerating-innovation-in-fraud-defense"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T21:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fingerprint Raises $33M in Series C Funding to Accelerate Enterprise Device Intelligence and Fraud Prevention Adoption]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/fingerprint-raises-33m-in-series-c-funding-to-accelerate-enterprise-device-intelligence-and-fraud-prevention-adoption</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/fingerprint-raises-33m-in-series-c-funding-to-accelerate-enterprise-device-intelligence-and-fraud-prevention-adoption"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SailPoint Unveils Annual 'Horizons of Identity Security' Report]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/sailpoint-unveils-annual-horizons-of-identity-security-report</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/sailpoint-unveils-annual-horizons-of-identity-security-report"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T20:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[23AndMe Hacker Leaks New Tranche of Stolen Data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/23andme-hacker-leaks-new-tranche-of-stolen-data-</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/23andme-hacker-leaks-new-tranche-of-stolen-data-"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T20:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two weeks after the first data leak from the DNA ancestry service, the threat actor produces an additional 4 million user records they purportedly stole.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean State Actors Attack Critical Bug in TeamCity Server]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/north-korean-state-actors-attack-critical-bug-in-teamcity-server</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/north-korean-state-actors-attack-critical-bug-in-teamcity-server"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T20:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Known threat groups Diamond Sleet and Onyx Sleet focus on cyber espionage, data theft, network sabotage, and other malicious actions, Microsoft says.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europol Strike Wounds Ragnar Locker Ransomware Group]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/europol-strike-ragnar-locker-ransomware</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/europol-strike-ragnar-locker-ransomware"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T19:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several countries in Europe as well as the United States and Japan were involved in the operation, which is aimed at defanging one of the bigger names in ransomware.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tips for a Successful SecOps Game Plan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge/tips-for-a-successful-secops-gameplan</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge/tips-for-a-successful-secops-gameplan"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dark Reading's special report on SecOps data analytics looks at the elements needed to set up a proper data foundation — because getting the data right when collecting, aggregating, and analyzing it is essential.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George V. Hulme, Contributor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI-Powered Israeli 'Cyber Dome' Defense Operation Comes to Life]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/ai-powered-israeli-cyber-dome-defense-operation-comes-to-life</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/ai-powered-israeli-cyber-dome-defense-operation-comes-to-life"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T17:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Israelis are building a cyber defense system that will use ChatGPT-like generative AI platforms to parse threat intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Do We Need Real-World Context to Prioritize CVEs?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge-ask-the-experts/why-do-cve-scores-need-real-world-context-to-prioritize</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge-ask-the-experts/why-do-cve-scores-need-real-world-context-to-prioritize"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Without the proper context, organizations waste time mitigating software flaws that won't likely affect their systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shachar Menashe, Senior Director of Security Research, JFrog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Q&A: The Outlook for Israeli Cyber Startups, As War Clouds Gather]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/outlook-israeli-cyber-startups-war-clouds-gather</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/outlook-israeli-cyber-startups-war-clouds-gather"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T16:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid the burgeoning war, Israel's tech sector is focused on resilience. Ofer Schreiber, senior partner at YL Ventures, weighs in on the conflict, funding for cybersecurity startups, overblown valuations, and what the future holds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Raywood, Senior Editor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Patch Now: APTs Continue to Pummel WinRAR Bug]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/patch-now-apts-pummel-winrar-bug</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/patch-now-apts-pummel-winrar-bug"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T15:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[State-sponsored cyber-espionage actors from Russia and China continue to target WinRAR users with various info-stealing and backdoor malware, as a patching lag plagues the software's footprint.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Montalbano, Contributor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iran-Linked 'MuddyWater' Spies on Mideast Gov't for 8 Months]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/iran-linked-muddywater-spies-middle-east-govt-eight-months</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/iran-linked-muddywater-spies-middle-east-govt-eight-months"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T14:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The state-sponsored threat actors (aka APT34, Crambus, Helix Kitten, or OilRig) spent months seemingly taking whatever government data they wished, using never-before-seen tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Trifecta of Consumer Data Privacy: Education, Advocacy & Accountability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/the-trifecta-of-consumer-data-privacy-education-advocacy-accountability</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/the-trifecta-of-consumer-data-privacy-education-advocacy-accountability"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's time to build a culture of privacy, one that businesses uphold.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arjun Bhatnagar, CEO, Cloaked</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sophisticated MATA Framework Strikes Eastern European Oil and Gas Companies]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/sophisticated-mata-framework-strikes.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/sophisticated-mata-framework-strikes.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T13:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An updated version of a sophisticated backdoor framework called MATA has been used in attacks aimed at over a dozen Eastern European companies in the oil and gas sector and defense industry as part of a cyber espionage operation that took place between August 2022 and May 2023.
"The actors behind the attack used spear-phishing mails to target several victims, some were infected with Windows]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerability Scanning: How Often Should I Scan?]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/vulnerability-scanning-how-often-should.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/vulnerability-scanning-how-often-should.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T11:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The time between a vulnerability being discovered and hackers exploiting it is narrower than ever – just 12 days. So it makes sense that organizations are starting to recognize the importance of not leaving long gaps between their scans, and the term "continuous vulnerability scanning" is becoming more popular. 
Hackers won’t wait for your next scan
One-off scans can be a simple ‘one-and-done']]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Play Protect Introduces Real-Time Code-Level Scanning for Android Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/google-play-protect-introduces-real.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/google-play-protect-introduces-real.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T11:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has announced an update to its Play Protect with support for real-time scanning at the code level to tackle novel malicious apps prior to downloading and installing them on Android devices.
"Google Play Protect will now recommend a real-time app scan when installing apps that have never been scanned before to help detect emerging threats," the tech giant said.
Google Play Protect is a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Uber CISO Appealing His Conviction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/10/former-uber-ciso-appealing-his-conviction.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/10/former-uber-ciso-appealing-his-conviction.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T11:08:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Joe Sullivan, Uber&#8217;s CEO during their 2016 data breach, is <a href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/former-uber-ciso-appeals-conviction-over-2016-data-breach">appealing</a> his conviction.</p>
<blockquote><p>Prosecutors charged Sullivan, whom Uber hired as CISO after the 2014 breach, of withholding information about the 2016 incident from the FTC even as its investigators were scrutinizing the company&#8217;s data security and privacy practices. The government argued that Sullivan should have informed the FTC of the 2016 incident, but instead went out of his way to conceal it from them.</p>
<p>Prosecutors also accused Sullivan of attempting to conceal the breach itself by paying $100,000 to buy the silence of the two hackers behind the compromise. Sullivan had characterized the payment as a bug bounty similar to ones that other companies routinely make to researchers who report vulnerabilities and other security issues to them. His lawyers pointed out that Sullivan had made the payment with the full knowledge and blessing of Travis Kalanick, Uber&#8217;s CEO at the time, and other members of the ride-sharing giant&#8217;s legal team...</p></blockquote>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iran-Linked OilRig Targets Middle East Governments in 8-Month Cyber Campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/iran-linked-oilrig-targets-middle-east.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/iran-linked-oilrig-targets-middle-east.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T10:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Iran-linked OilRig threat actor targeted an unnamed Middle East government between February and September 2023 as part of an eight-month-long campaign.
The attack led to the theft of files and passwords and, in one instance, resulted in the deployment of a PowerShell backdoor called PowerExchange, the Symantec Threat Hunter Team, part of Broadcom, said in a report shared with The Hacker News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Warns of North Korean Attacks Exploiting JetBrains TeamCity Flaw]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/microsoft-warns-of-north-korean-attacks.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/microsoft-warns-of-north-korean-attacks.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T07:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean threat actors are actively exploiting a critical security flaw in JetBrains TeamCity to opportunistically breach vulnerable servers, according to Microsoft.
The attacks, which entail the exploitation of CVE-2023-42793 (CVSS score: 9.8), have been attributed to Diamond Sleet (aka Labyrinth Chollima) and Onyx Sleet (aka Andariel or Silent Chollima).
It's worth noting that both the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google TAG Detects State-Backed Threat Actors Exploiting WinRAR Flaw]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/google-tag-detects-state-backed-threat.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/google-tag-detects-state-backed-threat.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T04:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A number of state-back threat actors from Russia and China have been observed exploiting a recent security flaw in the WinRAR archiver tool for Windows as part of their operations.
The vulnerability in question is CVE-2023-38831 (CVSS score: 7.8), which allows attackers to execute arbitrary code when a user attempts to view a benign file within a ZIP archive. The shortcoming has been actively]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What CISOs Should Exclude From SEC Cybersecurity Filings]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge/what-cisos-should-exclude-from-sec-cybersecurity-filings</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge/what-cisos-should-exclude-from-sec-cybersecurity-filings"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T21:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Should CISOs include only known information in the SEC filings for a material security incident, or is there room to include details that may change during the investigation?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evan Schuman, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[D-Link Confirms Breach, Rebuts Hacker's Claims About Scope]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/d-link-confirms-breach-rebuts-hackers-claims-scope</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/d-link-confirms-breach-rebuts-hackers-claims-scope"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T21:16:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The router specialist says the attacker's claims to have heisted millions and millions of records are significantly overblown. But an incident did happen, stemming from a successful phish.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI: Hackers Are Extorting Plastic Surgery Providers, Patients]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/fbi-hackers-extorting-plastic-surgery-providers-patients</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/fbi-hackers-extorting-plastic-surgery-providers-patients"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T20:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The sensitive nature of medical records, combined with providers' focus on patient care, make small doctor's offices ideal targets for  cyber extortion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Most Popular IT Admin Password Is Totally Depressing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/the-most-popular-it-admin-password-is-totally-depressing</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/the-most-popular-it-admin-password-is-totally-depressing"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T19:02:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analysis of more than 1.8 million admin portals reveals IT leaders, with the highest privileges, are just as lazy about passwords as everyone else.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Becky Bracken, Editor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OCP Launches SAFE to Standardize Firmware Audits]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge/ocp-launches-safe-to-standardize-firmware-audits</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge/ocp-launches-safe-to-standardize-firmware-audits"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Under the Security Appraisal Framework and Enablement (SAFE) program, device manufacturers will be able to work with approved auditors to verify firmware.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edge Editors, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Citrix Bug Exploited as a Zero-Day, 'Patching Is Not Enough']]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/critical-citrix-bug-exploited-zero-day-patching-not-enough</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/critical-citrix-bug-exploited-zero-day-patching-not-enough"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T18:49:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest threat to Citrix NetScaler, CVE-2023-4966, was exploited as a zero-day bug for months before a patch was issued. Researchers expect exploitation efforts to surge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tara Seals, Managing Editor, News, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Source Security Agents Promise Greater Simplicity, Flexibility]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/open-source-security-agents-promise-greater-simplicity-flexibility</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/open-source-security-agents-promise-greater-simplicity-flexibility"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T18:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Endpoint management based on open source agents, such as osquery, could simplify IT management and security while giving larger firms more customization options.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Lemos, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EPA Turns Off Taps on Water Utility Cyber Regulations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/ics-ot/epa-water-utility-cyber-regulations</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/ics-ot/epa-water-utility-cyber-regulations"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T17:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Facing a potential cascade of legal challenges from industry groups and state attorneys general, the EPA has rescinded its cyber-rules. But where does that leave local water safety?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tara Seals, Managing Editor, News, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korea's Kimsuky Doubles Down on Remote Desktop Control]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/north-korea-s-kimsuky-doubles-down-on-remote-desktop-control</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/north-korea-s-kimsuky-doubles-down-on-remote-desktop-control"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T16:11:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The sophisticated APT employs various tactics to abuse Windows and other built-in protocols with both custom and public malware to take over victim systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Montalbano, Contributor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lazarus Group Targeting Defense Experts with Fake Interviews via Trojanized VNC Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/lazarus-group-targeting-defense-experts.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/lazarus-group-targeting-defense-experts.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T14:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The North Korea-linked Lazarus Group (aka Hidden Cobra or TEMP.Hermit) has been observed using trojanized versions of Virtual Network Computing (VNC) apps as lures to target the defense industry and nuclear engineers as part of a long-running campaign known as Operation Dream Job.
"The threat actor tricks job seekers on social media into opening malicious apps for fake job interviews," Kaspersky]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Need for a Cybersecurity-Centric Business Culture]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/the-need-for-a-cybersecurity-centric-business-culture</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/the-need-for-a-cybersecurity-centric-business-culture"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building a culture of cybersecurity is achievable by acknowledging its importance and consistently reinforcing that message.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Jansen, Vice President &amp; Global Lead of Cyber Incident Response Services, Consilio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pro-Iranian Hacktivists Set Sights on Israeli Industrial Control Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/pro-iranian-hacktivists-sights-israeli-industrial-control-systems</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/pro-iranian-hacktivists-sights-israeli-industrial-control-systems"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T13:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The hacktivists known as SiegedSec identify ICS targets, but there's no evidence of attacks yet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Raywood, Senior Editor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israeli Cybersecurity Startups: Impact of a Growing Conflict]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/israeli-cybersecurity-startups-impact-of-a-growing-conflict-</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/israeli-cybersecurity-startups-impact-of-a-growing-conflict-"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T13:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For Israeli startups and those closely linked to the country, the deepening crisis in the Middle East following the deadly Hamas attacks of Oct. 7 pose a fraught mix of complications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Eddy, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Citrix NetScaler Flaw Exploited to Target from Government, Tech Firms]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/critical-citrix-netscaler-flaw.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/critical-citrix-netscaler-flaw.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T12:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Citrix is warning of exploitation of a recently disclosed critical security flaw in NetScaler ADC and Gateway appliances that could result in exposure of sensitive information.
Tracked as CVE-2023-4966 (CVSS score: 9.4), the vulnerability impacts the following supported versions -

NetScaler ADC and NetScaler Gateway 14.1 before 14.1-8.50
NetScaler ADC and NetScaler Gateway 13.1 before]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unraveling Real-Life Attack Paths – Key Lessons Learned]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/unraveling-real-life-attack-paths-key.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/unraveling-real-life-attack-paths-key.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T11:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the ever-evolving landscape of cybersecurity, attackers are always searching for vulnerabilities and exploits within organizational environments. They don't just target single weaknesses; they're on the hunt for combinations of exposures and attack methods that can lead them to their desired objective.
Despite the presence of numerous security tools, organizations often have to deal with two]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qubitstrike Targets Jupyter Notebooks with Crypto Mining and Rootkit Campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/qubitstrike-targets-jupyter-notebooks.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/qubitstrike-targets-jupyter-notebooks.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T11:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A threat actor, presumably from Tunisia, has been linked to a new campaign targeting exposed Jupyter Notebooks in a two-fold attempt to illicitly mine cryptocurrency and breach cloud environments.
Dubbed Qubitstrike by Cado, the intrusion set utilizes Telegram API to exfiltrate cloud service provider credentials following a successful compromise.
"The payloads for the Qubitstrike campaign are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analysis of Intellexa’s Predator Spyware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/10/analysis-of-intellexas-predator-spyware.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/10/analysis-of-intellexas-predator-spyware.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T11:06:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Amnesty International has <a href="https://securitylab.amnesty.org/latest/2023/10/global-predator-files-investigation-reveals-catastrophic-failure-to-regulate-surveillance-trade/">published</a> a comprehensive analysis of the Predator government spyware products.</p>
<p>These technologies used to be the exclusive purview of organizations like the NSA. Now they&#8217;re available to every country on the planet&#8212;democratic, nondemocratic, authoritarian, whatever&#8212;for a price. This is the legacy of not securing the Internet when we could have.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jupyter Notebook Ripe for Cloud Credential Theft, Researchers Warn]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/jupyter-notebook-cloud-credential-theft</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/jupyter-notebook-cloud-credential-theft"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If not correctly locked down, Jupyter Notebook offers a novel initial access vector that hackers can use to compromise enterprise cloud environments, as seen in a recent hacking incident.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TetrisPhantom: Cyber Espionage via Secure USBs Targets APAC Governments]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/tetrisphantom-cyber-espionage-via.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/tetrisphantom-cyber-espionage-via.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T09:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Government entities in the Asia-Pacific (APAC) region are the target of a long-running cyber espionage campaign dubbed TetrisPhantom.
"The attacker covertly spied on and harvested sensitive data from APAC government entities by exploiting a particular type of secure USB drive, protected by hardware encryption to ensure the secure storage and transfer of data between computer systems," Kaspersky]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Admin Takeover Vulnerability Exposed in Synology's DiskStation Manager]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/new-admin-takeover-vulnerability.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/new-admin-takeover-vulnerability.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T06:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A medium-severity flaw has been discovered in Synology's DiskStation Manager (DSM) that could be exploited to decipher an administrator's password and remotely hijack the account.
"Under some rare conditions, an attacker could leak enough information to restore the seed of the pseudorandom number generator (PRNG), reconstruct the admin password, and remotely take over the admin account,"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[D-Link Confirms Data Breach: Employee Falls Victim to Phishing Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/d-link-confirms-data-breach-employee.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/d-link-confirms-data-breach-employee.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T03:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taiwanese networking equipment manufacturer D-Link has confirmed a data breach that led to the exposure of what it said is "low-sensitivity and semi-public information."
"The data was confirmed not from the cloud but likely originated from an old D-View 6 system, which reached its end of life as early as 2015," the company said.
"The data was used for registration purposes back then. So far, no]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Security and Collaboration in the Modern Enterprise]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/tech-trends/data-security-collaboration-in-modern-enterprise</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/tech-trends/data-security-collaboration-in-modern-enterprise"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The "CISO Survival Guide" explores the complex and shifting challenges, perceptions, and innovations that will shape how organizations securely expand in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rey Kirton, Vice President, Forgepoint Capital</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Quietly Wades Into the Passkey Waters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/amazon-quietly-wades-into-passkey-waters</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/amazon-quietly-wades-into-passkey-waters"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The move by the e-commerce kahuna to offer advanced authentication to its 300+ million users has the potential to move the needle on the technology's adoption, security experts say.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tara Seals, Managing Editor, News, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chatbot Offers Roadmap for How to Conduct a Bio Weapons Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/chatbot-roadmap-how-to-conduct-a-bio-weapons-attack</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/chatbot-roadmap-how-to-conduct-a-bio-weapons-attack"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once ethics guardrails are breached, generative AI and LLMs could become nearly unlimited in its capacity to enable evil acts, researchers warn.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UAE, US Partner to Bolster Financial Services Cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/uae-and-us-partner-to-bolster-financial-services-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/uae-and-us-partner-to-bolster-financial-services-security"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T19:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The two countries agree to share financial services information and provide cross-border training and best practices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zero-Day Alert: Thousands of Cisco IOS XE Systems Now Compromised]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/ten-thousand-cisco-ios-xe-systems-compromised-zero-day-bug</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/ten-thousand-cisco-ios-xe-systems-compromised-zero-day-bug"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T19:16:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just a day after Cisco disclosed CVE-2023-20198, it remains unpatched, and one vendor says a Shodan scan shows at least 10,000 Cisco devices with an implant for arbitrary code execution on them. The vendor meanwhile has updated the advisory with more mitigation steps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Etherhiding' Blockchain Technique Masks Malicious Code in WordPress Sites]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/etherhiding-blockchain-technique-hides-malicious-code-wordpress-sites</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/etherhiding-blockchain-technique-hides-malicious-code-wordpress-sites"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T18:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ClearFake campaign uses fake browser updates to lure victims and spread RedLine, Amadey, and Lumma stealers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Montalbano, Contributor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watch Out: Attackers Are Hiding Malware in 'Browser Updates']]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/watch-out-attackers-hiding-malware-browser-updates</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/watch-out-attackers-hiding-malware-browser-updates"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T16:34:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Updating your browser when prompted is a good practice, just make sure the notification comes from the vendor themselves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Discord: A Playground for Nation-State Hackers Targeting Critical Infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/discord-playground-for-nation-state.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/discord-playground-for-nation-state.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T14:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In what's the latest evolution of threat actors abusing legitimate infrastructure for nefarious ends, new findings show that nation-state hacking groups have entered the fray in leveraging the social platform for targeting critical infrastructure.
Discord, in recent years, has become a lucrative target, acting as a fertile ground for hosting malware using its content delivery network (CDN) as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Vulnerabilities Uncovered in Open Source CasaOS Cloud Software]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/critical-vulnerabilities-uncovered-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/10/critical-vulnerabilities-uncovered-in.html"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T14:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two critical security flaws discovered in the open-source CasaOS personal cloud software could be successfully exploited by attackers to achieve arbitrary code execution and take over susceptible systems.
The vulnerabilities, tracked as CVE-2023-37265 and CVE-2023-37266, both carry a CVSS score of 9.8 out of a maximum of 10.
Sonar security researcher Thomas Chauchefoin, who discovered the bugs,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 6 Mistakes in Incident Response Tabletop Exercises]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/top-6-mistakes-in-incident-response-tabletop-exercises</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/top-6-mistakes-in-incident-response-tabletop-exercises"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avoid these errors to get the greatest value from your incident response training sessions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan René Rosado, Security Solution Architect, Trace3</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerability Summary for the Week of October 9, 2023]]></title>
        <id>/node/18971</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/bulletins/sb23-289"/>
        <updated>2023-10-16T11:09:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[High Vulnerabilities

Primary
Description
Published
CVSS Score
Source & Patch Info

3ds -- teamwork_cloud_no_magic_release
A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability affecting Teamwork Cloud from No Magic Release 2021x through No Magic Release 2022x could allow with some very specific conditions an attacker to send a specifically crafted query to the server.
2023-10-09
8.8
CVE-2023-3589
MISC

acronis -- agent
Local privilege escalation due to DLL hijacking vulnerability. The following products are affected: Acronis Agent (Windows) before build 36497.
2023-10-09
7.3
CVE-2023-45248
MISC

acronis -- agent
Sensitive information disclosure and manipulation due to missing authorization. The following products are affected: Acronis Agent (Linux, macOS, Windows) before build 35895.
2023-10-…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Congratulations to the Top MSRC 2023 Q3 Security Researchers!]]></title>
        <id>https://msrc.microsoft.com/blog/2023/10/congratulations-to-the-top-msrc-2023-q3-security-researchers/</id>
        <link href="https://msrc.microsoft.com/blog/2023/10/congratulations-to-the-top-msrc-2023-q3-security-researchers/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-16T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Congratulations to all the researchers recognized in this quarter’s Microsoft Researcher Recognition Program leaderboard! Thank you to everyone for your hard work and continued partnership to secure customers.
The top three researchers of the 2023 Q3 Security Researcher Leaderboard are Wei, VictorV, and Anonymous!
Check out the full list of researchers recognized this quarter here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Microsoft Security Response Center</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Threat Actors Exploit Atlassian Confluence CVE-2023-22515 for Initial Access to Networks]]></title>
        <id>/node/18970</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/cybersecurity-advisories/aa23-289a"/>
        <updated>2023-10-13T20:48:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUMMARY
The Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA), Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI), and Multi-State Information Sharing and Analysis Center (MS-ISAC) are releasing this joint Cybersecurity Advisory (CSA) in response to the active exploitation of CVE-2023-22515. This recently disclosed vulnerability affects certain versions of Atlassian Confluence Data Center and Server, enabling malicious cyber threat actors to obtain initial access to Confluence instances by creating unauthorized Confluence administrator accounts. Threat actors exploited CVE-2023-22515 as a zero-day to obtain access to victim systems and continue active exploitation post-patch. Atlassian has rated this vulnerability as critical; CISA, FBI, and MS-ISAC expect widespread, continued exploitation due t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the Microsoft AI Bug Bounty Program featuring the AI-powered Bing experience]]></title>
        <id>https://msrc.microsoft.com/blog/2023/10/introducing-the-microsoft-ai-bug-bounty-program-featuring-the-ai-powered-bing-experience/</id>
        <link href="https://msrc.microsoft.com/blog/2023/10/introducing-the-microsoft-ai-bug-bounty-program-featuring-the-ai-powered-bing-experience/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today at BlueHat we announced the new Microsoft AI bug bounty program with awards up to $15,000. This new bounty program features the AI-powered Bing experience as the first in scope product. The following products and integrations are eligible for bounty awards:
AI-powered Bing experiences on bing.com in Browser (All major vendors are supported, including Bing Chat, Bing Chat for Enterprise, and Bing Image Creator) AI-powered Bing integration in Microsoft Edge (Windows), including Bing Chat for Enterprise AI-powered Bing integration in the Microsoft Start Application (iOS and Android) AI-powered Bing integration in the Skype Mobile Application (iOS and Android) Full details can be found on our bounty program website.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Microsoft Security Response Center</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[#StopRansomware: AvosLocker Ransomware (Update)]]></title>
        <id>/node/18935</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/cybersecurity-advisories/aa23-284a"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T15:46:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUMMARY
Note: This joint Cybersecurity Advisory (CSA) is part of an ongoing #StopRansomware effort to publish advisories for network defenders that detail various ransomware variants and ransomware threat actors. These #StopRansomware advisories include recently and historically observed tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs) and indicators of compromise (IOCs) to help organizations protect against ransomware. Visit stopransomware.gov to see all #StopRansomware advisories and to learn more about other ransomware threats and no-cost resources.
The Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) and the Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) are releasing this joint Cybersecurity Advisory (CSA) to disseminate known IOCs, TTPs, and detection methods associated with the AvosLocker v…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerability Summary for the Week of October 2, 2023]]></title>
        <id>/node/18930</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/bulletins/sb23-283"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T10:08:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[High Vulnerabilities

Primary
Description
Published
CVSS Score
Source & Patch Info

acronis -- agent
Local privilege escalation due to improper soft link handling. The following products are affected: Acronis Agent (Linux, macOS, Windows) before build 29051.
2023-10-04
7.8
CVE-2023-44209
MISC

acronis -- cyber_protect_home_office
Sensitive information disclosure and manipulation due to missing authorization. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect Home Office (Windows) before build 40713.
2023-10-04
9.1
CVE-2023-44208
MISC

afterlogic -- aurora_files
A deserialization vulnerability in Afterlogic Aurora Files v9.7.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via supplying a crafted .sabredav file.
2023-10-03
8.8
CVE-2023-43176
MISC
MISC
MISC
MISC

apple -- ipados/ios
The …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Response to Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) Attacks against HTTP/2]]></title>
        <id>https://msrc.microsoft.com/blog/2023/10/microsoft-response-to-distributed-denial-of-service-ddos-attacks-against-http/2/</id>
        <link href="https://msrc.microsoft.com/blog/2023/10/microsoft-response-to-distributed-denial-of-service-ddos-attacks-against-http/2/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summary Summary Beginning in September 2023, Microsoft was notified by industry partners about a newly identified Distributed Denial-of-Service (DDoS) attack technique being used in the wild targeting HTTP/2 protocol. This vulnerability (CVE-2023-44487) impacts any internet exposed HTTP/2 endpoints. As an industry leader, Microsoft promptly opened an investigation and subsequently began working with industry partners for a coordinated disclosure and mitigation plan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Microsoft Security Response Center</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity Awareness Month 2023: Elevating Security Together]]></title>
        <id>https://msrc.microsoft.com/blog/2023/10/cybersecurity-awareness-month-2023-elevating-security-together/</id>
        <link href="https://msrc.microsoft.com/blog/2023/10/cybersecurity-awareness-month-2023-elevating-security-together/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the 20th anniversary of Cybersecurity Awareness Month begins, I find myself reflecting on the strides made since its inception. The journey to enhance and improve cybersecurity is ongoing and extends beyond October. It’s not merely a technological challenge; it is fundamentally about people. It’s about the customers and communities that we at Microsoft work tirelessly to safeguard and defend.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Microsoft Security Response Center</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NSA and CISA Red and Blue Teams Share Top Ten Cybersecurity Misconfigurations]]></title>
        <id>/node/18905</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/cybersecurity-advisories/aa23-278a"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T19:42:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A plea for network defenders and software manufacturers to fix common problems.
EXECUTIVE SUMMARY
The National Security Agency (NSA) and Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) are releasing this joint cybersecurity advisory (CSA) to highlight the most common cybersecurity misconfigurations in large organizations, and detail the tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs) actors use to exploit these misconfigurations.
Through NSA and CISA Red and Blue team assessments, as well as through the activities of NSA and CISA Hunt and Incident Response teams, the agencies identified the following 10 most common network misconfigurations:
Default configurations of software and applications
Improper separation of user/administrator privilege
Insufficient internal network monitoring
La…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerability Summary for the Week of September 25, 2023]]></title>
        <id>/node/18904</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/bulletins/sb23-275"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T11:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[High Vulnerabilities

Primary
Description
Published
CVSS Score
Source & Patch Info

accusoft -- imagegear
An out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in the tiff_planar_adobe functionality of Accusoft ImageGear 20.1. A specially crafted malformed file can lead to memory corruption. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.
2023-09-25
9.8
CVE-2023-32284
MISC

accusoft -- imagegear
A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the create_png_object functionality of Accusoft ImageGear 20.1. A specially crafted malformed file can lead to memory corruption. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.
2023-09-25
9.8
CVE-2023-32614
MISC

accusoft -- imagegear
A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the pictwread functio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft’s Response to Open-Source Vulnerabilities - CVE-2023-4863 and CVE-2023-5217]]></title>
        <id>https://msrc.microsoft.com/blog/2023/10/microsofts-response-to-open-source-vulnerabilities-cve-2023-4863-and-cve-2023-5217/</id>
        <link href="https://msrc.microsoft.com/blog/2023/10/microsofts-response-to-open-source-vulnerabilities-cve-2023-4863-and-cve-2023-5217/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is aware and has released patches associated with the two Open-Source Software security vulnerabilities, CVE-2023-4863 and CVE-2023-5217. Through our investigation, we found that these affect a subset of our products and as of today, we have addressed them in our products as outlined below: CVE-2023-4863
Microsoft Edge Microsoft Teams for Desktop Skype for Desktop Webp Image Extensions (Released on Windows and updates through Microsoft Store) CVE-2023-5217]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Microsoft Security Response Center</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerability Summary for the Week of September 18, 2023]]></title>
        <id>/node/18896</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/bulletins/sb23-272"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T13:31:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[High Vulnerabilities

Primary
Description
Published
CVSS Score
Source & Patch Info

acronis -- cyber_protect_home_office
Sensitive information disclosure due to insecure folder permissions. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect Home Office (Windows) before build 40713.
2023-09-20
7.5
CVE-2023-5042
MISC

apple -- multiple_products
The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in Safari 17, iOS 16.7 and iPadOS 16.7, macOS Sonoma 14. Processing web content may lead to arbitrary code execution. Apple is aware of a report that this issue may have been actively exploited against versions of iOS before iOS 16.7.
2023-09-21
9.8
CVE-2023-41993
MISC
MISC
MISC
MISC

apple -- multiple_products
The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>