<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://ehsanedalat.github.io/securitynews/index.html</id>
    <title>News | S&amp;P Homepage</title>
    <updated>2023-09-10T01:09:57.534Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://ehsanedalat.github.io/securitynews/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://ehsanedalat.github.io/securitynews/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Millions Infected by Spyware Hidden in Fake Telegram Apps on Google Play]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/millions-infected-by-spyware-hidden-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/millions-infected-by-spyware-hidden-in.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T08:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spyware masquerading as modified versions of Telegram have been spotted in the Google Play Store that’s designed to harvest sensitive information from compromised Android devices.
According to Kaspersky security researcher Igor Golovin, the apps come with nefarious features to capture and exfiltrate names, user IDs, contacts, phone numbers, and chat messages to an actor-controlled server.
The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybercriminals Weaponizing Legitimate Advanced Installer Tool in Crypto-Mining Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/cybercriminals-weaponizing-legitimate.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/cybercriminals-weaponizing-legitimate.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T06:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A legitimate Windows tool used for creating software packages called Advanced Installer is being abused by threat actors to drop cryptocurrency-mining malware on infected machines since at least November 2021.
"The attacker uses Advanced Installer to package other legitimate software installers, such as Adobe Illustrator, Autodesk 3ds Max, and SketchUp Pro, with malicious scripts and uses]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6338-2: Linux kernel vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6338-2</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6338-2"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T22:26:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zi Fan Tan discovered that the binder IPC implementation in the Linux
kernel contained a use-after-free vulnerability. A local attacker could use
this to cause a denial of service (system crash) or possibly execute
arbitrary code. (CVE-2023-21255)

It was discovered that a race condition existed in the f2fs file system in
the Linux kernel, leading to a null pointer dereference vulnerability. An
attacker could use this to construct a malicious f2fs image that, when
mounted and operated on, could cause a denial of service (system crash).
(CVE-2023-2898)

It was discovered that the DVB Core driver in the Linux kernel did not
properly handle locking events in certain situations. A local attacker
could use this to cause a denial of service (kernel deadlock).
(CVE-2023-31084)

Quentin Minster di…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6339-2: Linux kernel vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6339-2</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6339-2"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T21:44:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was discovered that the NTFS file system implementation in the Linux
kernel did not properly validate MFT flags in certain situations. An
attacker could use this to construct a malicious NTFS image that, when
mounted and operated on, could cause a denial of service (system crash).
(CVE-2022-48425)

Zi Fan Tan discovered that the binder IPC implementation in the Linux
kernel contained a use-after-free vulnerability. A local attacker could use
this to cause a denial of service (system crash) or possibly execute
arbitrary code. (CVE-2023-21255)

It was discovered that a race condition existed in the f2fs file system in
the Linux kernel, leading to a null pointer dereference vulnerability. An
attacker could use this to construct a malicious f2fs image that, when
mounted and operated on, could cause a denial of service (system crash).
(CVE-2023-2898)

It was discovered that the DVB Core driver in the Linux kernel did not
properly handle locking events in certain situations. A local attacker
could use this to cause a denial of service (kernel deadlock).
(CVE-2023-31084)

Yang Lan discovered that the GFS2 file system implementation in the Linux
kernel could attempt to dereference a null pointer in some situations. An
attacker could use this to construct a malicious GFS2 image that, when
mounted and operated on, could cause a denial of service (system crash).
(CVE-2023-3212)

It was discovered that the KSMBD implementation in the Linux kernel did not
properly validate buffer sizes in certain operations, leading to an out-of-
bounds read vulnerability. A remote attacker could use this to cause a
denial of service (system crash) or possibly expose sensitive information.
(CVE-2023-38426, CVE-2023-38428)

It was discovered that the KSMBD implementation in the Linux kernel did not
properly calculate the size of certain buffers. A remote attacker could use
this to cause a denial of service (system crash) or possibly execute
arbitrary code. (CVE-2023-38429)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6340-2: Linux kernel vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6340-2</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6340-2"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T21:36:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ruihan Li discovered that the bluetooth subsystem in the Linux kernel did
not properly perform permissions checks when handling HCI sockets. A
physically proximate attacker could use this to cause a denial of service
(bluetooth communication). (CVE-2023-2002)

Zi Fan Tan discovered that the binder IPC implementation in the Linux
kernel contained a use-after-free vulnerability. A local attacker could use
this to cause a denial of service (system crash) or possibly execute
arbitrary code. (CVE-2023-21255)

Juan Jose Lopez Jaimez, Meador Inge, Simon Scannell, and Nenad Stojanovski
discovered that the BPF verifier in the Linux kernel did not properly mark
registers for precision tracking in certain situations, leading to an out-
of-bounds access vulnerability. A local attacker could use this t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friday Squid Blogging: Glass Squid Video]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/09/friday-squid-blogging-glass-squid-video.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/09/friday-squid-blogging-glass-squid-video.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T21:03:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Here&#8217;s a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lAKQu9CiIfc">fantastic video</a> of <i>Taonius Borealis</i>, a glass squid, from NOAA.</p>
<p>As usual, you can also use this squid post to talk about the security stories in the news that I haven’t covered.</p>
<p>Read my blog posting guidelines <a href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2017/03/commenting_poli.html">here</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6342-2: Linux kernel (Azure)]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6342-2</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6342-2"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T20:18:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tavis Ormandy discovered that some AMD processors did not properly handle
speculative execution of certain vector register instructions. A local
attacker could use this to expose sensitive information. (CVE-2023-20593)

Zheng Zhang discovered that the device-mapper implementation in the Linux
kernel did not properly handle locking during table_clear() operations. A
local attacker could use this to cause a denial of service (kernel
deadlock). (CVE-2023-2269)

It was discovered that a use-after-free vulnerability existed in the HFS+
file system implementation in the Linux kernel. A local attacker could
possibly use this to cause a denial of service (system crash).
(CVE-2023-2985)

It was discovered that the DVB Core driver in the Linux kernel did not
properly handle locking events in certain situations. A local attacker
could use this to cause a denial of service (kernel deadlock).
(CVE-2023-31084)

It was discovered that the Quick Fair Queueing network scheduler
implementation in the Linux kernel contained an out-of-bounds write
vulnerability. A local attacker could use this to cause a denial of service
(system crash) or possibly execute arbitrary code. (CVE-2023-3611)

It was discovered that the network packet classifier with
netfilter/firewall marks implementation in the Linux kernel did not
properly handle reference counting, leading to a use-after-free
vulnerability. A local attacker could use this to cause a denial of service
(system crash) or possibly execute arbitrary code. (CVE-2023-3776)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 Ways to Expand the Cyber Talent Pool From Splash Pad to Watering Hole]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge/3-ways-to-expand-cyber-talent-pool-from-splash-pad-to-watering-hole</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge/3-ways-to-expand-cyber-talent-pool-from-splash-pad-to-watering-hole"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why — and how — "unqualified" candidates will fill the reservoir with the security workers America is thirsty for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erin Weiss Kaya, Senior Cyber Talent and Organizational Strategist, Booz Allen Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Security Bug Opens Cisco BroadWorks to Complete Takeover]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/critical-security-bug-cisco-broadworks-complete-takeover</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/critical-security-bug-cisco-broadworks-complete-takeover"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T18:32:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cyberattackers could exploit CVE-2023-20238 to carry out a variety of nefarious deeds, from data theft and code execution to phishing, fraud, and DoS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tara Seals, Managing Editor, News, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Evil Telegram' Spyware Campaign Infects 60K+ Mobile Users]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/evil-telegram-spyware-campaign-infects-60k-mobile-users</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/evil-telegram-spyware-campaign-infects-60k-mobile-users"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T18:25:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legitimate-seeming Telegram "mods" available in the official Google Play store for the encrypted messaging app signal the rise of a new enterprise threat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tara Seals, Managing Editor, News, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.K. and U.S. Sanction 11 Russia-based Trickbot Cybercrime Gang Members]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/uk-and-us-sanction-11-russia-based.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/uk-and-us-sanction-11-russia-based.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T17:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.K. and U.S. governments on Thursday sanctioned 11 individuals who are alleged to be part of the notorious Russia-based TrickBot cybercrime gang.
“Russia has long been a safe haven for cybercriminals, including the TrickBot group,” the U.S. Treasury Department said, adding it has “ties to Russian intelligence services and has targeted the U.S. Government and U.S. companies, including]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft, Google Take on Obsolete TLS Protocols]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/microsoft-google-take-on-obsolete-tls-protocols</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/microsoft-google-take-on-obsolete-tls-protocols"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T16:18:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google shortened the lifetime of Transport Layer Security (TLS) certificates, and Microsoft plans to downgrade support for older versions, giving companies more data security but also removing visibility into their own traffic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Lemos, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kenya Initiates Public Sector Digital Skills Training, No Mention of Cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/kenya-initiates-public-sector-digital-skills-training-no-mention-of-cyber</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/kenya-initiates-public-sector-digital-skills-training-no-mention-of-cyber"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T16:15:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Training will cover cloud skills and working in a paperless environment, but any mention of a cybersecurity element is conspicuously lacking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Raywood, Senior Editor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trickbot, Conti Sanctions Affect Top Cybercrime Brass]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/trickbot-conti-sanctions-affect-top-cybercrime-brass</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/trickbot-conti-sanctions-affect-top-cybercrime-brass"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T15:40:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US Treasury officials said the sanctions move is part of its effort to combat Russian state-sponsored cybercrime.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 Strategies to Defend Against Resurging Infostealers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/3-strategies-to-defend-against-resurging-infostealers</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/3-strategies-to-defend-against-resurging-infostealers"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Infostealer incidents have more than doubled recently, making it critical to bolster your defenses to mitigate this growing threat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ganesh Pai, Founder &amp; CEO, Uptycs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco ASA Zero-Day Exploited in Akira Ransomware Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34898</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/cisco-asa-zero-day-exploited-in-akira-ransomware-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T13:28:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco is warning of a zero-day vulnerability in Cisco ASA and FTD that can be exploited remotely, without authentication, in brute force attacks.
The post Cisco ASA Zero-Day Exploited in Akira Ransomware Attacks appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Arghire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Phishing Campaign Launched via Google Looker Studio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34897</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/new-phishing-campaign-launched-via-google-looker-studio/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T13:03:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check Point has observed a wave of phishing attacks launched via Google Looker Studio to steal credentials and funds from intended victims.
The post New Phishing Campaign Launched via Google Looker Studio appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Arghire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Other News: LastPass Vault Hacking, Russia Targets Ukraine Energy Facility, NXP Breach]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34896</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/in-other-news-lastpass-vault-hacking-russia-targets-ukraine-energy-facility-nxp-breach/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T12:44:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Noteworthy stories that might have slipped under the radar: LastPass vault hacking, Russia targets energy facility in Ukraine, NXP data breach.
The post In Other News: LastPass Vault Hacking, Russia Targets Ukraine Energy Facility, NXP Breach  appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SecurityWeek News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Rushes to Patch Zero-Day Flaws Exploited for Pegasus Spyware on iPhones]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/apple-rushes-to-patch-zero-day-flaws.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/apple-rushes-to-patch-zero-day-flaws.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T11:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple on Thursday released emergency security updates for iOS, iPadOS, macOS, and watchOS to address two zero-day flaws that have been exploited in the wild to deliver NSO Group's Pegasus mercenary spyware.
The issues are described as below -

CVE-2023-41061 - A validation issue in Wallet that could result in arbitrary code execution when handling a maliciously crafted attachment.
CVE-2023-41064]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco Issues Urgent Fix for Authentication Bypass Bug Affecting BroadWorks Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/cisco-issues-urgent-fix-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/cisco-issues-urgent-fix-for.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T11:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco has released security fixes to address multiple security flaws, including a critical bug, that could be exploited by a threat actor to take control of an affected system or cause a denial-of service (DoS) condition.
The most severe of the issues is CVE-2023-20238, which has the maximum CVSS severity rating of 10.0. It’s described as an authentication bypass flaw in the Cisco BroadWorks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting Your Microsoft IIS Servers Against Malware Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/protecting-your-microsoft-iis-servers.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/protecting-your-microsoft-iis-servers.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T11:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Internet Information Services (IIS) is a web server software package designed for Windows Server. Organizations commonly use Microsoft IIS servers to host websites, files, and other content on the web. Threat actors increasingly target these Internet-facing resources as low-hanging fruit for finding and exploiting vulnerabilities that facilitate access to IT environments. 
Recently, a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LLMs and Tool Use]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/09/ai-tool-use.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/09/ai-tool-use.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T11:05:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Last March, just two weeks after <a href="https://www.wired.com/story/gpt-4-openai-will-make-chatgpt-smarter-but-wont-fix-its-flaws/">GPT-4 was released</a>, researchers at Microsoft quietly <a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2303.16434" data-offer-url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2303.16434">announced</a> a plan to compile millions of APIs&#8212;tools that can do everything from ordering a pizza to solving physics equations to controlling the TV in your living room&#8212;into a compendium that would be made accessible to large language models (LLMs). This was just one milestone in the race across industry and academia to find the <a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2305.11554" data-offer-url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2305.11554">best</a> <a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2303.09014" data-offer-url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2303.09014">ways</a> <a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2304.08244" data-offer-url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2304.08244">to</a> <a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2304.09842" data-offer-url="https://arxiv.org/abs/2304.09842">teach</a> <a href="https://arxiv.org/pdf/2307.16789.pdf" data-offer-url="https://arxiv.org/pdf/2307.16789.pdf">LLMs</a> how to manipulate tools, which would supercharge the potential of AI more than any of the impressive advancements we&#8217;ve seen to date...</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emsisoft Tells Users to Update Products, Reboot Systems Due to Certificate Mishap]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34895</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/emsisoft-tells-users-to-update-products-reboot-systems-due-to-certificate-mishap/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T10:53:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Emsisoft urges its users to update anti-malware and other security products after signing them with an improperly issued digital certificate.
The post Emsisoft Tells Users to Update Products, Reboot Systems Due to Certificate Mishap appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Arghire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US, UK Sanction More Members of Trickbot Russian Cybercrime Group]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34894</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/us-uk-sanction-more-members-of-trickbot-russian-cybercrime-group/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T09:34:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US and UK have announced sanctions against 11 more alleged members of the Russian cybercrime group Trickbot. 
The post US, UK Sanction More Members of Trickbot Russian Cybercrime Group  appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eduard Kovacs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Aeronautical Organization Hacked via Zoho, Fortinet Vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34893</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/us-aeronautical-organization-hacked-via-zoho-fortinet-vulnerabilities/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T09:13:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[APTs exploited vulnerabilities in Zoho ManageEngine and Fortinet VPNs to hack an aerospace organization in early January 2023.
The post US Aeronautical Organization Hacked via Zoho, Fortinet Vulnerabilities  appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Arghire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean Hackers Exploit Zero-Day Bug to Target Cybersecurity Researchers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/north-korean-hackers-exploit-zero-day.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/north-korean-hackers-exploit-zero-day.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T08:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors associated with North Korea are continuing to target the cybersecurity community using a zero-day bug in an unspecified software over the past several weeks to infiltrate their machines.
The findings come from Google’s Threat Analysis Group (TAG), which found the adversary setting up fake accounts on social media platforms like X (formerly Twitter) and Mastodon to forge]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Warning: Nation-State Hackers Exploit Fortinet and Zoho Vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/cisa-warning-nation-state-hackers.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/cisa-warning-nation-state-hackers.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T05:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) on Thursday warned that multiple nation-state actors are exploiting security flaws in Fortinet FortiOS SSL-VPN and Zoho ManageEngine ServiceDesk Plus to gain unauthorized access and establish persistence on compromised systems.
“Nation-state advanced persistent threat (APT) actors exploited CVE-2022-47966 to gain unauthorized]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Software Supply Chain Strategies to Parry Dependency Confusion Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge-articles/software-supply-chain-strategies-to-parry-dependency-confusion-attacks</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge-articles/software-supply-chain-strategies-to-parry-dependency-confusion-attacks"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T01:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bad actors practice to deceive package managers with a tangled web of methods. Here's how to hoist them by their own petard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liad Cohen, Security Researcher &amp; Developer, OX Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thoma Bravo Makes 'Practical' Decision to Merge ForgeRock Into Ping Identity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/thoma-bravo-practical-decision-merge-forgerock-into-ping-identity</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/thoma-bravo-practical-decision-merge-forgerock-into-ping-identity"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The private equity from has invested billions of dollars in identity and access management (IAM), but now it's on Ping founder and CEO Andre Durand and his team to rationalize overlapping product lines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey Schwartz, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6355-1: GRUB2 vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6355-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6355-1"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T00:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Axtens discovered that specially crafted images could cause a
heap-based out-of-bonds write. A local attacker could possibly use
this to circumvent secure boot protections. (CVE-2021-3695)

Daniel Axtens discovered that specially crafted images could cause
out-of-bonds read and write. A local attacker could possibly use this
to circumvent secure boot protections. (CVE-2021-3696)

Daniel Axtens discovered that specially crafted images could cause
buffer underwrite which allows arbitrary data to be written to a heap.
A local attacker could possibly use this to circumvent secure
boot protections. (CVE-2021-3697)

It was discovered that GRUB2 configuration files were created with
the wrong permissions. An attacker could possibly use this to leak
encrypted passwords. (CVE-2021-3981)

Daniel Axtens discovered that specially crafted IP packets could cause
an integer underflow and write past the end of a bugger. An attacker
could possibly use this to circumvent secure boot protections.
(CVE-2022-28733)

Daniel Axtens discovered that specially crafted HTTP headers can cause
an out-of-bounds write of a NULL byte. An attacker could possibly use
this to corrupt GRUB2's internal data. (CVE-2022-28734)

Julian Andres Klode discovered that GRUB2 shim_lock allowed non-
kernel files to be loaded. A local attack could possibly use this to
circumvent secure boot protections. (CVE-2022-28735)

Chris Coulson discovered that executing chainloaders more than once
caused a use-after-free vulnerability. A local attack could possibly
use this to circumvent secure boot protections. (CVE-2022-28736)

Chris Coulson discovered that specially crafted executables could
cause shim to make out-of-bound writes. A local attack could possibly
use this to circumvent secure boot protections. (CVE-2022-28737)

Zhang Boyang discovered that specially crafted unicode sequences
could lead to an out-of-bounds write to a heap. A local attacker could
possibly use this to circumvent secure boot protections.
(CVE-2022-3775)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft ID Security Gaps That Let Threat Actor Steal Signing Key]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/microsoft-ids-security-gaps-that-let-threat-actor-steal-signing-key</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/microsoft-ids-security-gaps-that-let-threat-actor-steal-signing-key"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T22:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[China's Storm-0558 accessed user emails at some 25 enterprise organizations earlier this year using forged tokens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean Hackers Target Security Researchers — Again]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/north-korean-hackers-target-security-researchers-again</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/north-korean-hackers-target-security-researchers-again"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T21:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This time, they're creating elaborate impostor profiles and using a fresh zero-day and a fake Windows tool to lure in the suspecting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MAR-10454006.r5.v1 SUBMARINE, SKIPJACK, SEASPRAY, WHIRLPOOL, and SALTWATER Backdoors]]></title>
        <id>/node/18760</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/analysis-reports/ar23-250a-0"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T20:47:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notification
This report is provided "as is" for informational purposes only. The Department of Homeland Security (DHS) does not provide any warranties of any kind regarding any information contained herein. The DHS does not endorse any commercial product or service referenced in this bulletin or otherwise.
This document is marked TLP:CLEAR--Recipients may share this information without restriction. Sources may use TLP:CLEAR when information carries minimal or no foreseeable risk of misuse, in accordance with applicable rules and procedures for public release. Subject to standard copyright rules, TLP:CLEAR information may be shared without restriction. For more information on the Traffic Light Protocol (TLP), see http://www.cisa.gov/tlp.
Summary
Description
CISA obtained five malware sampl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Hit By 2 No-Click Zero-Days in Blastpass Exploit Chain]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/apple-hit-by-two-no-click-zero-days-in-blastpass-exploit-chain</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/apple-hit-by-two-no-click-zero-days-in-blastpass-exploit-chain"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers at Citizen Lab recommend immediately updating any iPhones and iPads to the latest OSes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Patches Actively Exploited iOS, macOS Zero-Days]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34891</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/apple-patches-actively-exploited-ios-macos-zero-days/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T20:20:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple pushes out an urgent point-update to its flagship iOS and macOS platforms to fix a pair of security defects being exploited in the wild.
The post Apple Patches Actively Exploited iOS, macOS Zero-Days appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Naraine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rigged Software and Zero-Days: North Korean APT Caught Hacking Security Researchers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34890</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/rigged-software-and-zero-days-north-korean-apt-caught-hacking-security-researchers/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T19:43:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google again catches a North Korean APT actor targeting security researchers with zero-days and rigged software tools.
The post Rigged Software and Zero-Days: North Korean APT Caught Hacking Security Researchers appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Naraine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rwanda Launches Smart-City Investment Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/rwanda-launches-smart-city-investment-program</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/rwanda-launches-smart-city-investment-program"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T19:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ambitious move by the nation also comes with cybersecurity risks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Raywood, Senior Editor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security for Multicloud and Hybrid Cloud Environments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/google-cloud-security/security-for-multicloud-and-hybrid-cloud-environments</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/google-cloud-security/security-for-multicloud-and-hybrid-cloud-environments"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In multicloud environments, security challenges are most common at the connecting points between different clouds. Internal cloud security skill sets and cloud-native security tools are also key.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anton Chuvakin, Security Advisor at Office of the CISO, Google Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFL Security Chief: Generative AI Threats a Concern as New Season Kicks Off]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/generative-ai-threats-a-concern-for-nfl-security-chief-as-new-season-kicks-off</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/generative-ai-threats-a-concern-for-nfl-security-chief-as-new-season-kicks-off"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deepfake videos and audio of NFL players and phishing communications via ChatGPT-like tools are a worry, the NFL's CISO says.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weaponized Windows Installers Target Graphic Designers in Crypto Heist]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/weaponized-windows-installers-target-graphic-designers-in-crypto-heist</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/weaponized-windows-installers-target-graphic-designers-in-crypto-heist"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T18:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attackers use legitimate Windows installer to hide malicious scripts that install a backdoor and miners that leverage victims' graphics processing power.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Montalbano, Contributor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How New SEC Rules Can Benefit Cybersecurity Teams]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/risk/how-new-sec-rules-can-benefit-cybersecurity-teams</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/risk/how-new-sec-rules-can-benefit-cybersecurity-teams"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Securities and Exchange Commission rules elevate cybersecurity to a critical strategic concern and compel businesses to prioritize cyber resilience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Haywood Marsh, General Manager, NAVEX IRM &amp; NetClaim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wealthy Russian With Kremlin Ties Gets 9 Years in Prison for Hacking and Insider Trading Scheme]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34887</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/wealthy-russian-with-kremlin-ties-gets-9-years-in-prison-for-hacking-and-insider-trading-scheme/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T16:23:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vladislav Klyushin was sentenced to nine years in prison for his role in a nearly $100M stock market cheating scheme that relied on information stolen by hacking.
The post Wealthy Russian With Kremlin Ties Gets 9 Years in Prison for Hacking and Insider Trading Scheme appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Associated Press</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6354-1: Python vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6354-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6354-1"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T16:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was discovered that Python did not properly handle XML entity
declarations in plist files. An attacker could possibly use this
vulnerability to perform an XML External Entity (XXE) injection,
resulting in a denial of service or information disclosure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Team8 Foundry Method for Selecting Investable Startups]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34883</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/the-team8-foundry-method-for-selecting-investable-startups/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T15:39:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Team8, a VC organization with added sauce, queried more than 130 CISOs from its own ‘CISO Village’ to discover the concerns of existing cybersecurity practitioners, and the technologies they are seeking for the future.
The post The Team8 Foundry Method for Selecting Investable Startups appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Townsend</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mac Users Beware: Malvertising Campaign Spreads Atomic Stealer macOS Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/mac-users-beware-malvertising-campaign.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/mac-users-beware-malvertising-campaign.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T15:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new malvertising campaign has been observed distributing an updated version of a macOS stealer malware called Atomic Stealer (or AMOS), indicating that it’s being actively maintained by its author.
An off-the-shelf Golang malware available for $1,000 per month, Atomic Stealer first came to light in April 2023. Shortly after that, new variants with an expanded set of information-gathering]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peril vs. Promise: Companies, Developers Worry Over Generative AI Risk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/peril-vs-promise-companies-developers-worry-over-generative-ai-risks</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/peril-vs-promise-companies-developers-worry-over-generative-ai-risks"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T14:45:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Executives and developers believe AI can help businesses thrive, but worry that reliance on generative AI brings significant risks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Lemos, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[See Tickets Alerts 300,000 Customers After Another Web Skimmer Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34882</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/see-tickets-alerts-300000-customers-after-another-web-skimmer-attack/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T14:31:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[See Tickets is informing 300,000 individuals that their payment card information was stolen in a new web skimmer attack.
The post See Tickets Alerts 300,000 Customers After Another Web Skimmer Attack appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Arghire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does Generative AI Comply With Asimov's 3 Laws of Robotics?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/does-generative-ai-comply-asimov-3-laws-of-robotics-</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/does-generative-ai-comply-asimov-3-laws-of-robotics-"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Putting the top 10 generative AI tools to the ethical test reveals more about humanity than artificial intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Lee, Technical Lead of Security Research &amp; EMEA Lead, Cisco Talos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Releases Guidance on Adopting DDoS Mitigations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34881</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/cisa-releases-guidance-on-adopting-ddos-mitigations/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T13:42:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CISA has released new guidance to help federal agencies decide upon and prioritize DDoS mitigations based on mission and reputational impact.
The post CISA Releases Guidance on Adopting DDoS Mitigations appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Arghire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Atomic macOS Stealer’ Malware Delivered via Malvertising Campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34880</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/atomic-macos-stealer-malware-delivered-via-malvertising-campaign/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T13:27:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A malware named Atomic macOS Stealer (AMOS) has been delivered to users via a malvertising campaign. 
The post ‘Atomic macOS Stealer’ Malware Delivered via Malvertising Campaign appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eduard Kovacs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6353-1: PLIB vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6353-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6353-1"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T13:24:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wooseok Kang discovered that PLIB did not properly manage memory under
certain circumstances. If a user were tricked into opening a specially
crafted TGA file, an attacker could possibly use this issue to cause
applications using PLIB to crash, resulting in a denial of service, or
possibly execute arbitrary code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco Patches Critical Vulnerability in BroadWorks Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34879</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/cisco-patches-critical-vulnerability-in-broadworks-platform/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T12:36:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco has released patches for CVE-2023-20238, a critical authentication bypass vulnerability in the BroadWorks Application Delivery Platform.
The post Cisco Patches Critical Vulnerability in BroadWorks Platform appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Arghire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tenable to Acquire Cloud Security Firm Ermetic for $240 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34878</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/tenable-to-acquire-cloud-security-firm-ermetic-for-240-million/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T12:17:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tenable is set to acquire cloud security firm Ermetic for $240 million as it looks to expand the capabilities of its exposure management platform.
The post Tenable to Acquire Cloud Security Firm Ermetic for $240 Million appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eduard Kovacs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco Releases Security Advisories for Multiple Products]]></title>
        <id>/node/18749</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/09/07/cisco-releases-security-advisories-multiple-products"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco has released security advisories to address vulnerabilities affecting multiple Cisco products. A cyber threat actor can exploit some of these vulnerabilities to take control of an affected system or cause a denial-of service condition. 
CISA encourages users and administrators to review the following advisories and apply the necessary updates.
BroadWorks and BroadWorks Xtended
Identity Services Engine RADIUS]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA, FBI, and CNMF Release Advisory on Multiple Nation-State Threat Actors Exploit CVE-2022-47966 and CVE-2022-42475]]></title>
        <id>/node/18750</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/09/07/cisa-fbi-and-cnmf-release-advisory-multiple-nation-state-threat-actors-exploit-cve-2022-47966-and"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, CISA, Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI), and U.S. Cyber Command’s Cyber National Mission Force (CNMF) published a joint Cybersecurity Advisory (CSA), Multiple Nation-State Threat Actors Exploit CVE-2022-47966 and CVE-2022-42475. This CSA provides information on an incident at an Aeronautical Sector organization, with malicious activity occurring as early as January 2023. 
CISA, FBI, and CNMF confirmed that nation-state advanced persistent threat (APT) actors exploited CVE-2022-47966 to gain unauthorized access to a public-facing application (Zoho ManageEngine ServiceDesk Plus), establish persistence, and move laterally through the network. This vulnerability allows for remote code execution on the ManageEngine application. Additional APT actors were also observed exploiting CVE-2022-42475 to establish presence on the organization’s firewall device.
The authoring agencies urge organizations to review this CSA and implement the recommended mitigations, which align with CISA’s Cross-Sector Cybersecurity Performance Goals (CPGs)—developed by CISA and the National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST)—as well as NSA-recommended best practices for securing infrastructure.
All organizations should report suspicious or criminal activity related to information found in this joint Cybersecurity Advisory by contacting your local FBI field office and CISA’s 24/7 Operations Center at report@cisa.gov or (888) 282-0870.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Releases Four Industrial Control Systems Advisories]]></title>
        <id>/node/18748</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/09/07/cisa-releases-four-industrial-control-systems-advisories"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CISA released four Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisories on September 7, 2023. These advisories provide timely information about current security issues, vulnerabilities, and exploits surrounding ICS.
ICSA-23-250-01 Dover Fueling Solutions MAGLINK LX Console
ICSA-23-250-02 Phoenix Contact TC ROUTER and TC CLOUD CLIENT
ICSA-23-250-03 Socomec MOD3GP-SY-120K
ICSA-23-157-01 Delta Electronics CNCSoft-B DOPSoft (Update)
CISA encourages users and administrators to review the newly released ICS advisories for technical details and mitigations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The State of the Virtual CISO Report: MSP/MSSP Security Strategies for 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/the-state-of-virtual-ciso-report.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/the-state-of-virtual-ciso-report.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T11:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By the end of 2024, the number of MSPs and MSSPs offering vCISO services is expected to grow by almost 5 fold, as can be seen in figure 1. This incredible surge reflects the growing business demand for specialized cybersecurity expertise and the lucrative opportunities for MSPs and MSSPs in vCISO services.
Figure 1: Timeline for offering vCISO services
The State of the Virtual CISO Survey Report]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hacker Tool to Get Personal Data from Credit Bureaus]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/09/the-hacker-tool-to-get-personal-data-from-credit-bureaus.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/09/the-hacker-tool-to-get-personal-data-from-credit-bureaus.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T11:09:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The new site 404 Media has a <a href="https://www.404media.co/the-secret-weapon-hackers-can-use-to-dox-nearly-anyone-in-america-for-15-tlo-usinfosearch-transunion/">good article</a> on how hackers are cheaply getting personal information from credit bureaus:</p>
<blockquote><p>This is the result of a secret weapon criminals are selling access to online that appears to tap into an especially powerful set of data: the target&#8217;s credit header. This is personal information that the credit bureaus Experian, Equifax, and TransUnion have on most adults in America via their credit cards. Through a complex web of agreements and purchases, that data trickles down from the credit bureaus to other companies who offer it to debt collectors, insurance companies, and law enforcement...</p></blockquote>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alert: Apache Superset Vulnerabilities Expose Servers to Remote Code Execution Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/alert-apache-superset-vulnerabilities.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/alert-apache-superset-vulnerabilities.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T11:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Patches have been released to address two new security vulnerabilities in Apache Superset that could be exploited by an attacker to gain remote code execution on affected systems.
The update (version 2.1.1) plugs CVE-2023-39265 and CVE-2023-37941, which make it possible to conduct nefarious actions once a bad actor is able to gain control of Superset’s metadata database.
Outside of these]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mirai Botnet Variant 'Pandora' Hijacks Android TVs for Cyberattacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/mirai-botnet-variant-pandora-hijacks.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/mirai-botnet-variant-pandora-hijacks.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T09:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Mirai botnet variant called Pandora has been observed infiltrating inexpensive Android-based TV sets and TV boxes and using them as part of a botnet to perform distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attacks.
Doctor Web said the compromises are likely to occur either during malicious firmware updates or when applications for viewing pirated video content are installed.
"It is likely that this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Outlook Hack: Microsoft Reveals How a Crash Dump Led to a Major Security Breach]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/outlook-breach-microsoft-reveals-how.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/outlook-breach-microsoft-reveals-how.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T07:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft on Wednesday revealed that a China-based threat actor known as Storm-0558 acquired the inactive consumer signing key to forge tokens and access Outlook by compromising an engineer’s corporate account.
This enabled the adversary to access a debugging environment that contained information pertaining to a crash of the consumer signing system and steal the key. The system crash took place]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6352-1: Apache Shiro vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6352-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6352-1"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T01:36:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was discovered that Apache Shiro incorrectly handled certain HTTP
requests. A remote attacker could possibly use this issue to bypass
security restrictions. (CVE-2020-13933, CVE-2020-17510)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CybeReady Provides Cybersecurity Awareness Month Kits As CISOs Defend Against AI Driven Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/cybeready-provides-cybersecurity-awareness-month-kits-as-cisos-defend-against-ai-driven-attacks</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/cybeready-provides-cybersecurity-awareness-month-kits-as-cisos-defend-against-ai-driven-attacks"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T00:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coding Tips to Sidestep JavaScript Vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/coding-tips-to-sidestep-javascript-vulnerabilities</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/coding-tips-to-sidestep-javascript-vulnerabilities"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T23:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This Tech Tip focuses on best security practices to write secure JavaScript code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aviad Mizrachi, Co-Founder and CTO, Frontegg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity Builds Trust in Critical Infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge-articles/cybersecurity-builds-trust-in-critical-infrastructure</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge-articles/cybersecurity-builds-trust-in-critical-infrastructure"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T23:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Improving an energy company's resistance to cyberattack does more than protect vital resources — it enhances trust from customers and investors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leo Simonovich, VP &amp; Global Head, Industrial Cyber and Digital Security, Siemens Energy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MAR-10430311-1.v1 Multiple Nation-State Threat Actors Exploit CVE-2022-47966 and CVE-2022-42475]]></title>
        <id>/node/18744</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/analysis-reports/ar23-250a"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T23:28:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notification
This report is provided "as is" for informational purposes only. The Department of Homeland Security (DHS) does not provide any warranties of any kind regarding any information contained herein. The DHS does not endorse any commercial product or service referenced in this bulletin or otherwise.
This document is marked TLP:CLEAR--Recipients may share this information without restriction. Sources may use TLP:CLEAR when information carries minimal or no foreseeable risk of misuse, in accordance with applicable rules and procedures for public release. Subject to standard copyright rules, TLP:CLEAR information may be shared without restriction. For more information on the Traffic Light Protocol (TLP), see http://www.cisa.gov/tlp.
Summary
Description
CISA received 4 files for analys…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IBM Addresses Data Incident for Janssen CarePath Database]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/ibm-addresses-data-incident-for-janssen-carepath-database</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/ibm-addresses-data-incident-for-janssen-carepath-database"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T22:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IBM Expands Cloud Security and Compliance Center]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/ibm-expands-cloud-security-and-compliance-center</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/ibm-expands-cloud-security-and-compliance-center"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T22:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[W3LL Gang Compromises Thousands of Microsoft 365 Accounts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/w3ll-gang-compromises-thousands-of-microsoft-365-accounts</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/w3ll-gang-compromises-thousands-of-microsoft-365-accounts"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T22:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A secretive phishing cabal boasts a sophisticated affiliate network and a modular, custom toolset that's claiming victims on three continents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tara Seals, Managing Editor, News, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6351-1: Linux kernel (GKE) vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6351-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6351-1"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T21:41:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was discovered that the NTFS file system implementation in the Linux
kernel did not properly validate MFT flags in certain situations. An
attacker could use this to construct a malicious NTFS image that, when
mounted and operated on, could cause a denial of service (system crash).
(CVE-2022-48425)

Zi Fan Tan discovered that the binder IPC implementation in the Linux
kernel contained a use-after-free vulnerability. A local attacker could use
this to cause a denial of service (system crash) or possibly execute
arbitrary code. (CVE-2023-21255)

It was discovered that a race condition existed in the f2fs file system in
the Linux kernel, leading to a null pointer dereference vulnerability. An
attacker could use this to construct a malicious f2fs image that, when
mounted and operated on, could cause a denial of service (system crash).
(CVE-2023-2898)

It was discovered that the DVB Core driver in the Linux kernel did not
properly handle locking events in certain situations. A local attacker
could use this to cause a denial of service (kernel deadlock).
(CVE-2023-31084)

Yang Lan discovered that the GFS2 file system implementation in the Linux
kernel could attempt to dereference a null pointer in some situations. An
attacker could use this to construct a malicious GFS2 image that, when
mounted and operated on, could cause a denial of service (system crash).
(CVE-2023-3212)

It was discovered that the KSMBD implementation in the Linux kernel did not
properly validate buffer sizes in certain operations, leading to an out-of-
bounds read vulnerability. A remote attacker could use this to cause a
denial of service (system crash) or possibly expose sensitive information.
(CVE-2023-38426, CVE-2023-38428)

It was discovered that the KSMBD implementation in the Linux kernel did not
properly calculate the size of certain buffers. A remote attacker could use
this to cause a denial of service (system crash) or possibly execute
arbitrary code. (CVE-2023-38429)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crash Dump Error: How a Chinese Espionage Group Exploited Microsoft’s Mistakes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34873</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/crash-dump-error-how-a-chinese-espionage-group-exploited-microsofts-errors/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T19:45:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft reveals how a crash dump from 2021 inadvertently exposed a key that Chinese cyberspies later leveraged to hack US government emails.
The post Crash Dump Error: How a Chinese Espionage Group Exploited Microsoft’s Mistakes appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Naraine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AtlasVPN Linux Zero-Day Disconnects Users, Reveals IP Addresses]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/atlasvpn-linux-zero-day-disconnects-users-reveals-ip-addresses</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/atlasvpn-linux-zero-day-disconnects-users-reveals-ip-addresses"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All it takes is a simple copy-paste to undo a VPN service used by millions worldwide.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cash-Strapped IronNet Faces Bankruptcy Options]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34872</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/cash-strapped-ironnet-faces-bankruptcy-options/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T18:20:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It appears to be the end of the road for IronNet, the once-promising network security play founded by former NSA director General Keith Alexander.
The post Cash-Strapped IronNet Faces Bankruptcy Options appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Naraine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6350-1: Linux kernel vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6350-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6350-1"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T17:57:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was discovered that the NTFS file system implementation in the Linux
kernel did not properly validate MFT flags in certain situations. An
attacker could use this to construct a malicious NTFS image that, when
mounted and operated on, could cause a denial of service (system crash).
(CVE-2022-48425)

Zi Fan Tan discovered that the binder IPC implementation in the Linux
kernel contained a use-after-free vulnerability. A local attacker could use
this to cause a denial of service (system crash) or possibly execute
arbitrary code. (CVE-2023-21255)

It was discovered that a race condition existed in the f2fs file system in
the Linux kernel, leading to a null pointer dereference vulnerability. An
attacker could use this to construct a malicious f2fs image that, when
mounted and operated on, could cause a denial of service (system crash).
(CVE-2023-2898)

It was discovered that the DVB Core driver in the Linux kernel did not
properly handle locking events in certain situations. A local attacker
could use this to cause a denial of service (kernel deadlock).
(CVE-2023-31084)

Yang Lan discovered that the GFS2 file system implementation in the Linux
kernel could attempt to dereference a null pointer in some situations. An
attacker could use this to construct a malicious GFS2 image that, when
mounted and operated on, could cause a denial of service (system crash).
(CVE-2023-3212)

It was discovered that the KSMBD implementation in the Linux kernel did not
properly validate buffer sizes in certain operations, leading to an out-of-
bounds read vulnerability. A remote attacker could use this to cause a
denial of service (system crash) or possibly expose sensitive information.
(CVE-2023-38426, CVE-2023-38428)

It was discovered that the KSMBD implementation in the Linux kernel did not
properly calculate the size of certain buffers. A remote attacker could use
this to cause a denial of service (system crash) or possibly execute
arbitrary code. (CVE-2023-38429)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MinIO Cyberattack Showcases Fresh Corporate Cloud Vector]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/minio-attack-corporate-cloud-attack-vector</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/minio-attack-corporate-cloud-attack-vector"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T17:54:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The open source object storage service was the target of a never-before-seen attack on corporate cloud services, which researchers said should put DevOps in particular on notice.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia's 'Fancy Bear' APT Targets Ukrainian Energy Facility]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/russia-fancy-bear-apt-ukrainian-energy-facility</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/russia-fancy-bear-apt-ukrainian-energy-facility"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T17:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The group, best known for 2016 US election interference and other attacks on Ukraine, used phishing emails offering pictures of women to lure its victim into opening a malicious attachment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple Nation-State Threat Actors Exploit CVE-2022-47966 and CVE-2022-42475]]></title>
        <id>/node/18743</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/cybersecurity-advisories/aa23-250a"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T17:03:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUMMARY
The Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA), Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI), and Cyber National Mission Force (CNMF) identified the presence of indicators of compromise (IOCs) at an Aeronautical Sector organization as early as January 2023. Analysts confirmed that nation-state advanced persistent threat (APT) actors exploited CVE-2022-47966 to gain unauthorized access to a public-facing application (Zoho ManageEngine ServiceDesk Plus), establish persistence, and move laterally through the network. This vulnerability allows for remote code execution on the ManageEngine application. Additional APT actors were also observed exploiting CVE-2022-42475 to establish presence on the organization’s firewall device.
CISA and co-sealers are releasing this joint Cybersec…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6349-1: Linux kernel (Azure) vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6349-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6349-1"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T16:59:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ruihan Li discovered that the bluetooth subsystem in the Linux kernel did
not properly perform permissions checks when handling HCI sockets. A
physically proximate attacker could use this to cause a denial of service
(bluetooth communication). (CVE-2023-2002)

Zi Fan Tan discovered that the binder IPC implementation in the Linux
kernel contained a use-after-free vulnerability. A local attacker could use
this to cause a denial of service (system crash) or possibly execute
arbitrary code. (CVE-2023-21255)

Juan Jose Lopez Jaimez, Meador Inge, Simon Scannell, and Nenad Stojanovski
discovered that the BPF verifier in the Linux kernel did not properly mark
registers for precision tracking in certain situations, leading to an out-
of-bounds access vulnerability. A local attacker could use this t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Investors Betting Big on Upwind for CNAPP Tech]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34871</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/investors-betting-big-on-upwind-for-cnapp-tech/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T16:30:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Upwind raises a total of $80 million in just 10 months as investors pour cash into startups in the cloud and data security categories.
The post Investors Betting Big on Upwind for CNAPP Tech appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Naraine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google's Souped-up Chrome Store Review Process Foiled by Data-Stealer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/google-chrome-store-review-process-data-stealer</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/google-chrome-store-review-process-data-stealer"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have discovered that despite Google's adoption of the Manifest V3 security standard to protect against malicious plug-ins, attackers can still get bad extensions past its review process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Montalbano, Contributor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6348-1: Linux kernel vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6348-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6348-1"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T16:15:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Moghimi discovered that some Intel(R) Processors did not properly
clear microarchitectural state after speculative execution of various
instructions. A local unprivileged user could use this to obtain to
sensitive information. (CVE-2022-40982)

Tavis Ormandy discovered that some AMD processors did not properly handle
speculative execution of certain vector register instructions. A local
attacker could use this to expose sensitive information. (CVE-2023-20593)

Ye Zhang and Nicolas Wu discovered that the io_uring subsystem in the Linux
kernel did not properly handle locking for rings with IOPOLL, leading to a
double-free vulnerability. A local attacker could use this to cause a
denial of service (system crash) or possibly execute arbitrary code.
(CVE-2023-21400)

It was discovered th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6347-1: Linux kernel (Azure CVM) vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6347-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6347-1"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T15:43:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[William Zhao discovered that the Traffic Control (TC) subsystem in the
Linux kernel did not properly handle network packet retransmission in
certain situations. A local attacker could use this to cause a denial of
service (kernel deadlock). (CVE-2022-4269)

It was discovered that the NTFS file system implementation in the Linux
kernel did not properly check buffer indexes in certain situations, leading
to an out-of-bounds read vulnerability. A local attacker could possibly use
this to expose sensitive information (kernel memory). (CVE-2022-48502)

Seth Jenkins discovered that the Linux kernel did not properly perform
address randomization for a per-cpu memory management structure. A local
attacker could use this to expose sensitive information (kernel memory) or
in conjunction with another…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webinar Tomorrow: Unpacking the Secure Supply Chain Consumption Framework (S2C2F)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34867</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/webinar-tomorrow-unpacking-the-secure-supply-chain-consumption-framework-s2c2f/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T15:17:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join Microsoft and Finite State for a webinar that will introduce a new strategy for securing the software supply chain. 
The post Webinar Tomorrow: Unpacking the Secure Supply Chain Consumption Framework (S2C2F) appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SecurityWeek News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thousands of Popular Websites Leaking Secrets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34866</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/researchers-find-thousands-of-popular-websites-leaking-secrets/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T14:49:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Truffle Security has discovered thousands of popular websites leaking their secrets, including .git directories and AWS and GitHub keys.
The post Thousands of Popular Websites Leaking Secrets appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Arghire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dozens of Unpatched Flaws Expose Security Cameras Made by Defunct Company Zavio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34864</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/dozens-of-unpatched-flaws-expose-security-cameras-made-by-defunct-company-zavio/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T14:40:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dozens of vulnerabilities have been found in widely used security cameras made by defunct Chinese company Zavio. 
The post Dozens of Unpatched Flaws Expose Security Cameras Made by Defunct Company Zavio appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eduard Kovacs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6345-1: SoX vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6345-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6345-1"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T14:12:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was discovered that SoX incorrectly handled certain inputs. If a
user or an automated system were tricked into opening a specially crafted
input file, an attacker could possibly use this issue to cause a denial
of service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6346-1: Linux kernel (Raspberry Pi) vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6346-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6346-1"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T14:11:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Moghimi discovered that some Intel(R) Processors did not properly
clear microarchitectural state after speculative execution of various
instructions. A local unprivileged user could use this to obtain to
sensitive information. (CVE-2022-40982)

Tavis Ormandy discovered that some AMD processors did not properly handle
speculative execution of certain vector register instructions. A local
attacker could use this to expose sensitive information. (CVE-2023-20593)

It was discovered that the universal 32bit network packet classifier
implementation in the Linux kernel did not properly perform reference
counting in some situations, leading to a use-after-free vulnerability. A
local attacker could use this to cause a denial of service (system crash)
or possibly execute arbitrary code. (CVE-2023-3609)

It was discovered that the Quick Fair Queueing network scheduler
implementation in the Linux kernel contained an out-of-bounds write
vulnerability. A local attacker could use this to cause a denial of service
(system crash) or possibly execute arbitrary code. (CVE-2023-3611)

It was discovered that the network packet classifier with
netfilter/firewall marks implementation in the Linux kernel did not
properly handle reference counting, leading to a use-after-free
vulnerability. A local attacker could use this to cause a denial of service
(system crash) or possibly execute arbitrary code. (CVE-2023-3776)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Password-Stealing Chrome Extension Demonstrates New Vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34863</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/password-stealing-chrome-extension-demonstrates-new-vulnerabilities/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T14:07:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Academic researchers design a Chrome extension to steal passwords from input fields and publish it to the Chrome webstore.
The post Password-Stealing Chrome Extension Demonstrates New Vulnerabilities appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Arghire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zero-Day Alert: Latest Android Patch Update Includes Fix for Newly Actively Exploited Flaw]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/zero-day-alert-latest-android-patch.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/zero-day-alert-latest-android-patch.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T14:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has rolled out monthly security patches for Android to address a number of flaws, including a zero-day bug that it said may have been exploited in the wild.
Tracked as CVE-2023-35674, the high-severity vulnerability is described as a case of privilege escalation impacting the Android Framework.
“There are indications that CVE-2023-35674 may be under limited, targeted exploitation,” the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Securing Your Legacy: Identities, Data, and Processes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/securing-your-legacy-identities-data-and-processes</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/securing-your-legacy-identities-data-and-processes"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legacy systems of all kinds pose significant cybersecurity risks. Here's how to mitigate them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dirk Schrader, Resident CISO (EMEA) &amp; VP of Security Research, Netwrix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alert: Phishing Campaigns Deliver New SideTwist Backdoor and Agent Tesla Variant]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/alert-phishing-campaigns-deliver-new.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/alert-phishing-campaigns-deliver-new.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T13:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Iranian threat actor tracked as APT34 has been linked to a new phishing attack that leads to the deployment of a variant of a backdoor called SideTwist.
“APT34 has a high level of attack technology, can design different intrusion methods for different types of targets, and has supply chain attack capability,” NSFOCUS Security Labs said in a report published last week.
APT34, also known by]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overcoming Open Source Vulnerabilities in the Software Supply Chain]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/microsoft/overcoming-open-source-vulnerabilities-in-the-software-supply-chain-</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/microsoft/overcoming-open-source-vulnerabilities-in-the-software-supply-chain-"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By securing access to code and running scans against all code changes, developers can better prevent — and detect — potential risks and vulnerabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Microsoft Security, Microsoft</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6344-1: Linux kernel (Azure) vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6344-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6344-1"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T12:57:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zi Fan Tan discovered that the binder IPC implementation in the Linux
kernel contained a use-after-free vulnerability. A local attacker could use
this to cause a denial of service (system crash) or possibly execute
arbitrary code. (CVE-2023-21255)

It was discovered that a race condition existed in the f2fs file system in
the Linux kernel, leading to a null pointer dereference vulnerability. An
attacker could use this to construct a malicious f2fs image that, when
mounted and operated on, could cause a denial of service (system crash).
(CVE-2023-2898)

It was discovered that the DVB Core driver in the Linux kernel did not
properly handle locking events in certain situations. A local attacker
could use this to cause a denial of service (kernel deadlock).
(CVE-2023-31084)

Quentin Minster di…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[25 Major Car Brands Get Failing Marks From Mozilla for Security and Privacy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34861</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/25-major-car-brands-get-failing-marks-from-mozilla-for-security-and-privacy/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T12:43:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla has analyzed the privacy and security of 25 major car brands and found that they collect a lot of data and can share it or sell it to third parties. 
The post 25 Major Car Brands Get Failing Marks From Mozilla for Security and Privacy  appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eduard Kovacs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6343-1: Linux kernel (OEM) vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6343-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6343-1"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T12:32:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was discovered that the IPv6 implementation in the Linux kernel
contained a high rate of hash collisions in connection lookup table. A
remote attacker could use this to cause a denial of service (excessive CPU
consumption). (CVE-2023-1206)

Ross Lagerwall discovered that the Xen netback backend driver in the Linux
kernel did not properly handle certain unusual packets from a
paravirtualized network frontend, leading to a buffer overflow. An attacker
in a guest VM could use this to cause a denial of service (host system
crash) or possibly execute arbitrary code. (CVE-2023-34319)

It was discovered that the bluetooth subsystem in the Linux kernel did not
properly handle L2CAP socket release, leading to a use-after-free
vulnerability. A local attacker could use this to cause a denial of service
(system crash) or possibly execute arbitrary code. (CVE-2023-40283)

It was discovered that some network classifier implementations in the Linux
kernel contained use-after-free vulnerabilities. A local attacker could use
this to cause a denial of service (system crash) or possibly execute
arbitrary code. (CVE-2023-4128)

Andy Nguyen discovered that the KVM implementation for AMD processors in
the Linux kernel with Secure Encrypted Virtualization (SEV) contained a
race condition when accessing the GHCB page. A local attacker in a SEV
guest VM could possibly use this to cause a denial of service (host system
crash). (CVE-2023-4155)

It was discovered that the TUN/TAP driver in the Linux kernel did not
properly initialize socket data. A local attacker could use this to cause a
denial of service (system crash). (CVE-2023-4194)

Maxim Suhanov discovered that the exFAT file system implementation in the
Linux kernel did not properly check a file name length, leading to an out-
of-bounds write vulnerability. An attacker could use this to construct a
malicious exFAT image that, when mounted and operated on, could cause a
denial of service (system crash) or possibly execute arbitrary code.
(CVE-2023-4273)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android Zero-Day Patched With September 2023 Security Updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34860</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/android-zero-day-patched-with-september-2023-security-updates/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T12:01:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Android’s September 2023 security update resolves a high-severity elevation of privilege vulnerability exploited in malicious attacks.
The post Android Zero-Day Patched With September 2023 Security Updates  appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Arghire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Releases Capacity Enhancement Guide to Strengthen Agency Resilience to DDoS Attack]]></title>
        <id>/node/18739</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/09/06/cisa-releases-capacity-enhancement-guide-strengthen-agency-resilience-ddos-attack"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CISA has released actionable guidance for Federal Civilian Executive Branch (FCEB) agencies to help them evaluate and mitigate the risk of volumetric distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attacks against their websites and related web services. The Capacity Enhancement Guide: Volumetric DDoS Against Web Services Technical Guidance:  
Helps agencies prioritize DDoS mitigations based on mission and reputational impact. 
Describes DDoS mitigation services so agencies can make risk-informed tradeoff decisions on how to use available resources most effectively. 
CISA encourages FCEB agencies to review the guidance and apply the recommendations. Visit Capacity Enhancement Guides for Federal Agencies for more ways to reduce cybersecurity risk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Releases Update to Threat Actors Exploiting Citrix CVE-2023-3519 to Implant Webshells]]></title>
        <id>/node/18742</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/09/06/cisa-releases-update-threat-actors-exploiting-citrix-cve-2023-3519-implant-webshells"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has released an update to a previously published Cybersecurity Advisory (CSA), Threat Actors Exploiting Citrix CVE-2023-3519 to Implant Webshells. The CSA—originally released to warn network defenders of critical infrastructure organizations about threat actors exploiting CVE-2023-3519, an unauthenticated remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability affecting NetScaler (formerly Citrix) Application Delivery Controller (ADC) and NetScaler Gateway—contains victim information gathered in August 2023. Since July 2023, the Joint Cyber Defense Collaborative (JCDC) has facilitated continuous, real-time threat information sharing with and between partners on post-exploitation activity of CVE-2023-3519. JCDC consolidated and shared detection methods, threat actor tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs), and indicators of compromise (IOCs) received from industry and international partners. The updated CSA contains new TTPs as well as IOCs received from some of these partners and an additional victim.
CISA strongly urges all critical infrastructure organizations to review the advisory and follow the mitigation recommendations—such as prioritizing patching known exploited vulnerabilities like Citrix CVE-2023-3519.
To report incidents and anomalous activity, please contact CISA, either through the agency’s Incident Reporting System or the 24/7 Operations Center at report@cisa.gov or (888) 282-0870.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Adds One Known Vulnerability to Catalog]]></title>
        <id>/node/18733</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/09/06/cisa-adds-one-known-vulnerability-catalog"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CISA has added one new vulnerability to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog, based on evidence of active exploitation.
CVE-2023-33246 Apache RocketMQ Command Execution Vulnerability 
These types of vulnerabilities are frequent attack vectors for malicious cyber actors and pose significant risks to the federal enterprise. Note: To view other newly added vulnerabilities in the catalog, click on the arrow in the "Date Added to Catalog" column—which will sort by descending dates.
Binding Operational Directive (BOD) 22-01: Reducing the Significant Risk of Known Exploited Vulnerabilities established the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog as a living list of known Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVEs) that carry significant risk to the federal enterprise. BOD 22-01 requires Federal Civilian Executive Branch (FCEB) agencies to remediate identified vulnerabilities by the due date to protect FCEB networks against active threats. See the BOD 22-01 Fact Sheet for more information.
Although BOD 22-01 only applies to FCEB agencies, CISA strongly urges all organizations to reduce their exposure to cyberattacks by prioritizing timely remediation of Catalog vulnerabilities as part of their vulnerability management practice. CISA will continue to add vulnerabilities to the catalog that meet the specified criteria.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerability Summary for the Week of August 28, 2023]]></title>
        <id>/node/18740</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/bulletins/sb23-249"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T11:29:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[High Vulnerabilities

Primary
Description
Published
CVSS Score
Source & Patch Info

earcms -- ear_app
An issue found in Earcms Ear App v.20181124 allows a remote cyber threat actor to execute arbitrary code via the uload/index-uplog.php.
2023-08-29
9.8
CVE-2020-18912
MISC
MISC

tripspark -- veo_transportation_novusedu
TripSpark VEO Transportation-2.2.x-XP_BB-20201123-184084 NovusEDU-2.2.x-XP_BB-20201123-184084 allows unsafe data inputs in POST body parameters from end users without sanitizing using server-side logic. It was possible to inject custom SQL commands into the "Student Busing Information" search queries.
2023-08-29
9.8
CVE-2021-3262
MISC
MISC
MISC

motorola_mobility -- mbts_site_controller_firmware
Motorola MBTS Site Controller accepts hard-coded backdoor password. The Motorola …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three CISOs Share How to Run an Effective SOC]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/three-cisos-share-how-to-run-effective.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/three-cisos-share-how-to-run-effective.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T11:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The role of the CISO keeps taking center stage as a business enabler: CISOs need to navigate the complex landscape of digital threats while fostering innovation and ensuring business continuity. Three CISOs; Troy Wilkinson, CISO at IPG; Rob Geurtsen, former Deputy CISO at Nike; and Tammy Moskites, Founder of CyAlliance and former CISO at companies like Time Warner and Home Depot – shared their]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Startup Loses Encryption Key for Electronic Wallet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/09/cryptocurrency-startup-loses-encryption-key-for-electronic-wallet.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/09/cryptocurrency-startup-loses-encryption-key-for-electronic-wallet.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T11:05:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The cryptocurrency fintech startup Prime Trust <a href="https://www.404media.co/crypto-startup-prime-trust-files-for-bankruptcy-after-losing-password-to-38-9-million-crypto-wallet/">lost</a> the encryption key to its hardware wallet&#8212;and the recovery key&#8212;and therefore $38.9 million. It is now in bankruptcy.</p>
<p>I can&#8217;t understand why anyone thinks these technologies are a good idea.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacker Conversations: Alex Ionescu]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34853</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/hacker-conversations-alex-ionescu/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SecurityWeek talks to Alex Ionescu, a world-renowned cybersecurity expert who has combined a career as a business executive with that of a security researcher. 
The post Hacker Conversations: Alex Ionescu appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Townsend</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[9 Alarming Vulnerabilities Uncovered in SEL's Power Management Products]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/9-alarming-vulnerabilities-uncovered-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/9-alarming-vulnerabilities-uncovered-in.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T10:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nine security flaws have been disclosed in electric power management products made by Schweitzer Engineering Laboratories (SEL).
“The most severe of those nine vulnerabilities would allow a threat actor to facilitate remote code execution (RCE) on an engineering workstation,” Nozomi Networks said in a report published last week.
The issues, tracked as CVE-2023-34392 and from CVE-2023-31168]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[W3LL Store: How a Secret Phishing Syndicate Targets 8,000+ Microsoft 365 Accounts]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/w3ll-store-how-secret-phishing.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/w3ll-store-how-secret-phishing.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T08:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A previously undocumented "phishing empire" has been linked to cyber attacks aimed at compromising Microsoft 365 business email accounts over the past six years.
"The threat actor created a hidden underground market, named W3LL Store, that served a closed community of at least 500 threat actors who could purchase a custom phishing kit called W3LL Panel, designed to bypass MFA, as well as 16]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ukraine's CERT Thwarts APT28's Cyberattack on Critical Energy Infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/ukraines-cert-thwarts-apt28s.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/ukraines-cert-thwarts-apt28s.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T08:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Computer Emergency Response Team of Ukraine (CERT-UA) on Tuesday said it thwarted a cyber attack against an unnamed critical energy infrastructure facility in the country.
The intrusion, per the agency, started with a phishing email containing a link to a malicious ZIP archive that activates the infection chain.
“Visiting the link will download a ZIP archive containing three JPG images (]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Results of Major Technical Investigations for Storm-0558 Key Acquisition]]></title>
        <id>https://msrc.microsoft.com/blog/2023/09/results-of-major-technical-investigations-for-storm-0558-key-acquisition/</id>
        <link href="https://msrc.microsoft.com/blog/2023/09/results-of-major-technical-investigations-for-storm-0558-key-acquisition/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On July 11, 2023, Microsoft published a blog post which details how the China-Based threat actor, Storm-0558, used an acquired Microsoft account (MSA) consumer key to forge tokens to access OWA and Outlook.com. Upon identifying that the threat actor had acquired the consumer key, Microsoft performed a comprehensive technical investigation into the acquisition of the Microsoft account consumer signing key, including how it was used to access enterprise email.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Microsoft Security Response Center</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6342-1: Linux kernel vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6342-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6342-1"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T00:31:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tavis Ormandy discovered that some AMD processors did not properly handle
speculative execution of certain vector register instructions. A local
attacker could use this to expose sensitive information. (CVE-2023-20593)

Zheng Zhang discovered that the device-mapper implementation in the Linux
kernel did not properly handle locking during table_clear() operations. A
local attacker could use this to cause a denial of service (kernel
deadlock). (CVE-2023-2269)

It was discovered that a use-after-free vulnerability existed in the HFS+
file system implementation in the Linux kernel. A local attacker could
possibly use this to cause a denial of service (system crash).
(CVE-2023-2985)

It was discovered that the DVB Core driver in the Linux kernel did not
properly handle locking events in certain situations. A local attacker
could use this to cause a denial of service (kernel deadlock).
(CVE-2023-31084)

It was discovered that the Quick Fair Queueing network scheduler
implementation in the Linux kernel contained an out-of-bounds write
vulnerability. A local attacker could use this to cause a denial of service
(system crash) or possibly execute arbitrary code. (CVE-2023-3611)

It was discovered that the network packet classifier with
netfilter/firewall marks implementation in the Linux kernel did not
properly handle reference counting, leading to a use-after-free
vulnerability. A local attacker could use this to cause a denial of service
(system crash) or possibly execute arbitrary code. (CVE-2023-3776)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Discover Critical Vulnerability in PHPFusion CMS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/researchers-discover-critical-vulnerability-in-phpfusion-cms</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/researchers-discover-critical-vulnerability-in-phpfusion-cms"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T21:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No patch is available yet for the bug, which can enable remote code execution under the correct circumstances.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LockBit Leaks Documents Filched From UK Defense Contractor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/lockbit-leaks-documents-filched-from-uk-defence-contractor</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/lockbit-leaks-documents-filched-from-uk-defence-contractor"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T21:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A company that builds physical perimeter defenses failed to keep the LockBit group from penetrating its cyber defenses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tuya Smart and Amazon Web Services Collaborate to Establish an IoT Security Lab]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/ics-ot/tuya-smart-and-amazon-web-services-collaborate-to-establish-an-iot-security-lab</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/ics-ot/tuya-smart-and-amazon-web-services-collaborate-to-establish-an-iot-security-lab"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T20:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global Cloud Security Market to Reach $62.9B by 2028]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/global-cloud-security-market-to-reach-62-9b-by-2028</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/global-cloud-security-market-to-reach-62-9b-by-2028"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T20:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hornetsecurity Releases 365 Total Protection Plan 4 for Microsoft 365]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/hornetsecurity-releases-365-total-protection-plan-4-for-microsoft-365</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/hornetsecurity-releases-365-total-protection-plan-4-for-microsoft-365"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GhostSec Leaks Source Code of Alleged Iranian Surveillance Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/ghostsec-source-code-alleged-iranian-surveillance-tool</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/ghostsec-source-code-alleged-iranian-surveillance-tool"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T19:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GhostSec has made the source code for what it calls a powerful surveillance tool openly available in a 26GB file, but FANAP denies its legitimacy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Raywood, Senior Editor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peiter 'Mudge' Zatko Lands Role as CISA Senior Technical Adviser]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/careers-and-people/peiter-mudge-zatko-lands-role-as-cisa-senior-technical-</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/careers-and-people/peiter-mudge-zatko-lands-role-as-cisa-senior-technical-"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T18:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The former hacker and Twitter security executive will use his role to help fulfill the Biden administration's plans for the National Cybersecurity Strategy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Target High-Privileged Okta Accounts via Help Desk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/hackers-target-high-privileged-okta-accounts-via-help-desk</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/hackers-target-high-privileged-okta-accounts-via-help-desk"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T18:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors convince employees to reset MFA for Super Admin accounts in the IAM service to leverage compromised accounts, impersonating users and moving laterally within an organization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Montalbano, Contributor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Initiatives Force Closer Partnership Between CISOs, CDOs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/risk/data-initiatives-force-closer-partnership-ciso-cdo</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/risk/data-initiatives-force-closer-partnership-ciso-cdo"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Though security leaders and chief data officers both care about data management, their different missions have created a tension that needs addressing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia Undertakes Disinformation Campaign Across Africa]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/russia-undertakes-disinformation-campaign-across-africa-follwnfg-coups</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/russia-undertakes-disinformation-campaign-across-africa-follwnfg-coups"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T17:48:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following coups in some African nations, Russia is exploiting the instability with the manipulation of media channels to stoke anti-French sentiment, among other things.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Companies Can Cope With the Risks of Generative AI Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/how-companies-can-cope-risk-generative-ai-tools</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/how-companies-can-cope-risk-generative-ai-tools"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To benefit from AI yet minimize risk, companies should be cautious about information they share, be aware of AI's limitations, and stay vigilant about business implications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shay Levi, Co-Founder &amp; CTO, Noname Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New BLISTER Malware Update Fuelling Stealthy Network Infiltration]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/new-blister-malware-update-fuelling.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/new-blister-malware-update-fuelling.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T14:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An updated version of a malware loader known as BLISTER is being used as part of SocGholish infection chains to distribute an open-source command-and-control (C2) framework called Mythic.
“New BLISTER update includes keying feature that allows for precise targeting of victim networks and lowers exposure within VM/sandbox environments,” Elastic Security Labs researchers Salim Bitam and Daniel]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As LotL Attacks Evolve, So Must Defenses]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/as-lotl-attacks-evolve-so-must-defenses</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/as-lotl-attacks-evolve-so-must-defenses"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Because living-off-the-land (LotL) attacks masquerade as frequently used, legitimate companies, they are very difficult to block and detect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Troy Gill, Senior Manager of Threat Research, OpenText Cybersecurity</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Name That Edge Toon: Prized Possessions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge-articles/name-that-edge-toon-prized-collection</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge-articles/name-that-edge-toon-prized-collection"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Come up with a clever caption, and our panel of experts will reward the winner with a $25 Amazon gift card.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Klossner, Cartoonist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Python Variant of Chaes Malware Targets Banking and Logistics Industries]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/new-python-variant-of-chaes-malware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/new-python-variant-of-chaes-malware.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T12:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Banking and logistics industries are under the onslaught of a reworked variant of a malware called Chaes.
"It has undergone major overhauls: from being rewritten entirely in Python, which resulted in lower detection rates by traditional defense systems, to a comprehensive redesign and an enhanced communication protocol," Morphisec said in a new detailed technical write-up shared with The Hacker]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Releases Two Industrial Control Systems Advisories]]></title>
        <id>/node/18731</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/09/05/cisa-releases-two-industrial-control-systems-advisories"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CISA released two Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisories on September 5, 2023. These advisories provide timely information about current security issues, vulnerabilities, and exploits surrounding ICS. 
ICSA-23-248-01 Fujitsu Limited Real-time Video Transmission Gear IP series
ICSMA-23-248-01 Softneta MedDream PACS Premium
 
CISA encourages users and administrators to review the newly released ICS advisories for technical details and mitigations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Way Too Vulnerable: Join this Webinar to Understand and Strengthen Identity Attack Surface]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/way-too-vulnerable-join-this-webinar-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/way-too-vulnerable-join-this-webinar-to.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T11:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's digital age, it's not just about being online but how securely your organization operates online. Regardless of size or industry, every organization heavily depends on digital assets. The digital realm is where business takes place, from financial transactions to confidential data storage.
While organizations have quickly adopted tools like Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA),]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Key Cybersecurity Tools That Can Mitigate the Cost of a Breach]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/key-cybersecurity-tools-that-can.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/key-cybersecurity-tools-that-can.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T11:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IBM's 2023 installment of their annual "Cost of a Breach" report has thrown up some interesting trends. Of course, breaches being costly is no longer news at this stage! What’s interesting is the difference in how organizations respond to threats and which technologies are helping reduce the costs associated with every IT team’s nightmare scenario. 
The average cost of a breach rose once again]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inconsistencies in the Common Vulnerability Scoring System (CVSS)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/09/inconsistencies-in-the-common-vulnerability-scoring-system-cvss.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/09/inconsistencies-in-the-common-vulnerability-scoring-system-cvss.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T11:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Interesting <a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2308.15259">research</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>Shedding Light on CVSS Scoring Inconsistencies: A User-Centric Study on Evaluating Widespread Security Vulnerabilities</p>
<p><b>Abstract:</b> The Common Vulnerability Scoring System (CVSS) is a popular method for evaluating the severity of vulnerabilities in vulnerability management. In the evaluation process, a numeric score between 0 and 10 is calculated, 10 being the most severe (critical) value. The goal of CVSS is to provide comparable scores across different evaluators. However, previous works indicate that CVSS might not reach this goal: If a vulnerability is evaluated by several analysts, their scores often differ. This raises the following questions: Are CVSS evaluations consistent? Which factors influence CVSS assessments? We systematically investigate these questions in an online survey with 196 CVSS users. We show that specific CVSS metrics are inconsistently evaluated for widespread vulnerability types, including Top 3 vulnerabilities from the &#8221;2022 CWE Top 25 Most Dangerous Software Weaknesses&#8221; list. In a follow-up survey with 59 participants, we found that for the same vulnerabilities from the main study, 68% of these users gave different severity ratings. Our study reveals that most evaluators are aware of the problematic aspects of CVSS, but they still see CVSS as a useful tool for vulnerability assessment. Finally, we discuss possible reasons for inconsistent evaluations and provide recommendations on improving the consistency of scoring...</p></blockquote>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Warn of Cyber Weapons Used by Lazarus Group's Andariel Cluster]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/researchers-warn-of-cyber-weapons-used.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/researchers-warn-of-cyber-weapons-used.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T10:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The North Korean threat actor known as Andariel has been observed employing an arsenal of malicious tools in its cyber assaults against corporations and organizations in the southern counterpart.
“One characteristic of the attacks identified in 2023 is that there are numerous malware strains developed in the Go language,” the AhnLab Security Emergency Response Center (ASEC) said in a deep dive]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Takes Down Thousands of Accounts Involved in Disinformation Ops from China and Russia]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/meta-takes-down-thousands-of-accounts.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/meta-takes-down-thousands-of-accounts.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T06:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta has disclosed that it disrupted two of the largest known covert influence operations in the world from China and Russia, blocking thousands of accounts and pages across its platform.
“It targeted more than 50 apps, including Facebook, Instagram, X (formerly Twitter), YouTube, TikTok, Reddit, Pinterest, Medium, Blogspot, LiveJournal, VKontakte, Vimeo, and dozens of smaller platforms and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Exploit MinIO Storage System Vulnerabilities to Compromise Servers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/hackers-exploit-minio-storage-system.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/hackers-exploit-minio-storage-system.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T14:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An unknown threat actor has been observed weaponizing high-severity security flaws in the MinIO high-performance object storage system to achieve unauthorized code execution on affected servers.
Cybersecurity and incident response firm Security Joes said the intrusion leveraged a publicly available exploit chain to backdoor the MinIO instance.
The comprises CVE-2023-28432 (CVSS score: 7.5) and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Realism Reigns on AI at Black Hat and DEF CON]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/omdia/realism-reigns-on-ai-at-black-hat-and-def-con</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/omdia/realism-reigns-on-ai-at-black-hat-and-def-con"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Realistic expectations and caution began to replace wonder and confusion for generative AI at the recent security industry gatherings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Curtis Franklin, Senior Analyst, Omdia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[X (Twitter) to Collect Biometric Data from Premium Users to Combat Impersonation]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/x-twitter-to-collect-biometric-data.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/x-twitter-to-collect-biometric-data.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T12:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[X, the social media site formerly known as Twitter, has updated its privacy policy to collect users’ biometric data to tackle fraud and impersonation on the platform.
“Based on your consent, we may collect and use your biometric information for safety, security, and identification purposes,” the company said. The revised policy is expected to go into effect on September 29, 2023.
The social]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything You Wanted to Know About AI Security but Were Afraid to Ask]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/everything-you-wanted-to-know-about-ai.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/everything-you-wanted-to-know-about-ai.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T11:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s been a great deal of AI hype recently, but that doesn’t mean the robots are here to replace us. This article sets the record straight and explains how businesses should approach AI.
From musing about self-driving cars to fearing AI bots that could destroy the world, there has been a great deal of AI hype in the past few years. AI has captured our imaginations, dreams, and occasionally,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vietnamese Cybercriminals Targeting Facebook Business Accounts with Malvertising]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/vietnamese-cybercriminals-targeting.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/vietnamese-cybercriminals-targeting.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malicious actors associated with the Vietnamese cybercrime ecosystem are leveraging advertising-as-a-vector on social media platforms such as Meta-owned Facebook to distribute malware.
“Threat actors have long used fraudulent ads as a vector to target victims with scams, malvertising, and more,” WithSecure researcher Mohammad Kazem Hassan Nejad said. “And with businesses now leveraging the reach]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Facing Third-Party Threats With Non-Employee Risk Management]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/risk/facing-third-party-threats-with-non-employee-risk-management</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/risk/facing-third-party-threats-with-non-employee-risk-management"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As businesses continue to grapple with third-party threats, a revamped approach to non-employee risk management can help limit their potential exposure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beware of MalDoc in PDF: A New Polyglot Attack Allowing Attackers to Evade Antivirus]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/beware-of-maldoc-in-pdf-new-polyglot.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/beware-of-maldoc-in-pdf-new-polyglot.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T05:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have called attention to a new antivirus evasion technique that involves embedding a malicious Microsoft Word file into a PDF file.
The sneaky method, dubbed MalDoc in PDF by JPCERT/CC, is said to have been employed in an in-the-wild attack in July 2023.
"A file created with MalDoc in PDF can be opened in Word even though it has magic numbers and file structure of PDF,"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese-Speaking Cybercriminals Launch Large-Scale iMessage Smishing Campaign in U.S.]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/chinese-speaking-cybercriminals-launch.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/chinese-speaking-cybercriminals-launch.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T05:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new large-scale smishing campaign is targeting the U.S. by sending iMessages from compromised Apple iCloud accounts with an aim to conduct identity theft and financial fraud.
“The Chinese-speaking threat actors behind this campaign are operating a package-tracking text scam sent via iMessage to collect personally identifying information (PII) and payment credentials from victims, in the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PoC Exploit Released for Critical VMware Aria's SSH Auth Bypass Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/poc-exploit-released-for-critical.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/poc-exploit-released-for-critical.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T04:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Proof-of-concept (PoC) exploit code has been made available for a recently disclosed and patched critical flaw impacting VMware Aria Operations for Networks (formerly vRealize Network Insight).
The flaw, tracked as CVE-2023-34039, is rated 9.8 out of a maximum of 10 for severity and has been described as a case of authentication bypass due to a lack of unique cryptographic key generation.
“A]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Okta Warns of Social Engineering Attacks Targeting Super Administrator Privileges]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/okta-warns-of-social-engineering.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/okta-warns-of-social-engineering.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T04:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Identity services provider Okta on Friday warned of social engineering attacks orchestrated by threat actors to obtain elevated administrator permissions.
“In recent weeks, multiple U.S.-based Okta customers have reported a consistent pattern of social engineering attacks against IT service desk personnel, in which the caller’s strategy was to convince service desk personnel to reset all]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friday Squid Blogging: We’re Genetically Engineering Squid Now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/09/friday-squid-blogging-were-genetically-engineering-squid-now.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/09/friday-squid-blogging-were-genetically-engineering-squid-now.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T21:29:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Is <a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2023/08/28/1196073961/how-scientists-engineered-a-see-through-squid-with-its-brain-in-plain-view">this</a> a good idea?</p>
<blockquote><p>The transparent squid is a genetically altered version of the <a href="https://www.mbl.edu/research/research-organisms/hummingbird-bobtail-squid">hummingbird bobtail squid</a>, a species usually found in the tropical waters from Indonesia to China and Japan. It&#8217;s typically smaller than a thumb and shaped like a dumpling. And like other cephalopods, it has a relatively large and sophisticated brain.</p>
<p>The see-through version is made possible by a gene editing technology called <a>CRISPR</a>, which became popular nearly a decade ago.</p>
<p>Albertin and Rosenthal thought they might be able to use CRISPR to create a special squid for research. They focused on the hummingbird bobtail squid because it is small, a prodigious breeder, and thrives in lab aquariums, including one at the lab in Woods Hole...</p></blockquote>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lacework Expands Partnership With Google Cloud to Deliver Enterprise Flexibility in the Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/lacework-expands-partnership-with-google-cloud-to-deliver-enterprise-flexibility-in-the-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/lacework-expands-partnership-with-google-cloud-to-deliver-enterprise-flexibility-in-the-cloud"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T20:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ReasonLabs Summer 2023 Trends Report Reveals Top Consumer Security Threats]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/reasonlabs-summer-2023-trends-report-reveals-top-consumer-security-threats</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/reasonlabs-summer-2023-trends-report-reveals-top-consumer-security-threats"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T20:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI for Good: Voxel AI Tech Increases Funding to $30M With Strategic Funding Round]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/ai-for-good-voxel-ai-tech-increases-funding-to-30m-with-strategic-funding-round</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/ai-for-good-voxel-ai-tech-increases-funding-to-30m-with-strategic-funding-round"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T20:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inaugural Pwn2Own Automotive Contest Dangles $1M for Car Hackers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/inaugural-pwn2own-automotive-contest-1m-car-hackers</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/inaugural-pwn2own-automotive-contest-1m-car-hackers"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The competition encourages automotive research and allows for contestants to take part in person or remotely.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Government Denies Blocking Sales of AI Chips to Middle East]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/us-government-denies-blocking-chip-sales-middle-east</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/us-government-denies-blocking-chip-sales-middle-east"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T18:50:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia and AMD do face expanded export rules for their A100 and H100 artificial intelligence (AI) chips in the Middle East, but it's not yet clear why.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Raywood, Senior Editor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MSSQL Databases Under Fire From FreeWorld Ransomware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/mssql-databases-under-fire-from-freeworld-ransomware</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/mssql-databases-under-fire-from-freeworld-ransomware"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T18:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The sophisticated attacks, tracked as DB#JAMMER, run shell commands to impair defenses and deploy tools to establish persistence on the host.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Eddy, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will the AI Arms Race Lead to the Pollution of the Internet?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/will-the-ai-arms-race-lead-to-the-pollution-of-the-internet-</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/will-the-ai-arms-race-lead-to-the-pollution-of-the-internet-"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T17:59:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Content creators want to protect their intellectual property from AI by poisoning data. Could this destroy the machine learning ecosystem?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Lemos, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Key Group Ransomware Foiled by New Decryptor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/key-group-ransomware-decryptor</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/key-group-ransomware-decryptor"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T17:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers crack Key Group's ransomware encryption and release free tool for victim organizations to recover their data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NYC Subway Disables Trip-History Feature Over Tap-and-Go Privacy Concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/risk/new-york-subway-disables-trip-history-feature-tap-and-go-privacy-concerns</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/risk/new-york-subway-disables-trip-history-feature-tap-and-go-privacy-concerns"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T16:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The move by New York's Metropolitan Transit Authority (MTA) follows a report that showed how easy it is for someone to pull up another individual's seven-day ride history through the One Metro New York (OMNY) website.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Threat Actors Targeting Microsoft SQL Servers to Deploy FreeWorld Ransomware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/threat-actors-targeting-microsoft-sql.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/threat-actors-targeting-microsoft-sql.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T15:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors are exploiting poorly secured Microsoft SQL (MS SQL) servers to deliver Cobalt Strike and a ransomware strain called FreeWorld.
Cybersecurity firm Securonix, which has dubbed the campaign DB#JAMMER, said it stands out for the way the toolset and infrastructure is employed.
“Some of these tools include enumeration software, RAT payloads, exploitation and credential stealing software]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proposed SEC Cybersecurity Rule Will Put Unnecessary Strain on CISOs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/risk/proposed-sec-cybersecurity-rule-will-put-unnecessary-strain-on-cisos</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/risk/proposed-sec-cybersecurity-rule-will-put-unnecessary-strain-on-cisos"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Security and Exchange Commission's Proposed Rule for Public Companies (PPRC) is ambiguous.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Hodson, Chief Security Officer, Cyberhaven</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VMware Releases Security Update for Tools]]></title>
        <id>/node/18726</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/09/01/vmware-releases-security-update-tools"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VMware has released a security update to address a vulnerability in VMware Tools. A cyber threat actor can exploit this vulnerability to obtain sensitive information.
CISA encourages users and administrators to review VMware Security Advisory VMSA-2023-0019 and apply the necessary update.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spyware Vendor Hacked]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/09/spyware-vendor-hacked.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/09/spyware-vendor-hacked.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T11:07:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>A Brazilian spyware app vendor was <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2023/08/26/brazil-webdetetive-spyware-deleted/">hacked</a> by activists:</p>
<blockquote><p>In an undated note seen by TechCrunch, the unnamed hackers described how they found and exploited several security vulnerabilities that allowed them to compromise WebDetetive’s servers and access its user databases. By exploiting other flaws in the spyware maker’s web dashboard&#8212;used by abusers to access the stolen phone data of their victims&#8212;the hackers said they enumerated and downloaded every dashboard record, including every customer’s email address.</p>
<p>The hackers said that dashboard access also allowed them to delete victim devices from the spyware network altogether, effectively severing the connection at the server level to prevent the device from uploading new data. &#8220;Which we definitely did. Because we could. Because #fuckstalkerware,&#8221; the hackers wrote in the note...</p></blockquote>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian State-Backed 'Infamous Chisel' Android Malware Targets Ukrainian Military]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/russian-state-backed-infamous-chisel.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/russian-state-backed-infamous-chisel.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T10:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity and intelligence agencies from Australia, Canada, New Zealand, the U.K., and the U.S. on Thursday disclosed details of a mobile malware strain targeting Android devices used by the Ukrainian military.
The malicious software, dubbed Infamous Chisel and attributed to a Russian state-sponsored actor called Sandworm, has capabilities to “enable unauthorized access to compromised]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New SuperBear Trojan Emerges in Targeted Phishing Attack on South Korean Activists]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/new-superbear-trojan-emerges-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/new-superbear-trojan-emerges-in.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T09:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new phishing attack likely targeting civil society groups in South Korea has led to the discovery of a novel remote access trojan called SuperBear.
The intrusion singled out an unnamed activist, who was contacted in late August 2023 and received a malicious LNK file from an address impersonating a member of the organization, non-profit entity Interlabs said in a new report.
The LNK file, upon]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It's a Zero-day? It's Malware? No! It's Username and Password]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/its-zero-day-its-malware-no-its.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/its-zero-day-its-malware-no-its.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As cyber threats continue to evolve, adversaries are deploying a range of tools to breach security defenses and compromise sensitive data. Surprisingly, one of the most potent weapons in their arsenal is not malicious code but simply stolen or weak usernames and passwords. This article explores the seriousness of compromised credentials, the challenges they present to security solutions, and the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Classiscam Scam-as-a-Service Raked $64.5 Million During the COVID-19 Pandemic]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/classiscam-scam-as-service-raked-645.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/09/classiscam-scam-as-service-raked-645.html"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T07:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Classiscam scam-as-a-service program has reaped the criminal actors $64.5 million in illicit earnings since its emergence in 2019.
"Classiscam campaigns initially started out on classified sites, on which scammers placed fake advertisements and used social engineering techniques to convince users to pay for goods by transferring money to bank cards," Group-IB said in a new report.
"Since]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[National Cybersecurity Alliance Receives 200K Grant From Craig Newmark Philanthropies for HBCU Cybersecurity Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/national-cybersecurity-alliance-receives-200k-grant-from-craig-newmark-philanthropies-for-hbcu-cybersecurity-program</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/national-cybersecurity-alliance-receives-200k-grant-from-craig-newmark-philanthropies-for-hbcu-cybersecurity-program"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T21:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cygna Labs Corp. Announces Expansion of its DNS Firewall Service]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/perimeter/cygna-labs-corp-announces-expansion-of-its-dns-firewall-service</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/perimeter/cygna-labs-corp-announces-expansion-of-its-dns-firewall-service"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T21:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing SafeUTM: The Free Version of NGFW]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/perimeter/introducing-safeutm-the-free-version-of-ngfw</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/perimeter/introducing-safeutm-the-free-version-of-ngfw"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T21:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 out of 4 Cyberattacks in the Education Sector Are Associated With a Compromised On‑Premises User or Admin Account]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/3-out-of-4-cyberattacks-in-the-education-sector-are-associated-with-a-compromised-on-premises-user-or-admin-account</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/3-out-of-4-cyberattacks-in-the-education-sector-are-associated-with-a-compromised-on-premises-user-or-admin-account"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T21:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UN: Southeast Asia Gangs Are Trafficking Cybercrime Workers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/un-southeast-asia-gangs-trafficking-cybercrime-workers</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/un-southeast-asia-gangs-trafficking-cybercrime-workers"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybercrime syndicates are forcing people into working for them, and it's a difficult issue to solve, involving digital platforms, political powers, and organized crime on a global scale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Insurance Costs Rise, Coverage Shrinks, but Policies Remain Essential]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/risk/insurance-costs-rise-coverage-shrinks-but-policies-remain-essential</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/risk/insurance-costs-rise-coverage-shrinks-but-policies-remain-essential"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T20:53:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The number of companies that have used their cyber insurance policies multiple times rises, but policy coverage grows more expensive and less comprehensive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Lemos, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybercriminals Team Up to Upgrade 'SapphireStealer' Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/cybercriminals-team-up-upgrade-sapphirestealer-malware</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/cybercriminals-team-up-upgrade-sapphirestealer-malware"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A hacker published a real gem of an infostealer to GitHub that requires zero coding knowledge to use. Then a community sprung up around it, polishing the code to a high shine and creating new, even more robust features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK Agrees to Support Kuwait's Cybersecurity Center]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/uk-agrees-support-kuwait-cybersecurity-center</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/uk-agrees-support-kuwait-cybersecurity-center"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T18:40:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The UK has agreed to help the Kuwaitis meet their stated goal of information-sharing and achieving globally coordinated incident response going forward.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paramount, Forever 21 Data Breaches Set Stage for Follow-on Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/paramount-forever-21-data-breaches-follow-on-attacks</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/paramount-forever-21-data-breaches-follow-on-attacks"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T18:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Forever 21 breach alone affects a half-million people, who could be a mix of consumers and employees; Paramount is staying mum on who exactly is impacted.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tara Seals, Managing Editor, News, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple iPhone 14 Pro Offered Up to the Hacking Masses]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/apple-iphone-14-pro-hacking</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/apple-iphone-14-pro-hacking"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since launching in 2019, the Security Device Research Program has discovered 130 critical vulnerabilities; applications are now open for Apple's 2024 iteration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cyberattackers Swarm OpenFire Cloud Servers With Takeover Barrage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/remote-workforce/cyberattackers-openfire-cloud-servers-takeover-barrage</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/remote-workforce/cyberattackers-openfire-cloud-servers-takeover-barrage"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T14:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Kinsing threat group has launched more than 1,000 cyberattacks in less than two months, exploiting a security vulnerability in the internal corporate messaging app in order to upload the malware and a cryptominer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Montalbano, Contributor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SapphireStealer Malware: A Gateway to Espionage and Ransomware Operations]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/sapphirestealer-malware-gateway-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/sapphirestealer-malware-gateway-to.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T14:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An open-source .NET-based information stealer malware dubbed SapphireStealer is being used by multiple entities to enhance its capabilities and spawn their own bespoke variants.
“Information-stealing malware like SapphireStealer can be used to obtain sensitive information, including corporate credentials, which are often resold to other threat actors who leverage the access for additional]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Brief History of ICS-Tailored Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/brief-history-of-ics-tailored-attacks</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/brief-history-of-ics-tailored-attacks"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's on the cyber defenders to learn from the past and make industrial control system networks hostile to attackers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oleg Brodt, Head of R&amp;D and Innovation, Cyber@Ben-Gurion University, Israel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adversaries Ride RocketMQ Bug to DreamBus Bot Resurgence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/threat-actors-riding-rocketmq-bug-to-dreambus-bot-resurgence</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/threat-actors-riding-rocketmq-bug-to-dreambus-bot-resurgence"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T13:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last seen in 2021, DreamBus Monero crypto bot is back and finding new life on vulnerable RocketMQ servers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean Hackers Deploy New Malicious Python Packages in PyPI Repository]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/north-korean-hackers-deploy-new.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/north-korean-hackers-deploy-new.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T12:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three additional rogue Python packages have been discovered in the Package Index (PyPI) repository as part of an ongoing malicious software supply chain campaign called VMConnect, with signs pointing to the involvement of North Korean state-sponsored threat actors.
The findings come from ReversingLabs, which detected the packages tablediter, request-plus, and requestspro.
First disclosed at the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Releases Four Industrial Control Systems Advisories]]></title>
        <id>/node/18718</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/08/31/cisa-releases-four-industrial-control-systems-advisories"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CISA released four Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisories on August 31, 2023. These advisories provide timely information about current security issues, vulnerabilities, and exploits surrounding ICS.
ICSA-23-243-01 ARDEREG Sistemas SCADA
ICSA-23-243-02 GE Digital CIMPLICITY
ICSA-23-243-03 PTC Kepware KepServerEX
ICSA-23-243-04 Digi RealPort Protocol
CISA encourages users and administrators to review the newly released ICS advisories for technical details and mitigations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA and International Partners Release Malware Analysis Report on Infamous Chisel Mobile Malware]]></title>
        <id>/node/18719</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/08/31/cisa-and-international-partners-release-malware-analysis-report-infamous-chisel-mobile-malware"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, the United Kingdom’s National Cyber Security Centre (NCSC-UK), the United States’ Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA), National Security Agency (NSA), and Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI), New Zealand’s National Cyber Security Centre (NCSC-NZ), the Canadian Centre for Cyber Security (CCCS), and the Australian Signals Directorate (ASD) published a joint Malware Analysis Report (MAR), on Infamous Chisel, a new mobile malware targeting Android devices that has capabilities to enable unauthorized access to compromised devices, scan files, monitor traffic, and periodically steal sensitive information. Infamous Chisel mobile malware has been used in a malware campaign targeting Android devices used by the Ukrainian military.
Infamous Chisel is a collection of components targeting Android devices that the authoring organizations have attributed to Sandworm, the Russian Main Intelligence Directorate’s (GRU’s) Main Centre for Special Technologies, GTsST. The malware’s capability includes network monitoring, traffic collection, network backdoor access via The Onion Router (Tor) and Secure Shell (SSH), network scanning, and Secure Copy Protocol (SCP) file transfer. 
The authoring organizations urge cybersecurity defenders to review the malware analysis report for indicators of compromise (IOCs), detection rules, and signatures to determine system compromise. For more information about malware, see CISA’s Malware, Phishing, and Ransomware page. The joint MAR can also be read in full on the NCSC-UK website. Associated files relating to this report can also be accessed via the NCSC's Malware Analysis Reports page. For more information on Russian state-sponsored cyber activity, please see CISA’s Russia Cyber Threat Overview and Advisories webpage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Warns of Hurricane-Related Scams]]></title>
        <id>/node/18721</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/08/31/cisa-warns-hurricane-related-scams"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CISA urges users to remain on alert for malicious cyber activity following natural disasters, such as hurricanes, as attackers target disaster victims and concerned citizens by leveraging social engineering tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs).
Social engineering TTPs include phishing, in which threat actors pose as trustworthy persons/organizations—such as disaster-relief charities—to solicit personal information via email or malicious websites. CISA recommends exercising caution in handling emails with disaster-related subject lines, attachments, or hyperlinks. In addition, be wary of social media pleas and texts messages related to severe weather events.
CISA encourages users to review the following resources to avoid falling victim to malicious cyber activity:
Federal Trade Commission’s Staying Alert to Disaster-related Scams and Before Giving to a Charity,
Consumer Financial Protection Bureau's Frauds and scams, and
CISA’s Using Caution with Email Attachments and Avoiding Social Engineering and Phishing Attacks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Numbers Don't Lie: Exposing the Harsh Truths of Cyberattacks in New Report]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/numbers-dont-lie-exposing-harsh-truths.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/numbers-dont-lie-exposing-harsh-truths.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How often do cyberattacks happen? How frequently do threat actors target businesses and governments around the world? The BlackBerry® Threat Research and Intelligence Team recently analyzed 90 days of real-world data to answer these questions. Full results are in the latest BlackBerry Global Threat Intelligence Report, but read on for a teaser of several interesting cyber attack statistics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Own Your Own Government Surveillance Van]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/08/own-your-own-government-surveillance-van.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/08/own-your-own-government-surveillance-van.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T11:06:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>A used government surveillance van is <a href="https://www.theautopian.com/a-used-car-dealership-in-chicago-is-selling-an-actual-government-surveillance-van-for-26795/">for sale</a> in Chicago:</p>
<blockquote><p>So how was this van turned into a mobile spying center? Well, let&#8217;s start with how it has more LCD monitors than a Counterstrike LAN party. They can be used to monitor any of six different video inputs including a videoscope camera. A videoscope and a borescope are very similar as they&#8217;re both cameras on the ends of optical fibers, so the same tech you&#8217;d use to inspect cylinder walls is also useful for surveillance. Kind of cool, right? Multiple Sony DVD-based video recorders store footage captured by cameras, audio recorders by high-end equipment brand Marantz capture sounds, and time and date generators sync gathered media up for accurate analysis. Circling back around to audio, this van features seven different audio inputs including a body wire channel...</p></blockquote>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Earth Estries' Espionage Campaign Targets Governments and Tech Titans Across Continents]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/earth-estries-espionage-campaign.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/earth-estries-espionage-campaign.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T09:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A hacking outfit nicknamed Earth Estries has been attributed to a new, ongoing cyber espionage campaign targeting government and technology industries based in the Philippines, Taiwan, Malaysia, South Africa, Germany, and the U.S.
"The threat actors behind Earth Estries are working with high-level resources and functioning with sophisticated skills and experience in cyber espionage and illicit]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Infamous Chisel Malware Analysis Report]]></title>
        <id>/node/18713</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/analysis-reports/ar23-243a"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T00:56:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Infamous Chisel–A collection of components associated with Sandworm designed to enable remote access and exfiltrate information from Android phones.
Executive Summary
Infamous Chisel is a collection of components targeting Android devices.
This malware is associated with Sandworm activity.
It performs periodic scanning of files and network information for exfiltration.
System and application configuration files are exfiltrated from an infected device.
Infamous Chisel provides network backdoor access via a Tor (The Onion Router) hidden service and Secure Shell (SSH).
Other capabilities include network monitoring, traffic collection, SSH access, network scanning, and SCP file transfer.
Overview
The UK National Cyber Security Centre (NCSC), the U.S. National Security Agency (NSA), U.S. Cybers…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Group Spreads Android Spyware via Trojan Signal, Telegram Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/china-group-spreads-android-spyware-via-trojan-signal-telegram-apps</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/china-group-spreads-android-spyware-via-trojan-signal-telegram-apps"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T21:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thousands of devices have become infected with "BadBazaar," malware previously used to spy on Uyghur and Turkic ethnic minorities in China.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[APT Attacks From 'Earth Estries' Hit Gov't, Tech With Custom Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/-apt-attacks-from-earth-estries-hit-govt-tech-with-custom-malware</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/-apt-attacks-from-earth-estries-hit-govt-tech-with-custom-malware"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T21:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A sophisticated threat actor managed to fly under the radar for three years, despite flexing serious muscle.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New York Times Spoofed to Hide Russian Disinformation Campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/new-york-times-spoofed-russian-disinformation-campaign</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/new-york-times-spoofed-russian-disinformation-campaign"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Operation Doppelganger" has convincingly masqueraded as multiple news sites with elaborate fake stories containing real bylines of journalists, blasting them out on social media platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Can Exploit Windows Container Isolation Framework to Bypass Endpoint Security]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/hackers-can-exploit-windows-container.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/hackers-can-exploit-windows-container.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T17:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New findings show that malicious actors could leverage a sneaky malware detection evasion technique and bypass endpoint security solutions by manipulating the Windows Container Isolation Framework.
The findings were presented by Deep Instinct security researcher Daniel Avinoam at the DEF CON security conference held earlier this month.
Microsoft's container architecture (and by extension,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 Strategies to Safeguard the Finance Industry Against Deepfake Onslaught]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/4-strategies-to-safeguard-the-finance-industry-against-deepfake-onslaught</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/4-strategies-to-safeguard-the-finance-industry-against-deepfake-onslaught"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Through strategic measures and a united front, the finance industry can overcome the looming threat of deepfakes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Kirkwood, Deputy CISO, LogRhythm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Performance-Enhanced Android MMRat Scurries Onto Devices via Fake App Stores]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/performance-enhanced-android-mmrat-scurries-onto-devices-via-fake-app-stores</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/performance-enhanced-android-mmrat-scurries-onto-devices-via-fake-app-stores"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The stealthy Trojan targets users in Southeast Asia, allowing attackers to remotely control devices to commit bank fraud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Montalbano, Contributor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MMRat Android Trojan Executes Remote Financial Fraud Through Accessibility Feature]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/mmrat-android-trojan-executes-remote.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/mmrat-android-trojan-executes-remote.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T15:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A previously undocumented Android banking trojan dubbed MMRat has been observed targeting mobile users in Southeast Asia since late June 2023 to remotely commandeer the devices and perform financial fraud.
"The malware, named after its distinctive package name com.mm.user, can capture user input and screen content, and can also remotely control victim devices through various techniques, enabling]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should Senior IT Professionals Be Accountable for Professional Decisions?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/should-senior-it-professionals-be-accountable-for-professional-decisions-</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/should-senior-it-professionals-be-accountable-for-professional-decisions-"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone makes mistakes — but what if your mistakes risk the security of millions of people?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Watts, Managing Director, Databarracks</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China-Linked BadBazaar Android Spyware Targeting Signal and Telegram Users]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/china-linked-badbazaar-android-spyware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/china-linked-badbazaar-android-spyware.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T13:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered malicious Android apps for Signal and Telegram distributed via the Google Play Store and Samsung Galaxy Store that are engineered to deliver the BadBazaar spyware on infected devices.
Slovakian company ESET attributed the campaign to a China-linked actor called GREF.
"Most likely active since July 2020 and since July 2022, respectively, the campaigns]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Apps Go Rogue]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/08/when-apps-go-rogue.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/08/when-apps-go-rogue.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T13:39:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Interesting <a href="https://gizmodo.com/how-nightowl-for-mac-added-a-botnet-1850740785">story</a> of an Apple Macintosh app that went rogue. Basically, it was a good app until one particular update&#8230;when it went bad.</p>
<blockquote><p>With more official macOS features added in 2021 that enabled the &#8220;Night Shift&#8221; dark mode, the NightOwl app was left forlorn and forgotten on many older Macs. Few of those supposed tens of thousands of users likely noticed when the app they ran in the background of their older Macs was bought by another company, nor when earlier this year that company silently updated the dark mode app so that it hijacked their machines in order to send their IP data through a server network of affected computers, AKA a botnet...</p></blockquote>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Airbnb, Cybercriminals Find a Comfortable Home for Fraud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/airbnb-cybercriminals-comfortable-home-fraud</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/airbnb-cybercriminals-comfortable-home-fraud"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T13:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The popular travel rental site is an ideal destination for cybercrooks bent on taking over accounts and bookings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Juniper Networks Releases Security Advisory for Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved]]></title>
        <id>/node/18708</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/08/30/juniper-networks-releases-security-advisory-junos-os-and-junos-os-evolved"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Juniper Networks has released a security advisory to address a vulnerability for Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved. A cyber threat actor could exploit this vulnerability to cause a denial-of-service condition.
CISA encourages users and administrators to review Juniper’s Support Portal and apply the necessary update.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VMware Releases Security Updates for Aria Operations for Networks]]></title>
        <id>/node/18709</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/08/30/vmware-releases-security-updates-aria-operations-networks"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VMware has released security updates to address multiple vulnerabilities in Aria Operations for Networks. A cyber threat actor can exploit one of these vulnerabilities to take control of an affected system.
CISA encourages users and administrators to review VMware Security Advisory VMSA-2023-0018 and apply the necessary updates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Prevent ChatGPT From Stealing Your Content & Traffic]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/how-to-prevent-chatgpt-from-stealing.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/how-to-prevent-chatgpt-from-stealing.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T11:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT and similar large language models (LLMs) have added further complexity to the ever-growing online threat landscape. Cybercriminals no longer need advanced coding skills to execute fraud and other damaging attacks against online businesses and customers, thanks to bots-as-a-service, residential proxies, CAPTCHA farms, and other easily accessible tools. 
Now, the latest technology damaging]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malicious npm Packages Aim to Target Developers for Source Code Theft]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/malicious-npm-packages-aim-to-target.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/malicious-npm-packages-aim-to-target.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T11:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An unknown threat actor is leveraging malicious npm packages to target developers with an aim to steal source code and configuration files from victim machines, a sign of how threats lurk consistently in open-source repositories.
"The threat actor behind this campaign has been linked to malicious activity dating back to 2021," software supply chain security firm Checkmarx said in a report shared]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alert: Juniper Firewalls, Openfire, and Apache RocketMQ Under Attack from New Exploits]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/alert-juniper-firewalls-openfire-and.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/alert-juniper-firewalls-openfire-and.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently disclosed security flaws impacting Juniper firewalls, Openfire, and Apache RocketMQ servers have come under active exploitation in the wild, according to multiple reports.
The Shadowserver Foundation said that it's "seeing exploitation attempts from multiple IPs for Juniper J-Web CVE-2023-36844 (& friends) targeting /webauth_operation.php endpoint," the same day a proof-of-concept (PoC)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Vulnerability Alert: VMware Aria Operations Networks at Risk from Remote Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/critical-vulnerability-alert-vmware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/critical-vulnerability-alert-vmware.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T06:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VMware has released software updates to correct two security vulnerabilities in Aria Operations for Networks that could be potentially exploited to bypass authentication and gain remote code execution.
The most severe of the flaws is CVE-2023-34039 (CVSS score: 9.8), which relates to a case of authentication bypass arising as a result of a lack of unique cryptographic key generation.
"A]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI Dismantles QakBot Malware, Frees 700,000 Computers, Seizes $8.6 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/fbi-dismantles-qakbot-malware-frees.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/fbi-dismantles-qakbot-malware-frees.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-30T04:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A coordinated law enforcement effort codenamed Operation Duck Hunt has felled QakBot, a notorious Windows malware family that's estimated to have compromised over 700,000 computers globally and facilitated financial fraud as well as ransomware.
To that end, the U.S. Justice Department (DoJ) said the malware is "being deleted from victim computers, preventing it from doing any more harm," adding]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Ways AI Can Revolutionize Digital Forensics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/6-ways-ai-can-revolutionize-digital-forensics</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/6-ways-ai-can-revolutionize-digital-forensics"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T22:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence tools can automate the analysis of logs, video, and other important but tedious aspects of investigations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shashidhar Angadi, Chief Technology Officer, Exterro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everest Group Research: C-Suite Must Recognize Critical Difference Between Cybersecurity and Cyber Resilience]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/everest-group-research-c-suite-must-recognize-critical-difference-between-cybersecurity-and-cyber-resilience</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/everest-group-research-c-suite-must-recognize-critical-difference-between-cybersecurity-and-cyber-resilience"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T21:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SPHERE Appoints Former Johnson & Johnson CISO Marene Allison to Board of Directors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/careers-and-people/sphere-appoints-former-johnson-johnson-ciso-marene-allison-to-board-of-directors</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/careers-and-people/sphere-appoints-former-johnson-johnson-ciso-marene-allison-to-board-of-directors"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T21:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unpatched Citrix NetScaler Devices Targeted by Ransomware Group FIN8]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/unpatched-citrix-devices-targeted-by-ransomware-group-fin8</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/unpatched-citrix-devices-targeted-by-ransomware-group-fin8"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T21:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Citrix issued a patch for the critical remote code execution bug in July for its NetScaler devices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delinea Research Reveals a Cyber Insurance Gap]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/delinea-research-reveals-a-cyber-insurance-gap</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/delinea-research-reveals-a-cyber-insurance-gap"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T21:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PurFoods Mom's Meals Reports Data Breach Exposing Social Security Numbers of Over 1.2 Million Consumers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/purfoods-mom-s-meals-reports-data-breach-exposing-social-security-numbers-of-over-1-2-million-consumers</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/purfoods-mom-s-meals-reports-data-breach-exposing-social-security-numbers-of-over-1-2-million-consumers"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T21:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sprawling Qakbot Malware Takedown Spans 700,000 Infected Machines]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/sprawling-qakbot-malware-takedown-spans-700-000-infected-machines</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/sprawling-qakbot-malware-takedown-spans-700-000-infected-machines"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T20:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Operation Duck Hunt" is not likely to eliminate the initial access botnet forever, but the proactive removal of the malware from victim machines by law enforcement is one of the largest and most significant efforts of its kind.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tara Seals, Managing Editor, News, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MOVEit Breach Shows Us SQL Injections Are Still Our Achilles' Heel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge-articles/moveit-was-a-sql-injection-accident-waiting-to-happen</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge-articles/moveit-was-a-sql-injection-accident-waiting-to-happen"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T20:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SQL injection and its ilk will stop being "a thing" only after organizations focus on security by construction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkhar Arasaratnam, General Manager, Open Source Security Foundation (OpenSSF)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Cripples China's Signature 'Spamouflage' Influence Op]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/meta-vs-china-social-giant-cripples-chinese-disinformation-apt</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/meta-vs-china-social-giant-cripples-chinese-disinformation-apt"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T20:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The social media giant is taking on Dragonbridge, the "largest known cross-platform covert influence operation in the world."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Identification and Disruption of QakBot Infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>/node/18705</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/cybersecurity-advisories/aa23-242a"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T19:28:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUMMARY
The Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) and Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) are releasing this joint Cybersecurity Advisory (CSA) to disseminate QakBot infrastructure indicators of compromise (IOCs) identified through FBI investigations as of August 2023. On August 25, FBI and international partners executed a coordinated operation to disrupt QakBot infrastructure worldwide. Disruption operations targeting QakBot infrastructure resulted in the botnet takeover, which severed the connection between victim computers and QakBot command and control (C2) servers. The FBI is working closely with industry partners to share information about the malware to maximize detection, remediation, and prevention measures for network defenders.
CISA and FBI encourage organiz…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South African Department of Defence Denies Stolen Data Claims]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/south-african-department-of-defence-denies-stolen-data-claims</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/south-african-department-of-defence-denies-stolen-data-claims"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T18:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attackers leaked 1.6TB of stolen data, which government officials dismissed as "fake news."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Raywood, Senior Editor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Somalia Orders ISPs to Block Telegram and TikTok]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/somalia-orders-isps-to-block-access-to-telegram-and-tiktok</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/somalia-orders-isps-to-block-access-to-telegram-and-tiktok"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T18:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Officials said the apps were used to "spread horrific content and misinformation to the public."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Raywood, Senior Editor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rackspace Faces Massive Cleanup Costs After Ransomware Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/remote-workforce/rackspace-massive-cleanup-costs-ransomware-attack</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/remote-workforce/rackspace-massive-cleanup-costs-ransomware-attack"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T17:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eight months after the cyberattack, the cloud hosting services company's remediation costs top $10 million as it tries to repair the damage caused by the Play ransomware gang.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Addressing Cybersecurity's Talent Shortage & Its Impact on CISOs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/addressing-cybersecurity-talent-shortage-its-impact-on-cisos</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/addressing-cybersecurity-talent-shortage-its-impact-on-cisos"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CISOs need to educate all arms of the business on security best practices so it becomes part of the business culture, thus expanding who's keeping watch. Automating routine tasks will help scale security.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Scott, CISO, Immuta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Hacking Group Exploits Barracuda Zero-Day to Target Government, Military, and Telecom]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/chinese-hacking-group-exploits.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/chinese-hacking-group-exploits.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T14:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A suspected Chinese-nexus hacking group exploited a recently disclosed zero-day flaw in Barracuda Networks Email Security Gateway (ESG) appliances to breach government, military, defense and aerospace, high-tech industry, and telecom sectors as part of a global espionage campaign.
Mandiant, which is tracking the activity under the name UNC4841, described the threat actor as "highly responsive to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DarkGate Malware Activity Spikes as Developer Rents Out Malware to Affiliates]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/darkgate-malware-activity-spikes-as.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/darkgate-malware-activity-spikes-as.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T14:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new malspam campaign has been observed deploying an off-the-shelf malware called DarkGate.
"The current spike in DarkGate malware activity is plausible given the fact that the developer of the malware has recently started to rent out the malware to a limited number of affiliates," Telekom Security said in a report published last week.
The latest report builds on recent findings from security]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kroll's Crypto Breach Highlights SIM-Swapping Risk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/remote-workforce/kroll-cryoto-breach-sim-swapping-risk</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/remote-workforce/kroll-cryoto-breach-sim-swapping-risk"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T14:28:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Information was exposed on hundreds of crypto-related bankruptcy claimants in proceedings involving FTX, Genesis, and BlockFI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here's What Your Breach Response Plan Might Be Missing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/what-your-breach-response-plan-might-be-missing</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/what-your-breach-response-plan-might-be-missing"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The best way to withstand a data breach is to be prepared. Here are four elements that are easily overlooked in breach response plans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Cusimano,  Technical Director, Object First</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Survey Provides Takeaways for Security Pros to Operationalize their Remediation Life Cycle]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/survey-provides-takeaways-for-security.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/survey-provides-takeaways-for-security.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T11:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ask any security professional and they’ll tell you that remediating risks from various siloed security scanning tools requires a tedious and labor-intensive series of steps focused on deduplication, prioritization, and routing of issues to an appropriate “fixer” somewhere in the organization. This burden on already resource-strapped security teams is an efficiency killer. 
A new study,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Identity Theft from 1965 Uncovered through Face Recognition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/08/identity-theft-from-1965-uncovered-through-face-recognition.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/08/identity-theft-from-1965-uncovered-through-face-recognition.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T11:03:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Interesting <a href="https://apnews.com/article/maine-brothers-assumed-identity-facial-recognition-technology-cf99404df550dcff9d20042b1f91dad2">story</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>Napoleon Gonzalez, of Etna, assumed the identity of his brother in 1965, a quarter century after his sibling&#8217;s death as an infant, and used the stolen identity to obtain Social Security benefits under both identities, multiple passports and state identification cards, law enforcement officials said.</p>
<p>[&#8230;]</p>
<p>A new investigation was launched in 2020 after facial identification software indicated Gonzalez&#8217;s face was on two state identification cards.</p>
<p>The facial recognition technology is used by the Maine Bureau of Motor Vehicles to ensure no one obtains multiple credentials or credentials under someone else&#8217;s name, said Emily Cook, spokesperson for the secretary of state&#8217;s office...</p></blockquote>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Citrix NetScaler Alert: Ransomware Hackers Exploiting Critical Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/citrix-netscaler-alert-ransomware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/citrix-netscaler-alert-ransomware.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T09:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unpatched Citrix NetScaler systems exposed to the internet are being targeted by unknown threat actors in what's suspected to be a ransomware attack.
Cybersecurity company Sophos is tracking the activity cluster under the moniker STAC4663.
Attack chains involve the exploitation of CVE-2023-3519, a critical code injection vulnerability impacting NetScaler ADC and Gateway servers that could]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phishing-as-a-Service Gets Smarter: Microsoft Sounds Alarm on AiTM Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/phishing-as-service-gets-smarter.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/phishing-as-service-gets-smarter.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T05:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is warning of an increase in adversary-in-the-middle (AiTM) phishing techniques, which are being propagated as part of the phishing-as-a-service (PhaaS) cybercrime model.
In addition to an uptick in AiTM-capable PhaaS platforms, the tech giant noted that existing phishing services like PerSwaysion are incorporating AiTM capabilities.
"This development in the PhaaS ecosystem enables]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Motherboard Mishaps Undermine Trust, Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/motherboard-mishaps-undermine-trust-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/motherboard-mishaps-undermine-trust-security"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T21:15:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MSI and Microsoft warn about new Windows Preview blue screens on some motherboards, the latest mishap to raise questions over the reliability of hardware and firmware.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Lemos, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Honeywell to Acquire SCADAfence, Strengthening Its Cybersecurity Software Portfolio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/ics-ot/honeywell-to-acquire-scadafence-strengthening-its-cybersecurity-software-portfolio</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/ics-ot/honeywell-to-acquire-scadafence-strengthening-its-cybersecurity-software-portfolio"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T21:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BreachLock Intelligence Report Reveals Critical Insights From Thousands of Penetration Tests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/breachlock-penetration-testing-intelligence-report-2023-reveals-critical-insights-from-thousands-of-penetration-tests</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/breachlock-penetration-testing-intelligence-report-2023-reveals-critical-insights-from-thousands-of-penetration-tests"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T21:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybercriminals Harness Leaked LockBit Builder in Wave of New Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/remote-workforce/cybercriminals-harness-leaked-lockbit-builder-new-attacks</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/remote-workforce/cybercriminals-harness-leaked-lockbit-builder-new-attacks"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T20:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enterprising, or simply lazy, cybercriminals are using Lockbit v3 to cut corners on ransomware.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Considerations for Reducing Risk When Migrating to the Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/google-cloud-security/considerations-for-reducing-risk-when-migrating-to-the-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/google-cloud-security/considerations-for-reducing-risk-when-migrating-to-the-cloud"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Proper planning is an essential part of reducing security and compliance risks before, during, and after a migration to a new cloud environment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rob Sadowski, Director, Trust &amp; Security Product Marketing for Google Cloud at Google</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Financial Firms Breached in MOVEit Cyberattacks Now Face Lawsuits]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/financial-firms-breached-in-moveit-cyberattacks-now-face-lawsuits</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/financial-firms-breached-in-moveit-cyberattacks-now-face-lawsuits"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T19:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TD Ameritrade, Charles Schwab named in new class action data breach lawsuit, following last week's filing against Prudential.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Becky Bracken, Editor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[London Police Warned to Stay Vigilant Amid Major Data Breach]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/london-police-warned-to-stay-vigilant-amid-major-data-breach</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/london-police-warned-to-stay-vigilant-amid-major-data-breach"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T17:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers hit a third-party contractor's IT systems, but they didn't steal any addresses or financial details, officials say.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Ways to Prepare for Google's 90-Day TLS Certificate Expiration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/5-ways-to-prepare-google-90-day-tls-certificate-expiration</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/5-ways-to-prepare-google-90-day-tls-certificate-expiration"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With bad guys frequently upping their game, security can't leave these protections to a once-a-year upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murali Palanisamy, Chief Solutions Officer, AppViewX</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Experts Uncover How Cybercriminals Could Exploit Microsoft Entra ID for Elevated Privilege]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/experts-uncover-how-cybercriminals.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/experts-uncover-how-cybercriminals.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T16:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a case of privilege escalation associated with a Microsoft Entra ID (formerly Azure Active Directory) application by taking advantage of an abandoned reply URL.
"An attacker could leverage this abandoned URL to redirect authorization codes to themselves, exchanging the ill-gotten authorization codes for access tokens," Secureworks Counter Threat Unit (]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developers Beware: Malicious Rust Libraries Caught Transmitting OS Info to Telegram Channel]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/developers-beware-malicious-rust.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/developers-beware-malicious-rust.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In yet another sign that developers continue to be targets of software supply chain attacks, a number of malicious packages have been discovered on the Rust programming language's crate registry.
The libraries, uploaded between August 14 and 16, 2023, were published by a user named "amaperf," Phylum said in a report published last week. The names of the packages, now taken down, are as follows:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Authentication Outage Underscores Why 'Fail Safe' Is Key]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/authentication-outage-highlights-why-fail-safe-is-key</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/authentication-outage-highlights-why-fail-safe-is-key"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T15:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Duo's service outage last week, impacting schools and businesses, highlights how companies should build in resiliency and business continuity into their authentication schemes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Lemos, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Legal Liability for Insecure Software Might Work, but It's Dangerous]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/legal-liability-for-insecure-software-might-work-but-it-s-dangerous</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/legal-liability-for-insecure-software-might-work-but-it-s-dangerous"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imposing government-regulated security requirements on software companies may go too far and create unintended consequences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Williams, CTO, Contrast Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerability Summary for the Week of August 21, 2023]]></title>
        <id>/node/18690</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/bulletins/sb23-240"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T12:07:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[High Vulnerabilities

Primary
Description
Published
CVSS Score
Source & Patch Info

qemu -- qemu
The hardware emulation in the of_dpa_cmd_add_l2_flood of rocker device model in QEMU, as used in 7.0.0 and earlier, allows remote attackers to crash the host qemu and potentially execute code on the host via execute a malformed program in the guest OS.
2023-08-22
10
CVE-2022-36648
MISC

c-ares -- c-ares
Buffer overflow vulnerability in c-ares before 1_16_1 thru 1_17_0 via function ares_parse_soa_reply in ares_parse_soa_reply.c.
2023-08-22
9.8
CVE-2020-22217
MISC

flac_project -- flac
Buffer Overflow vulnerability in function bitwriter_grow_ in flac before 1.4.0 allows remote attackers to run arbitrary code via crafted input to the encoder.
2023-08-22
9.8
CVE-2020-22219
MISC

leeco -- letv_x43_f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cyberattacks Targeting E-commerce Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/cyberattacks-targeting-e-commerce.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/cyberattacks-targeting-e-commerce.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T11:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cyber attacks on e-commerce applications are a common trend in 2023 as e-commerce businesses become more omnichannel, they build and deploy increasingly more API interfaces, with threat actors constantly exploring more ways to exploit vulnerabilities. This is why regular testing and ongoing monitoring are necessary to fully protect web applications, identifying weaknesses so they can be]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remotely Stopping Polish Trains]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/08/remotely-stopping-polish-trains.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/08/remotely-stopping-polish-trains.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T11:05:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Turns out that it&#8217;s <a href="https://www.wired.com/story/poland-train-radio-stop-attack/">easy</a> to broadcast radio commands that force Polish trains to stop:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8230;the saboteurs appear to have sent simple so-called &#8220;radio-stop&#8221; commands via radio frequency to the trains they targeted. Because the trains use a radio system that lacks encryption or authentication for those commands, Olejnik says, anyone with as little as $30 of off-the-shelf radio equipment can broadcast the command to a Polish train­&#8212;sending a series of three acoustic tones at a 150.100 megahertz frequency­&#8212;and trigger their emergency stop function...</p></blockquote>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Better SaaS Security Goes Beyond Procurement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/risk/better-saas-security-goes-beyond-procurement</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/risk/better-saas-security-goes-beyond-procurement"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The impulse to achieve strong SaaS security adherence through strict gatekeeping during procurement fails to reduce the risk that matters most.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malware Unleashed: Public Sector Hit in Sudden Surge, Reveals New Research]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/malware-unleashed-public-sector-hit-in-sudden-surge-reveals-new-research</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/malware-unleashed-public-sector-hit-in-sudden-surge-reveals-new-research"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Report unmasks recent cybersecurity challenges for governments, healthcare, financial services, and vital infrastructure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KmsdBot Malware Gets an Upgrade: Now Targets IoT Devices with Enhanced Capabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/kmsdbot-malware-gets-upgrade-now.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/kmsdbot-malware-gets-upgrade-now.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T05:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An updated version of a botnet malware called KmsdBot is now targeting Internet of Things (IoT) devices, simultaneously branching out its capabilities and the attack surface.
"The binary now includes support for Telnet scanning and support for more CPU architectures," Akamai security researcher Larry W. Cashdollar said in an analysis published this month.

The latest iteration,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LockBit 3.0 Ransomware Builder Leak Gives Rise to Hundreds of New Variants]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/lockbit-30-ransomware-builder-leak.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/lockbit-30-ransomware-builder-leak.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-26T10:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The leak of the LockBit 3.0 ransomware builder last year has led to threat actors abusing the tool to spawn new variants.
Russian cybersecurity company Kaspersky said it detected a ransomware intrusion that deployed a version of LockBit but with a markedly different ransom demand procedure.
"The attacker behind this incident decided to use a different ransom note with a headline related to a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kroll Suffers Data Breach: Employee Falls Victim to SIM Swapping Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/kroll-suffers-data-breach-employee.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/kroll-suffers-data-breach-employee.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-26T04:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Risk and financial advisory solutions provider Kroll on Friday disclosed that one of its employees fell victim to a "highly sophisticated" SIM swapping attack.
The incident, which took place on August 19, 2023, targeted the employee's T-Mobile account, the company said.
"Specifically, T-Mobile, without any authority from or contact with Kroll or its employee, transferred that employee's phone]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vendors Training AI With Customer Data Is an Enterprise Risk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge/vendors-training-ai-customer-data-enterprise-risk</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge/vendors-training-ai-customer-data-enterprise-risk"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Zoom has scrapped plans to harvest customer content for use in its AI and ML models, the incident should raise concerns for enterprises and consumers alike.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friday Squid Blogging: China’s Squid Fishing Ban Ineffective]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/08/friday-squid-blogging-chinas-squid-fishing-ban-ineffective.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/08/friday-squid-blogging-chinas-squid-fishing-ban-ineffective.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T21:06:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>China <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2023/aug/10/china-moratoriums-on-fishing-do-nothing-to-protect-squid">imposed</a> a &#8220;pilot program banning fishing in parts of the south-west Atlantic Ocean from July to October, and parts of the eastern Pacific Ocean from September to December.&#8221; However, the conservation group Oceana analyzed the data and figured out that the Chinese weren&#8217;t fishing in those areas in those months, anyway.</p>
<p>&#60;</p>
<p>blockquote&#62;In the south-west Atlantic moratorium area, Oceana found there had been no fishing conducted by Chinese fleets in the same time period in 2019. Between 1,800 and 8,500 fishing hours were detected in the zone in each of the five years to 2019. In the eastern Pacific zone, China&#8217;s fishing fleet appeared to fish only 38 hours in the year before the ban&#8217;s introduction...</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genworth Financial Under Investigation for Data Breach]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/-genworth-financial-under-investigation-for-data-breach</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/-genworth-financial-under-investigation-for-data-breach"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T20:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China Unleashes Flax Typhoon APT to Live Off the Land, Microsoft Warns]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/china-unleashes-flax-typhoon-apt-live-off-land-microsoft-warns</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/china-unleashes-flax-typhoon-apt-live-off-land-microsoft-warns"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T19:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cyber-espionage group has created a stealthy, hard-to-mitigate network of persistent access across a range of organizations, but the endgame is unclear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tara Seals, Managing Editor, News, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luna Grabber Malware Targets Roblox Gaming Devs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/luna-grabber-malware-targets-roblox-gaming-devs</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/luna-grabber-malware-targets-roblox-gaming-devs"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T18:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roblox gaming developers are lured in by a package that claims to create useful scripts to interact with the Roblox website, for example by “promot(ing) users, shout events, and so on, or to create Discord utiltiies (sic) to manage their community.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Whiffy Recon' Malware Transmits Device Location Every 60 Seconds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/whiffy-recon-malware-transmits-device-location-every-60-seconds</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/whiffy-recon-malware-transmits-device-location-every-60-seconds"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T16:34:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deployed by the infamous SmokeLoader botnet, the location-tracking malware could be used for a host of follow-on cyberattacks or even physical targeting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Eddy, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Bias in AI Algorithms a Threat to Cloud Security?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/is-bias-in-ai-algorithms-a-threat-to-cloud-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/is-bias-in-ai-algorithms-a-threat-to-cloud-security"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using AI for threat detection and response is essential — but it can't replace human intelligence, expertise, and intuition.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Shachar, Director of AI and Research, Skyhawk Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two LAPSUS$ Hackers Convicted in London Court for High-Profile Tech Firm Hacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/two-lapsus-hackers-convicted-in-london.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/two-lapsus-hackers-convicted-in-london.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T13:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two U.K. teenagers have been convicted by a jury in London for being part of the notorious LAPSUS$ (aka Slippy Spider) transnational gang and for orchestrating a series of brazen, high-profile hacks against major tech firms and demanding a ransom in exchange for not leaking the stolen information.
This includes Arion Kurtaj (aka White, Breachbase, WhiteDoxbin, and TeaPotUberHacker), an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NIST Publishes First Draft Standards for Post-Quantum Cryptography]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/nist-publishes-first-draft-standards-for-post-quantum-cryptography</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/nist-publishes-first-draft-standards-for-post-quantum-cryptography"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T12:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Publication of the first draft PQC standards opens a 90-day period for public comment and paves the way for interoperability testing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey Schwartz, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn How Your Business Data Can Amplify Your AI/ML Threat Detection Capabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/learn-how-your-business-data-can.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/learn-how-your-business-data-can.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T11:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's digital landscape, your business data is more than just numbers—it's a powerhouse. Imagine leveraging this data not only for profit but also for enhanced AI and Machine Learning (ML) threat detection.
For companies like Comcast, this isn't a dream. It's reality.
Your business comprehends its risks, vulnerabilities, and the unique environment in which it operates. No generic,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacking Food Labeling Laws]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/08/hacking-food-labeling-laws.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/08/hacking-food-labeling-laws.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T11:03:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This <a href="https://www.statnews.com/2023/08/21/kelloggs-mexico-nutrition-label/">article</a> talks about new Mexican laws about food labeling, and the lengths to which food manufacturers are going to ensure that they are not effective. There are the typical high-pressure lobbying tactics and lawsuits. But there&#8217;s also examples of companies hacking the laws:</p>
<blockquote><p>Companies like Coca-Cola and Kraft Heinz have begun designing their products so that their packages don&#8217;t have a true front or back, but rather two nearly identical labels&#8212;except for the fact that only one side has the required warning. As a result, supermarket clerks often place the products with the warning facing inward, effectively hiding it...</p></blockquote>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cerby Announces $17M in Series A Funding to Secure Nonstandard Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/cerby-announces-17m-in-series-a-funding-to-secure-nonstandard-applications</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/cerby-announces-17m-in-series-a-funding-to-secure-nonstandard-applications"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T23:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Insight Releases H1 2023 Report]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/critical-insight-releases-h1-2023-report</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/critical-insight-releases-h1-2023-report"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T23:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Black Hat USA 2023 Closes on Record-Breaking Event in Las Vegas]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge/black-hat-usa-2023-closes-on-record-breaking-event-in-las-vega</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge/black-hat-usa-2023-closes-on-record-breaking-event-in-las-vega"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T21:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malwarebytes Announces Acquisition of Online Privacy Company Cyrus]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/malwarebytes-announces-acquisition-of-online-privacy-company-cyrus</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/malwarebytes-announces-acquisition-of-online-privacy-company-cyrus"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T21:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cypago Raises $13M and Unveils its Cyber GRC Automation (CGA) Platform to Simplify GRC Processes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/risk/cypago-raises-13m-and-unveils-its-cyber-grc-automation-cga-platform-to-simplify-grc-processes</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/risk/cypago-raises-13m-and-unveils-its-cyber-grc-automation-cga-platform-to-simplify-grc-processes"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T20:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kyndryl and Cisco Expand Partnership Focusing on Cyber Resilience]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/kyndryl-and-cisco-expand-partnership-focusing-on-cyber-resilience</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/kyndryl-and-cisco-expand-partnership-focusing-on-cyber-resilience"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T20:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Space Industry More Prone to Foreign Espionage, US Agencies Warn]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/us-space-industry-more-prone-to-foreign-espionage-us-agencies-warn</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/us-space-industry-more-prone-to-foreign-espionage-us-agencies-warn"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Foreign intelligence entities have the US space industry in their sights, posing serious threats to US national security, multiple federal agencies say.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware With an Identity Crisis Targets Small Businesses, Individuals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/ransomware-with-an-identity-crisis-targets-small-businesses-individuals</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/ransomware-with-an-identity-crisis-targets-small-businesses-individuals"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T18:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TZW is the latest version of Adhubllka, which has been active since 2019 but has gone largely unreported due to its lower ransom demands.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Montalbano, Contributor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[eBay Users Beware Russian 'Telekopye' Telegram Phishing Bot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/ebay-users-russian-telekopye-telegram-phishing-bot</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/ebay-users-russian-telekopye-telegram-phishing-bot"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T17:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to a simple Telegram bot that democratizes phishing, ordinary Russians can conduct full-fledged phishing attacks with zero technical know-how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerability Summary for the Week of August 14, 2023]]></title>
        <id>/node/18651</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/bulletins/sb23-233"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T11:27:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[High Vulnerabilities

Primary
Description
Published
CVSS Score
Source & Patch Info

foldingathome -- client_advanced_control
An issue was discovered in FoldingAtHome Client Advanced Control GUI before commit 9b619ae64443997948a36dda01b420578de1af77, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via crafted payload to function parse_message in file Connection.py.
2023-08-11
9.8
CVE-2020-27544
MISC

sourcecodester -- school_faculty_scheduling_system
SQL Injection vulnerability in oretnom23 School Faculty Scheduling System version 1.0, allows remote attacker to execute arbitrary code, escalate privilieges, and gain sensitive information via crafted payload to id parameter in manage_user.php.
2023-08-11
9.8
CVE-2020-36034
MISC
MISC
MISC

bloofox -- bloofoxcms
File Upload vulnerability in b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MAR-10459736.r1.v1 WHIRLPOOL Backdoor]]></title>
        <id>/node/18646</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/analysis-reports/ar23-230a"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T13:38:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notification
This report is provided "as is" for informational purposes only. The Department of Homeland Security (DHS) does not provide any warranties of any kind regarding any information contained herein. The DHS does not endorse any commercial product or service referenced in this bulletin or otherwise.
This document is marked TLP:CLEAR--Recipients may share this information without restriction. Sources may use TLP:CLEAR when information carries minimal or no foreseeable risk of misuse, in accordance with applicable rules and procedures for public release. Subject to standard copyright rules, TLP:CLEAR information may be shared without restriction. For more information on the Traffic Light Protocol (TLP), see http://www.cisa.gov/tlp.
Summary
Description
CISA obtained a variant of the W…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerability Summary for the Week of August 7, 2023]]></title>
        <id>/node/18623</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/bulletins/sb23-226"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T11:56:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[High Vulnerabilities

Primary
Description
Published
CVSS Score
Source & Patch Info


			phoenixcontact -- wp_6xxx_series
In PHOENIX CONTACTs WP 6xxx series web panels in versions prior to 4.0.10 a remote attacker with low privileges may use an attribute of a specific HTTP POST request releated to date/time operations to gain full access to the device.
2023-08-08
9.9
CVE-2023-3572
MISC

qualcomm_inc. -- snapdragon
Memory corruption due to buffer copy without checking size of input in Audio while voice call with EVS vocoder.
2023-08-08
9.8
CVE-2022-40510
MISC

microsoft -- exchange_server
Microsoft Exchange Server Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability
2023-08-08
9.8
CVE-2023-21709
MISC

joomla -- joomla
Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulne…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>