<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://ehsanedalat.github.io/securitynews/index.html</id>
    <title>News | S&amp;P Homepage</title>
    <updated>2023-08-26T01:03:00.690Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://ehsanedalat.github.io/securitynews/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://ehsanedalat.github.io/securitynews/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friday Squid Blogging: China’s Squid Fishing Ban Ineffective]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/08/friday-squid-blogging-chinas-squid-fishing-ban-ineffective.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/08/friday-squid-blogging-chinas-squid-fishing-ban-ineffective.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T21:06:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>China <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2023/aug/10/china-moratoriums-on-fishing-do-nothing-to-protect-squid">imposed</a> a &#8220;pilot program banning fishing in parts of the south-west Atlantic Ocean from July to October, and parts of the eastern Pacific Ocean from September to December.&#8221; However, the conservation group Oceana analyzed the data and figured out that the Chinese weren&#8217;t fishing in those areas in those months, anyway.</p>
<p>&#60;</p>
<p>blockquote&#62;In the south-west Atlantic moratorium area, Oceana found there had been no fishing conducted by Chinese fleets in the same time period in 2019. Between 1,800 and 8,500 fishing hours were detected in the zone in each of the five years to 2019. In the eastern Pacific zone, China&#8217;s fishing fleet appeared to fish only 38 hours in the year before the ban&#8217;s introduction...</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genworth Financial Under Investigation for Data Breach]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/-genworth-financial-under-investigation-for-data-breach</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/-genworth-financial-under-investigation-for-data-breach"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T20:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China Unleashes Flax Typhoon APT to Live Off the Land, Microsoft Warns]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/china-unleashes-flax-typhoon-apt-live-off-land-microsoft-warns</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/china-unleashes-flax-typhoon-apt-live-off-land-microsoft-warns"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T19:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cyber-espionage group has created a stealthy, hard-to-mitigate network of persistent access across a range of organizations, but the endgame is unclear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tara Seals, Managing Editor, News, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luna Grabber Malware Targets Roblox Gaming Devs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/luna-grabber-malware-targets-roblox-gaming-devs</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/luna-grabber-malware-targets-roblox-gaming-devs"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T18:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roblox gaming developers are lured in by a package that claims to create useful scripts to interact with the Roblox website, for example by “promot(ing) users, shout events, and so on, or to create Discord utiltiies (sic) to manage their community.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Whiffy Recon' Malware Transmits Device Location Every 60 Seconds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/whiffy-recon-malware-transmits-device-location-every-60-seconds</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/whiffy-recon-malware-transmits-device-location-every-60-seconds"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T16:34:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deployed by the infamous SmokeLoader botnet, the location-tracking malware could be used for a host of follow-on cyberattacks or even physical targeting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Eddy, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Other News: Africa Cybercrime Crackdown, Unpatched macOS Flaw, Investor Disclosures]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34762</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/in-other-news-africa-cybercrime-crackdown-unpatched-macos-flaw-investor-disclosures/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T14:24:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Weekly cybersecurity news roundup that provides a summary of noteworthy stories that might have slipped under the radar for the week of August 21, 2023.
The post In Other News: Africa Cybercrime Crackdown, Unpatched macOS Flaw, Investor Disclosures appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eduard Kovacs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Bias in AI Algorithms a Threat to Cloud Security?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/is-bias-in-ai-algorithms-a-threat-to-cloud-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/is-bias-in-ai-algorithms-a-threat-to-cloud-security"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using AI for threat detection and response is essential — but it can't replace human intelligence, expertise, and intuition.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Shachar, Director of AI and Research, Skyhawk Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two LAPSUS$ Hackers Convicted in London Court for High-Profile Tech Firm Hacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/two-lapsus-hackers-convicted-in-london.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/two-lapsus-hackers-convicted-in-london.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T13:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two U.K. teenagers have been convicted by a jury in London for being part of the notorious LAPSUS$ transnational gang and for orchestrating a series of brazen, high-profile hacks against major tech firms and demanding a ransom in exchange for not leaking the stolen information.
This includes Arion Kurtaj (aka White, Breachbase, WhiteDoxbin, and TeaPotUberHacker), an 18-year-old from Oxford, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NIST Publishes First Draft Standards for Post-Quantum Cryptography]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/nist-publishes-first-draft-standards-for-post-quantum-cryptography</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/nist-publishes-first-draft-standards-for-post-quantum-cryptography"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T12:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Publication of the first draft PQC standards opens a 90-day period for public comment and paves the way for interoperability testing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey Schwartz, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean APT Hacks Internet Infrastructure Provider via ManageEngine Flaw]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34761</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/north-korean-apt-hacks-internet-infrastructure-provider-via-manageengine-flaw/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T12:47:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[North Korea-linked Lazarus Group exploited a ManageEngine vulnerability to compromise an internet backbone infrastructure provider.
The post North Korean APT Hacks Internet Infrastructure Provider via ManageEngine Flaw appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Arghire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cypago Raises $13 Million for GRC Automation Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34760</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/cypago-raises-13-million-for-grc-automation-platform/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T12:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Israeli startup Cypago raises $13 million in funding and launches a governance, risk management and compliance (GRC) automation platform.
The post Cypago Raises $13 Million for GRC Automation Platform  appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Arghire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA’s VDP Platform 2022 Annual Report Showcases Success]]></title>
        <id>/node/18679</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/08/25/cisas-vdp-platform-2022-annual-report-showcases-success"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, the Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) released its inaugural Vulnerability Disclosure Policy (VDP) Platform 2022 Annual Report, highlighting the service’s progress supporting vulnerability awareness and remediation across the Federal Civilian Executive Branch (FCEB). This report showcases how agencies have used the VDP Platform—launched in July 2021—to safeguard the FCEB and support risk reduction. The VDP platform gives federal agencies a single, user-friendly interface to intake vulnerability information and to collaborate with the public researcher community for vulnerability awareness and remediation.
CISA urges FCEB agencies to review the VDP Platform 2022 Annual Report and encourages use of the platform to promote good-faith security research if they are not already doing so. By promoting an agency’s VDP to the public security researcher community, the platform benefits users by harnessing researchers’ expertise to search for and detect vulnerabilities that traditional scanning technology might not find.
CISA is actively seeking to enhance future collaborations with the public security researcher community and welcomes participation and partnership.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn How Your Business Data Can Amplify Your AI/ML Threat Detection Capabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/learn-how-your-business-data-can.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/learn-how-your-business-data-can.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T11:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's digital landscape, your business data is more than just numbers—it's a powerhouse. Imagine leveraging this data not only for profit but also for enhanced AI and Machine Learning (ML) threat detection.
For companies like Comcast, this isn't a dream. It's reality.
Your business comprehends its risks, vulnerabilities, and the unique environment in which it operates. No generic,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lawmaker Wants Federal Contractors to Have Vulnerability Disclosure Policies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34758</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/lawmaker-wants-federal-contractors-to-have-vulnerability-disclosure-policies/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T11:33:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Congresswoman Nancy Mace has introduced a bill that would require federal contractors to have a Vulnerability Disclosure Policy (VDP).
The post Lawmaker Wants Federal Contractors to Have Vulnerability Disclosure Policies  appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eduard Kovacs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europe is Cracking Down on Big Tech. This Is What Will Change When You Sign On]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34757</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/europe-is-cracking-down-on-big-tech-this-is-what-will-change-when-you-sign-on/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T11:33:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Digital Services Act aims to protect European users when it comes to privacy, transparency and removal of harmful or illegal content.
The post Europe is Cracking Down on Big Tech. This Is What Will Change When You Sign On appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Associated Press</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacking Food Labeling Laws]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/08/hacking-food-labeling-laws.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/08/hacking-food-labeling-laws.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T11:03:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This <a href="https://www.statnews.com/2023/08/21/kelloggs-mexico-nutrition-label/">article</a> talks about new Mexican laws about food labeling, and the lengths to which food manufacturers are going to ensure that they are not effective. There are the typical high-pressure lobbying tactics and lawsuits. But there&#8217;s also examples of companies hacking the laws:</p>
<blockquote><p>Companies like Coca-Cola and Kraft Heinz have begun designing their products so that their packages don&#8217;t have a true front or back, but rather two nearly identical labels&#8212;except for the fact that only one side has the required warning. As a result, supermarket clerks often place the products with the warning facing inward, effectively hiding it...</p></blockquote>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Navigating Legacy Infrastructure: A CISO's Actionable Strategy for Success]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/navigating-legacy-infrastructure-cisos.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/navigating-legacy-infrastructure-cisos.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T10:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every company has some level of tech debt. Unless you’re a brand new start-up, you most likely have a patchwork of solutions that have been implemented throughout the years, often under various leadership teams with different priorities and goals. As those technologies age, they can leave your organization vulnerable to cyber threats.
While replacing legacy technologies can be costly, those]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China-Linked Flax Typhoon Cyber Espionage Targets Taiwan's Key Sectors]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/china-linked-flax-typhoon-cyber.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/china-linked-flax-typhoon-cyber.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T10:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A nation-state activity group originating from China has been linked to cyber attacks on dozens of organizations in Taiwan as part of a suspected espionage campaign.
The Microsoft Threat Intelligence team is tracking the activity under the name Flax Typhoon, which is also known as Ethereal Panda.
"Flax Typhoon gains and maintains long-term access to Taiwanese organizations' networks with minimal]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Workspace Introduces New AI-Powered Security Controls]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34756</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/google-workspace-introduces-new-ai-powered-security-controls/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T10:36:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has announced new AI-powered zero trust, digital sovereignty, and threat defense controls for Workspace customers.
The post Google Workspace Introduces New AI-Powered Security Controls appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Arghire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly 1,000 Organizations, 60 Million Individuals Impacted by MOVEit Hack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34755</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/nearly-1000-organizations-60-million-individuals-impacted-by-moveit-hack/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T09:30:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly 1,000 organizations and 60 million individuals are impacted by the MOVEit hack, and the Cl0p ransomware gang is leaking stolen data.
The post Nearly 1,000 Organizations, 60 Million Individuals Impacted by MOVEit Hack appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eduard Kovacs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Urgent FBI Warning: Barracuda Email Gateways Vulnerable Despite Recent Patches]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/urgent-fbi-warning-barracuda-email.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/urgent-fbi-warning-barracuda-email.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T08:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) is warning that Barracuda Networks Email Security Gateway (ESG) appliances patched against a recently disclosed critical flaw continue to be at risk of potential compromise from suspected Chinese hacking groups.
It also deemed the fixes as "ineffective" and that it "continues to observe active intrusions and considers all affected Barracuda ESG]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cerby Announces $17M in Series A Funding to Secure Nonstandard Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/cerby-announces-17m-in-series-a-funding-to-secure-nonstandard-applications</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/cerby-announces-17m-in-series-a-funding-to-secure-nonstandard-applications"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T23:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Insight Releases H1 2023 Report]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/critical-insight-releases-h1-2023-report</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/critical-insight-releases-h1-2023-report"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T23:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6307-1: JOSE for C/C++ vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6307-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6307-1"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T22:02:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was discovered that JOSE for C/C++ AES GCM decryption routine incorrectly
uses the Tag length from the actual Authentication Tag provided in the JWE.
An attacker could use this to cause a denial of service (system crash) or
might expose sensitive information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Black Hat USA 2023 Closes on Record-Breaking Event in Las Vega]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge/black-hat-usa-2023-closes-on-record-breaking-event-in-las-vega</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge/black-hat-usa-2023-closes-on-record-breaking-event-in-las-vega"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T21:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malwarebytes Announces Acquisition of Online Privacy Company Cyrus]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/malwarebytes-announces-acquisition-of-online-privacy-company-cyrus</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/malwarebytes-announces-acquisition-of-online-privacy-company-cyrus"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T21:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cypago Raises $13M and Unveils its Cyber GRC Automation (CGA) Platform to Simplify GRC Processes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/risk/cypago-raises-13m-and-unveils-its-cyber-grc-automation-cga-platform-to-simplify-grc-processes</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/risk/cypago-raises-13m-and-unveils-its-cyber-grc-automation-cga-platform-to-simplify-grc-processes"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T20:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kyndryl and Cisco Expand Partnership Focusing on Cyber Resilience]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/kyndryl-and-cisco-expand-partnership-focusing-on-cyber-resilience</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/kyndryl-and-cisco-expand-partnership-focusing-on-cyber-resilience"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T20:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Space Industry More Prone to Foreign Espionage, US Agencies Warn]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/us-space-industry-more-prone-to-foreign-espionage-us-agencies-warn</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/us-space-industry-more-prone-to-foreign-espionage-us-agencies-warn"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Foreign intelligence entities have the US space industry in their sights, posing serious threats to US national security, multiple federal agencies say.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese-Backed APT ‘Flax Typhoon’ Hacks Taiwan With Minimal Malware Footprint]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34754</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/chinese-backed-apt-flax-typhoon-hacks-taiwan-with-minimal-malware-footprint/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T19:59:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft warns that Chinese spies are hacking into Taiwanese organizations with minimal use of malware and by abusing legitimate software.
The post Chinese-Backed APT ‘Flax Typhoon’ Hacks Taiwan With Minimal Malware Footprint appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Naraine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware With an Identity Crisis Targets Small Businesses, Individuals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/ransomware-with-an-identity-crisis-targets-small-businesses-individuals</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/ransomware-with-an-identity-crisis-targets-small-businesses-individuals"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T18:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TZW is the latest version of Adhubllka, which has been active since 2019 but has gone largely unreported due to its lower ransom demands.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Montalbano, Contributor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[eBay Users Beware Russian 'Telekopye' Telegram Phishing Bot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/ebay-users-russian-telekopye-telegram-phishing-bot</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/ebay-users-russian-telekopye-telegram-phishing-bot"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T17:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to a simple Telegram bot that democratizes phishing, ordinary Russians can conduct full-fledged phishing attacks with zero technical know-how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[University of Minnesota Confirms Data Breach, Says Ransomware Not Involved]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34752</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/university-of-minnesota-confirms-data-breach-says-ransomware-not-involved/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T17:38:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[University of Minnesota confirms data was stolen from its systems, says no malware infection or file encryption has been identified.
The post University of Minnesota Confirms Data Breach, Says Ransomware Not Involved appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Arghire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6306-1: Fast DDS vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6306-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6306-1"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T17:34:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was discovered that Fast DDS incorrectly handled certain inputs.
A remote attacker could possibly use this issue to cause a denial of
service and information exposure. This issue only affected Ubuntu
22.04 LTS. (CVE-2021-38425)

It was discovered that Fast DDS incorrectly handled certain inputs.
An attacker could possibly use this issue to cause a crash.
(CVE-2023-39534, CVE-2023-39945, CVE-2023-39946, CVE-2023-39947,
CVE-2023-39948, CVE-2023-39949)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What the Hive Ransomware Case Says About RaaS and Cryptocurrency]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/what-the-hive-ransomware-case-says-about-raas-and-cryptocurrency</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/what-the-hive-ransomware-case-says-about-raas-and-cryptocurrency"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hive tells us a lot about ransomware-as-a-service trends and the best ways to defend against attacks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Estes, Intrusion Analyst, WatchGuard Technologies</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lazarus Group Exploits Critical Zoho ManageEngine Flaw to Deploy Stealthy QuiteRAT Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/lazarus-group-exploits-critical-zoho.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/lazarus-group-exploits-critical-zoho.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T15:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The North Korea-linked threat actor known as Lazarus Group has been observed exploiting a now-patched critical security flaw impacting Zoho ManageEngine ServiceDesk Plus to distribute a remote access trojan called such as QuiteRAT.
Targets include internet backbone infrastructure and healthcare entities in Europe and the U.S., cybersecurity company Cisco Talos said in a two-part analysis]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco Patches Vulnerabilities Exposing Switches, Firewalls to DoS Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34751</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/cisco-patches-vulnerabilities-exposing-switches-firewalls-to-dos-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T14:30:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco has released patches for three high-severity vulnerabilities in NX-OS and FXOS software that could lead to denial-of-service (DoS) conditions.
The post Cisco Patches Vulnerabilities Exposing Switches, Firewalls to DoS Attacks appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Arghire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Best Practices for Implementing Risk-First Cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/risk/5-best-practices-for-implementing-risk-first-cybersecurity</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/risk/5-best-practices-for-implementing-risk-first-cybersecurity"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Embracing a risk-first mindset empowers organizations to make informed decisions, strengthen security, safeguard valuable assets, and reduce financial impact.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kaus Phaltankar, Co-Founder &amp; CEO, Caveonix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Telegram Bot "Telekopye" Powering Large-scale Phishing Scams from Russia]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/new-telegram-bot-telekopye-powering.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/new-telegram-bot-telekopye-powering.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T12:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new financially motivated operation is leveraging a malicious Telegram bot to help threat actors scam their victims.
Dubbed Telekopye, a portmanteau of Telegram and kopye (meaning "spear" in Russian), the toolkit functions as an automated means to create a phishing web page from a premade template and send the URL to potential victims, codenamed Mammoths by the criminals.
"This toolkit is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korea's Lazarus APT Uses GUI Framework to Build Stealthy RAT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/north-koreas-lazarus-group-used-gui-framework-to-build-stealthy-rat</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/north-koreas-lazarus-group-used-gui-framework-to-build-stealthy-rat"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T12:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world's most notorious threat actor is using an unprecedented tactic for sneaking spyware into the IT networks of important companies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Releases Six Industrial Control Systems Advisories]]></title>
        <id>/node/18677</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/08/24/cisa-releases-six-industrial-control-systems-advisories"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CISA released six Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisories on August 24, 2023. These advisories provide timely information about current security issues, vulnerabilities, and exploits surrounding ICS.
ICSA-23-236-01 KNX Protocol
ICSA-23-236-02 Opto 22 SNAP PAC S1
ICSA-23-236-03 CODESYS Development System
ICSA-23-236-04 CODESYS Development System
ICSA-23-236-05 CODESYS Development System
ICSA-23-236-06 Rockwell Automation Input/Output Modules
CISA encourages users and administrators to review the newly released ICS advisories for technical details and mitigations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Adds Two Known Exploited Vulnerabilities to Catalog]]></title>
        <id>/node/18669</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/08/24/cisa-adds-two-known-exploited-vulnerabilities-catalog"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CISA has added two new vulnerabilities to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog, based on evidence of active exploitation.
CVE-2023-38831 RARLAB WinRAR Code Execution Vulnerability
CVE-2023-32315 Ignite Realtime Openfire Path Traversal Vulnerability
These types of vulnerabilities are frequent attack vectors for malicious cyber actors and pose significant risks to the federal enterprise. Note: To view other newly added vulnerabilities in the catalog, click on the arrow in the "Date Added to Catalog" column—which will sort by descending dates.
Binding Operational Directive (BOD) 22-01: Reducing the Significant Risk of Known Exploited Vulnerabilities established the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog as a living list of known Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVEs) that carry significant risk to the federal enterprise. BOD 22-01 requires Federal Civilian Executive Branch (FCEB) agencies to remediate identified vulnerabilities by the due date to protect FCEB networks against active threats. See the BOD 22-01 Fact Sheet for more information.
Although BOD 22-01 only applies to FCEB agencies, CISA strongly urges all organizations to reduce their exposure to cyberattacks by prioritizing timely remediation of Catalog vulnerabilities as part of their vulnerability management practice. CISA will continue to add vulnerabilities to the catalog that meet the specified criteria.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hidden Dangers of Public Wi-Fi]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/the-hidden-dangers-of-public-wi-fi.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/the-hidden-dangers-of-public-wi-fi.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T11:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Public Wi-Fi, which has long since become the norm, poses threats to not only individual users but also businesses. With the rise of remote work, people can now work from virtually anywhere: a cafe close to home, a hotel in a different city, or even while waiting for a plane at the airport. Next, let's explore the risks of connecting to public Wi-Fi, both for you personally and for businesses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Parmesan Anti-Forgery Protection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/08/parmesan-anti-forgery-protection.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/08/parmesan-anti-forgery-protection.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T11:24:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The <i>Guardian</i> is <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/food/2023/aug/18/parmesan-producers-fight-fakes-microtransponders-chips-rind">reporting</a> about microchips in wheels of Parmesan cheese as an anti-forgery measure.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New "Whiffy Recon" Malware Triangulates Infected Device Location via Wi-Fi Every Minute]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/new-whiffy-recon-malware-triangulates.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/new-whiffy-recon-malware-triangulates.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T11:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SmokeLoader malware is being used to deliver a new Wi-Fi scanning malware strain called Whiffy Recon on compromised Windows machines.
"The new malware strain has only one operation. Every 60 seconds it triangulates the infected systems' positions by scanning nearby Wi-Fi access points as a data point for Google's geolocation API," Secureworks Counter Threat Unit (CTU) said in a statement]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WinRAR Security Flaw Exploited in Zero-Day Attacks to Target Traders]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/winrar-security-flaw-exploited-in-zero.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/winrar-security-flaw-exploited-in-zero.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T11:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recently patched security flaw in the popular WinRAR archiving software has been exploited as a zero-day since April 2023, new findings from Group-IB reveal.
The vulnerability, cataloged as CVE-2023-38831, allows threat actors to spoof file extensions, thereby making it possible to launch malicious scripts contained within an archive that masquerades as seemingly innocuous image or text files.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thousands of Unpatched Openfire XMPP Servers Still Exposed to High-Severity Flaw]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/thousands-of-unpatched-openfire-xmpp.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/thousands-of-unpatched-openfire-xmpp.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T08:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thousands of Openfire XMPP servers are unpatched against a recently disclosed high-severity flaw and are susceptible to a new exploit, according to a new report from VulnCheck.
Tracked as CVE-2023-32315 (CVSS score: 7.5), the vulnerability relates to a path traversal vulnerability in Openfire's administrative console that could permit an unauthenticated attacker to access otherwise restricted]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tornado Cash Founders Charged in Billion-Dollar Crypto Laundering Scandal]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/tornado-cash-founders-charged-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/tornado-cash-founders-charged-in.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T07:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Justice Department (DoJ) on Wednesday unsealed an indictment against two founders of the now-sanctioned Tornado Cash cryptocurrency mixer service, charging them with laundering more than $1 billion in criminal proceeds.
Both the individuals, Roman Storm and Roman Semenov, have been charged with conspiracy to commit money laundering, conspiracy to commit sanctions violations, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[eSentire Labs Open Sources Project to Monitor LLMs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/esentire-labs-open-sources-project-to-monitor-llms</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/esentire-labs-open-sources-project-to-monitor-llms"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The eSentire LLM Gateway provides monitoring and governance of ChatGPT and other Large Language Models being used in the organization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prelude Security Tackles Continuous Security Testing in Containers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/prelude-security-tackles-continuous-security-testing-in-containers</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/prelude-security-tackles-continuous-security-testing-in-containers"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Probes are tiny processes which run inside containers and scan applications for vulnerabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware Reaches New Heights]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/ransomware-reaches-new-heights</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/ransomware-reaches-new-heights"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T21:40:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's not going anywhere: Easy-to-exploit bugs like MOVEit, leaks of stolen data, and rapid-fire escalation are keeping ransomware attacks as painful as ever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Lemos, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Threat Actor Exploits Zero-Day in WinRAR to Target Crypto Accounts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/threat-actor-exploits-zero-day-in-winrar-to-target-crypto-accounts</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/threat-actor-exploits-zero-day-in-winrar-to-target-crypto-accounts"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T21:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attacks targeting the now-patched bug have been going on since at least April 2023, security vendor says.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI Warns of Cryptocurrency Heists by North Korea's Lazarus Group]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/fbi-warns-of-cryptocurrency-heists-by-north-koreas-lazarus-group</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/fbi-warns-of-cryptocurrency-heists-by-north-koreas-lazarus-group"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The most recent stolen bitcoin comes just after three major operations occurred in June, with millions stolen in each heist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Name That Toon: Swift as an Arrow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/name-that-toon-swift-as-an-arrow</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/name-that-toon-swift-as-an-arrow"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feeling creative? Submit your caption and our panel of experts will reward the winner with a $25 Amazon gift card.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Klossner, Cartoonist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6305-1: PHP vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6305-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6305-1"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T16:40:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was discovered that PHP incorrectly handled certain XML files.
An attacker could possibly use this issue to expose sensitive information.
(CVE-2023-3823)

It was discovered that PHP incorrectly handled certain PHAR files.
An attacker could possibly use this issue to cause a crash,
expose sensitive information or execute arbitrary code.
(CVE-2023-3824)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Attackers Dangle AI-Based Facebook Ad Lures to Hijack Business Accounts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/attackers-dangle-ai-based-facebook-ad-lures-to-take-over-business-accounts</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/attackers-dangle-ai-based-facebook-ad-lures-to-take-over-business-accounts"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T15:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The offending ads and pages leveraged interest in AI to spread a malicious credential-stealing browser extension.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Montalbano, Contributor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Early Warning Indicators That Are Key to Protecting National Secrets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/5-early-warning-indicators-that-are-key-to-protecting-national-secrets</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/5-early-warning-indicators-that-are-key-to-protecting-national-secrets"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Defense Department must modernize user activity monitoring by prioritizing data that can be used early to proactively mitigate insider risk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kellie Roessler, Insider Risk Advocate &amp; Author, DTEX Insider Intelligence &amp; Investigations (i3) Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean Affiliates Suspected in $40M Cryptocurrency Heist, FBI Warns]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/north-korean-affiliates-suspected-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/north-korean-affiliates-suspected-in.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T12:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) on Tuesday warned that threat actors affiliated with North Korea may attempt to cash out stolen cryptocurrency worth more than $40 million.
The law enforcement agency attributed the blockchain activity to an adversary the U.S. government tracks as TraderTraitor, which is also known by the name Jade Sleet.
An investigation undertaken by the FBI found]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Set to Enable Default End-to-End Encryption on Messenger by Year End]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/meta-set-to-enable-default-end-to-end.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/meta-set-to-enable-default-end-to-end.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T12:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta has once again reaffirmed its plans to roll out support for end-to-end encryption (E2EE) by default for one-to-one friends and family chats on Messenger by the end of the year.
As part of that effort, the social media giant said it's upgrading "millions more people's chats" effective August 22, 2023, exactly seven months after it started gradually expanding the feature to more users in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Agile Approach to Mass Cloud Credential Harvesting and Crypto Mining Sprints Ahead]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/agile-approach-to-mass-cloud-credential.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/agile-approach-to-mass-cloud-credential.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T11:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers are not the only people who have adopted the agile methodology for their development processes. From 2023-06-15 to 2023-07-11, Permiso Security’s p0 Labs team identified and tracked an attacker developing and deploying eight (8) incremental iterations of their credential harvesting malware while continuing to develop infrastructure for an upcoming (spoiler: now launched) campaign]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Syrian Threat Actor EVLF Unmasked as Creator of CypherRAT and CraxsRAT Android Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/syrian-threat-actor-evlf-unmasked-as.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/syrian-threat-actor-evlf-unmasked-as.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T11:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Syrian threat actor named EVLF has been outed as the creator of malware families CypherRAT and CraxsRAT.
"These RATs are designed to allow an attacker to remotely perform real-time actions and control the victim device's camera, location, and microphone," Cybersecurity firm Cyfirma said in a report published last week.
CypherRAT and CraxsRAT are said to be offered to other cybercriminals as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[December’s Reimagining Democracy Workshop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/08/decembers-reimagining-democracy-workshop.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/08/decembers-reimagining-democracy-workshop.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T11:06:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Imagine that we&#8217;ve all&#8212;all of us, all of society&#8212;landed on some alien planet, and we have to form a government: clean slate. We don&#8217;t have any legacy systems from the US or any other country. We don&#8217;t have any special or unique interests to perturb our thinking.</p>
<p>How would we govern ourselves?</p>
<p>It&#8217;s unlikely that we would use the systems we have today. The modern representative democracy was the best form of government that mid-eighteenth-century technology could conceive of. The twenty-first century is a different place scientifically, technically and socially...</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spacecolon Toolset Fuels Global Surge in Scarab Ransomware Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/spacecolon-toolset-fuels-global-surge.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/spacecolon-toolset-fuels-global-surge.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T09:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A malicious toolset dubbed Spacecolon is being deployed as part of an ongoing campaign to spread variants of the Scarab ransomware across victim organizations globally.
"It probably finds its way into victim organizations by its operators compromising vulnerable web servers or via brute forcing RDP credentials," ESET security researcher Jakub Souček said in a detailed technical write-up]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Over a Dozen Malicious npm Packages Target Roblox Game Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/over-dozen-malicious-npm-packages.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/over-dozen-malicious-npm-packages.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T06:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than a dozen malicious packages have been discovered on the npm package repository since the start of August 2023 with capabilities to deploy an open-source information stealer called Luna Token Grabber on systems belonging to Roblox developers.
The ongoing campaign, first detected on August 1 by ReversingLabs, employs modules that masquerade as the legitimate package noblox.js, an API]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More Than Half of Browser Extensions Pose Security Risks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/study-more-than-half-of-browser-extensions-pose-security-risks</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/study-more-than-half-of-browser-extensions-pose-security-risks"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T21:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spin.AI's risk assessment of some 300,000 browser extensions found 51% had overly permissive access and could execute potentially malicious behaviors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grip Security Raising $41M Series B Led by Third Point Ventures]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/grip-security-raising-41m-series-b-led-by-third-point-ventures</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/grip-security-raising-41m-series-b-led-by-third-point-ventures"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forescout Joins MISA and Announces Integration With Microsoft Sentinel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/forescout-joins-misa-and-announces-integration-with-microsoft-sentinel</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/forescout-joins-misa-and-announces-integration-with-microsoft-sentinel"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T21:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Absolute Dental Services Notifies Patients of Data Security Incident]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/absolute-dental-services-notifies-patients-of-data-security-incident</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/absolute-dental-services-notifies-patients-of-data-security-incident"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T21:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adobe Patches Critical Deserialization Vulnerability, but Exploits Persist]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/adobe-patches-critical-deserialization-vulnerability-but-exploits-persist</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/adobe-patches-critical-deserialization-vulnerability-but-exploits-persist"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The vulnerability was being exploited in the wild, targeting two versions of Adobe ColdFusion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Controversial Cybercrime Law Passes in Jordan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/controversial-cybercrime-law-passes-in-jordan</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/controversial-cybercrime-law-passes-in-jordan"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T19:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The increase in cyberattacks against the Middle East in the last few years has pressured Jordan and other nations to better secure their infrastructures.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Raywood, Senior Editor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Newer, Better XLoader Signals a Dangerous Shift in macOS Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/newer-better-xloader-signals-dangerous-shift-macos-malware</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/newer-better-xloader-signals-dangerous-shift-macos-malware"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T19:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malware aimed at macOS is no longer just a knockoff of a Windows bug, as a new infostealer proliferating on Mac laptops demonstrates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Software Makers May Face Greater Liability in Wake of MOVEit Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/software-vendors-may-face-greater-liability-in-wake-of-moveit-lawsuit</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/software-vendors-may-face-greater-liability-in-wake-of-moveit-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T17:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Makers of vulnerable apps that are exploited in wide-scale supply chain attacks need to improve software security or face steep fines and settlement fees.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Montalbano, Contributor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Leadership Style Is a Security Risk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/risk/when-leadership-style-is-a-security-risk</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/risk/when-leadership-style-is-a-security-risk"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Risk-aware leaders can be a cybersecurity advantage. Their flexible leadership style and emphasis on security first help set the tone and demonstrate a commitment to avoiding risk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Farrar, CISO, Exabeam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6304-1: Inetutils vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6304-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6304-1"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T16:59:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was discovered that telnetd in GNU Inetutils incorrectly handled certain inputs.
An attacker could possibly use this issue to cause a crash.  This issue
only affected Ubuntu 20.04 LTS and Ubuntu 22.04 LTS (CVE-2022-39028)

It was discovered that Inetutils incorrectly handled certain inputs.
An attacker could possibly use this issue to expose sensitive information,
or execute arbitrary code.
(CVE-2023-40303)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Physical Impact of Cyberattacks on Cities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/physical-impact-of-cyberattacks-on-cities</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/physical-impact-of-cyberattacks-on-cities"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding potential threats and regularly updating response plans are the best lines of defense in the new world of cyberattacks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tracy Reinhold, Chief Security Officer, Everbridge</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Cuba' Ransomware Group Uses Every Trick in the Book]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge/cuba-ransomware-group-uses-every-trick-in-the-book</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge/cuba-ransomware-group-uses-every-trick-in-the-book"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How a Russian cybercrime group using Cuban Revolution references and iconography has emerged as one of the most profitable ransomware operations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Adds Two Known Exploited Vulnerabilities to Catalog]]></title>
        <id>/node/18655</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/08/22/cisa-adds-two-known-exploited-vulnerabilities-catalog"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CISA has added two new vulnerabilities to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog, based on evidence of active exploitation.
CVE-2023-38035 Ivanti Sentry Authentication Bypass Vulnerability 
CVE-2023-27532 Veeam Backup & Replication Cloud Connect Missing Authentication for Critical Function Vulnerability
These types of vulnerabilities are frequent attack vectors for malicious cyber actors and pose significant risks to the federal enterprise. Note: To view other newly added vulnerabilities in the catalog, click on the arrow in the "Date Added to Catalog" column—which will sort by descending dates.
Binding Operational Directive (BOD) 22-01: Reducing the Significant Risk of Known Exploited Vulnerabilities established the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog as a living list of known Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVEs) that carry significant risk to the federal enterprise. BOD 22-01 requires Federal Civilian Executive Branch (FCEB) agencies to remediate identified vulnerabilities by the due date to protect FCEB networks against active threats. See the BOD 22-01 Fact Sheet for more information.
Although BOD 22-01 only applies to FCEB agencies, CISA strongly urges all organizations to reduce their exposure to cyberattacks by prioritizing timely remediation of Catalog vulnerabilities as part of their vulnerability management practice. CISA will continue to add vulnerabilities to the catalog that meet the specified criteria.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Releases Four Industrial Control Systems Advisories]]></title>
        <id>/node/18664</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/08/22/cisa-releases-four-industrial-control-systems-advisories"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CISA released four Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisories on August 22, 2023. These advisories provide timely information about current security issues, vulnerabilities, and exploits surrounding ICS.
ICSA-23-234-01 Hitachi Energy AFF66x
ICSA-23-234-02 Trane Thermostats
ICSA-23-234-03 Rockwell Automation ThinManager ThinServer
ICSA-23-138-02 Mitsubishi Electric MELSEC WS Series (Update A)
CISA encourages users and administrators to review the newly released ICS advisories for technical details and mitigations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISOs Tout SaaS Cybersecurity Confidence, But 79% Admit to SaaS Incidents, New Report Finds]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/cisos-tout-saas-cybersecurity.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/cisos-tout-saas-cybersecurity.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T11:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new State of SaaS Security Posture Management Report from SaaS cybersecurity provider AppOmni indicates that Cybersecurity, IT, and business leaders alike recognize SaaS cybersecurity as an increasingly important part of the cyber threat landscape. And at first glance, respondents appear generally optimistic about their SaaS cybersecurity.
Over 600 IT, cybersecurity, and business leaders at]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Applying AI to License Plate Surveillance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/08/applying-ai-to-license-plate-surveillance.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/08/applying-ai-to-license-plate-surveillance.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T11:04:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>License plate scanners aren&#8217;t new. Neither is using them for bulk surveillance. What&#8217;s new is that AI is <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/thomasbrewster/2023/07/17/license-plate-reader-ai-criminal/">being used</a> on the data, identifying &#8220;suspicious&#8221; vehicle behavior:</p>
<blockquote><p>Typically, Automatic License Plate Recognition (ALPR) technology is used to search for plates linked to specific crimes. But in this case it was used to examine the driving patterns of anyone passing one of Westchester County&#8217;s 480 cameras over a two-year period. Zayas&#8217; lawyer Ben Gold contested the AI-gathered evidence against his client, decrying it as &#8220;dragnet surveillance.&#8221;...</p></blockquote>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Carderbee Attacks: Hong Kong Organizations Targeted via Malicious Software Updates]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/carderbee-attacks-hong-kong.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/carderbee-attacks-hong-kong.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T10:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A previously undocumented threat cluster has been linked to a software supply chain attack targeting organizations primarily located in Hong Kong and other regions in Asia.
The Symantec Threat Hunter Team, part of Broadcom, is tracking the activity under its insect-themed moniker Carderbee.
The attacks, per the cybersecurity firm, leverage a trojanized version of a legitimate software called]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese APT Targets Hong Kong in Supply Chain Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/chinese-apt-targets-hong-kong-in-supply-chain-attack</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/chinese-apt-targets-hong-kong-in-supply-chain-attack"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T10:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dubbed Carderbee, the group used legitimate software and Microsoft-signed malware to spread the Korplug/PlugX backdoor to various Asian targets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Montalbano, Contributor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Variant of XLoader macOS Malware Disguised as 'OfficeNote' Productivity App]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/new-variant-of-xloader-macos-malware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/new-variant-of-xloader-macos-malware.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T07:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new variant of an Apple macOS malware called XLoader has surfaced in the wild, masquerading its malicious features under the guise of an office productivity app called "OfficeNote."
"The new version of XLoader is bundled inside a standard Apple disk image with the name OfficeNote.dmg," SentinelOne security researchers Dinesh Devadoss and Phil Stokes said in a Monday analysis. "The application]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ivanti Warns of Critical Zero-Day Flaw Being Actively Exploited in Sentry Software]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/ivanti-warns-of-critical-zero-day-flaw.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/ivanti-warns-of-critical-zero-day-flaw.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T04:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software services provider Ivanti is warning of a new critical zero-day flaw impacting Ivanti Sentry (formerly MobileIron Sentry) that it said is being actively exploited in the wild, marking an escalation of its security woes.
Tracked as CVE-2023-38035 (CVSS score: 9.8), the issue has been described as a case of authentication bypass impacting versions 9.18 and prior due to what it called an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Adobe ColdFusion Flaw Added to CISA's Exploited Vulnerability Catalog]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/critical-adobe-coldfusion-flaw-added-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/critical-adobe-coldfusion-flaw-added-to.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T03:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has added a critical security flaw in Adobe ColdFusion to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, based on evidence of active exploitation.
The vulnerability, cataloged as CVE-2023-26359 (CVSS score: 9.8), relates to a deserialization flaw present in Adobe ColdFusion 2018 (Update 15 and earlier) and ColdFusion 2021 (]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ivanti Issues Fix for Critical Vuln in Its Sentry Gateway Technology]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/ivanti-issues-fix-for-critical-vuln-in-its-sentry-gateway-technology</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/ivanti-issues-fix-for-critical-vuln-in-its-sentry-gateway-technology"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security vendor will not say if attackers are already actively exploiting the flaw, as some reports have claimed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New NCUA Rule Requires Credit Unions to Report Cyberattacks Within 3 Days]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge/new-ncua-rule-requires-credit-unions-to-report-cyberattacks-within-3-days</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge/new-ncua-rule-requires-credit-unions-to-report-cyberattacks-within-3-days"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The updated cybersecurity reporting rule from the National Credit Union Administration takes effect Sept. 1.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edge Editors, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla Data Breach Investigation Reveals Inside Job]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/tesla-data-breach-investigation-reveals-inside-job</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/tesla-data-breach-investigation-reveals-inside-job"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T19:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The carmaker also reported it's taken legal action against the former employees involved in the data breach, which involved more than 75,000 names.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fed Warning: US Space Industry Subject to Foreign Spying, Disruptions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/fed-warning-us-space-industry-subject-to-foreign-spying-disruptions</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/fed-warning-us-space-industry-subject-to-foreign-spying-disruptions"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T19:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The space industry must improve security as foreign intelligence entities seek to steal trade secrets and disrupt space-based infrastructure, US agencies caution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Eddy, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Energy One Investigates Cyberattack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/energy-one-investigates-cyberattack</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/energy-one-investigates-cyberattack"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T18:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Energy One is trying to determine the initial point of entry and whether personal information has been compromised.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6303-2: ClamAV vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6303-2</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6303-2"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T16:38:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6303-1 fixed a vulnerability in ClamAV. This update provides
the corresponding update for Ubuntu 14.04 LTS, Ubuntu 16.04 LTS,
and Ubuntu 18.04 LTS.

Original advisory details:

 It was discovered that ClamAV incorrectly handled parsing HFS+ files. A
 remote attacker could possibly use this issue to cause ClamAV to crash,
 resulting in a denial of service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generative AI Is Scraping Your Data. So, Now What?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/generative-ai-is-scraping-your-data-so-now-what</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/generative-ai-is-scraping-your-data-so-now-what"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI innovation is moving faster than our laws and regulations, making it hard to decide whether Web or content scraping activity is good or bad, and what (if anything) you should do about it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin Fabre, Co-Founder &amp; CEO, DataDome</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New WinRAR Vulnerability Could Allow Hackers to Take Control of Your PC]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/new-winrar-vulnerability-could-allow.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/new-winrar-vulnerability-could-allow.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T13:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A high-severity security flaw has been disclosed in the WinRAR utility that could be potentially exploited by a threat actor to achieve remote code execution on Windows systems.
Tracked as CVE-2023-40477 (CVSS score: 7.8), the vulnerability has been described as a case of improper validation while processing recovery volumes.
"The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DEF CON's AI Village Pits Hackers Against LLMs to Find Flaws]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/def-cons-ai-village-pits-hackers-against-llms-to-find-flaws</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/def-cons-ai-village-pits-hackers-against-llms-to-find-flaws"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T13:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Touted as the largest red teaming exercise against LLMs in history, the AI Village attracted more than 2,000 hackers and throngs of media.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Becky Bracken, Editor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Adds One Known Exploited Vulnerability to Catalog]]></title>
        <id>/node/18648</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/08/21/cisa-adds-one-known-exploited-vulnerability-catalog"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CISA has added one new vulnerability to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog, based on evidence of active exploitation.
CVE-2023-26359 Adobe ColdFusion Deserialization of Untrusted Data Vulnerability
These types of vulnerabilities are frequent attack vectors for malicious cyber actors and pose significant risks to the federal enterprise. Note: To view other newly added vulnerabilities in the catalog, click on the arrow in the "Date Added to Catalog" column—which will sort by descending dates.
Binding Operational Directive (BOD) 22-01: Reducing the Significant Risk of Known Exploited Vulnerabilities established the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog as a living list of known Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVEs) that carry significant risk to the federal enterprise. BOD 22-01 requires Federal Civilian Executive Branch (FCEB) agencies to remediate identified vulnerabilities by the due date to protect FCEB networks against active threats. See the BOD 22-01 Fact Sheet for more information.
Although BOD 22-01 only applies to FCEB agencies, CISA strongly urges all organizations to reduce their exposure to cyberattacks by prioritizing timely remediation of Catalog vulnerabilities as part of their vulnerability management practice. CISA will continue to add vulnerabilities to the catalog that meet the specified criteria.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA, NSA, and NIST Publish Factsheet on Quantum Readiness]]></title>
        <id>/node/18653</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/08/21/cisa-nsa-and-nist-publish-factsheet-quantum-readiness"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, the Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA), National Security Agency (NSA) and National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) released a joint factsheet, Quantum-Readiness: Migration to Post-Quantum Cryptography (PQC), to inform organizations—especially those that support Critical Infrastructure—of the impacts of quantum capabilities, and to encourage the early planning for migration to post-quantum cryptographic standards by developing a Quantum-Readiness Roadmap.
CISA, NSA, and NIST urge organizations to review the joint factsheet and to begin preparing now by creating quantum-readiness roadmaps, conducting inventories, applying risk assessments and analysis, and engaging vendors. For more information and resources related to CISA’s PQC work, visit Post-Quantum Cryptography Initiative.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6303-1: ClamAV vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6303-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6303-1"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T11:32:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was discovered that ClamAV incorrectly handled parsing HFS+ files. A
remote attacker could possibly use this issue to cause ClamAV to crash,
resulting in a denial of service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerability Summary for the Week of August 14, 2023]]></title>
        <id>/node/18651</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/bulletins/sb23-233"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T11:27:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[High Vulnerabilities

Primary
Description
Published
CVSS Score
Source & Patch Info

foldingathome -- client_advanced_control
An issue was discovered in FoldingAtHome Client Advanced Control GUI before commit 9b619ae64443997948a36dda01b420578de1af77, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via crafted payload to function parse_message in file Connection.py.
2023-08-11
9.8
CVE-2020-27544
MISC

sourcecodester -- school_faculty_scheduling_system
SQL Injection vulnerability in oretnom23 School Faculty Scheduling System version 1.0, allows remote attacker to execute arbitrary code, escalate privilieges, and gain sensitive information via crafted payload to id parameter in manage_user.php.
2023-08-11
9.8
CVE-2020-36034
MISC
MISC
MISC

bloofox -- bloofoxcms
File Upload vulnerability in b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Investigate an OAuth Grant for Suspicious Activity or Overly Permissive Scopes]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/how-to-investigate-oauth-grant-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/how-to-investigate-oauth-grant-for.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T11:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From a user’s perspective, OAuth works like magic. In just a few keystrokes, you can whisk through the account creation process and gain immediate access to whatever new app or integration you’re seeking. Unfortunately, few users understand the implications of the permissions they allow when they create a new OAuth grant, making it easy for malicious actors to manipulate employees into giving]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[White House Announces AI Cybersecurity Challenge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/08/white-house-announces-ai-cybersecurity-challenge.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/08/white-house-announces-ai-cybersecurity-challenge.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T11:10:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>At Black Hat last week, the White House announced an <a href="https://aicyberchallenge.com/about/">AI Cyber Challenge</a>. Gizmodo <a href="https://gizmodo.com/white-house-announces-ai-cyber-challenge-blackhat-aixcc-1850718972">reports</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>The new AI cyber challenge (which is being abbreviated &#8220;AIxCC&#8221;) will have a number of different phases. Interested would-be competitors can now submit their proposals to the Small Business Innovation Research program for evaluation and, eventually, selected teams will participate in a 2024 &#8220;qualifying event.&#8221; During that event, the top 20 teams will be invited to a semifinal competition at that year&#8217;s DEF CON, another large cybersecurity conference, where the field will be further whittled down...</p></blockquote>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Malware Turned Thousands of Hacked Windows and macOS PCs into Proxy Servers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/this-malware-turned-thousands-of-hacked.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/this-malware-turned-thousands-of-hacked.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T10:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors are leveraging access to malware-infected Windows and macOS machines to deliver a proxy server application and use them as exit nodes to reroute proxy requests.
According to AT&T Alien Labs, the unnamed company that offers the proxy service operates more than 400,000 proxy exit nodes, although it's not immediately clear how many of them were co-opted by malware installed on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visibility Is Just Not Enough to Secure Operational Technology Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/ics-ot/visibility-is-just-not-enough-to-secure-operational-technology-systems</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/ics-ot/visibility-is-just-not-enough-to-secure-operational-technology-systems"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visibility is just the first step to secure your operational technology environment against today's threats. You need a proactive, defense-in-depth approach.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6302-1: Vim vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6302-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6302-1"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T05:45:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was discovered that Vim incorrectly handled memory when opening certain
files. If an attacker could trick a user into opening a specially crafted
file, it could cause Vim to crash, or possibly execute arbitrary code. This
issue only affected Ubuntu 22.04 LTS. (CVE-2022-2522, CVE-2022-2580,
CVE-2022-2817, CVE-2022-2819, CVE-2022-2862, CVE-2022-2889, CVE-2022-2982,
CVE-2022-3134)

It was discovered that Vim did not properly perform bounds checks in the
diff mode in certain situations. An attacker could possibly use this issue
to cause a denial of service. This issue only affected Ubuntu 18.04 LTS,
Ubuntu 20.04 LTS and Ubuntu 22.04 LTS. (CVE-2022-2598)

It was discovered that Vim did not properly perform bounds checks in
certain situations. An attacker could possibly use this issue to cause a
denial of service. This issue only affected Ubuntu 22.04 LTS.
(CVE-2022-2816)

It was discovered that Vim incorrectly handled memory when skipping
compiled code. An attacker could possibly use this issue to cause a denial
of service. This issue only affected Ubuntu 22.04 LTS. (CVE-2022-2874)

It was discovered that Vim incorrectly handled memory when opening certain
files. If an attacker could trick a user into opening a specially crafted
file, it could cause Vim to crash, or possibly execute arbitrary code. This
issue only affected Ubuntu 20.04 LTS and Ubuntu 22.04 LTS. (CVE-2022-3016,
CVE-2022-3037)

It was discovered that Vim incorrectly handled memory when invalid line
number on ":for" is ignored. An attacker could possibly use this issue to
cause a denial of service. (CVE-2022-3099)

It was discovered that Vim incorrectly handled memory when passing invalid
arguments to the assert_fails() method. An attacker could possibly use this
issue to cause a denial of service. This issue only affected Ubuntu 22.04
LTS. (CVE-2022-3153)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HiatusRAT Malware Resurfaces: Taiwan Firms and U.S. Military Under Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/hiatusrat-malware-resurfaces-taiwan.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/hiatusrat-malware-resurfaces-taiwan.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T05:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actors behind the HiatusRAT malware have returned from their hiatus with a new wave of reconnaissance and targeting activity aimed at Taiwan-based organizations and a U.S. military procurement system.
Besides recompiling malware samples for different architectures, the artifacts are said to have been hosted on new virtual private servers (VPSs), Lumen Black Lotus Labs said in a report]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6267-3: Firefox regressions]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6267-3</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6267-3"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T02:12:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6267-1 fixed vulnerabilities and USN-6267-2 fixed minor regressions in
Firefox. The update introduced several minor regressions. This update fixes
the problem.

We apologize for the inconvenience.

Original advisory details:

 Multiple security issues were discovered in Firefox. If a user were
 tricked into opening a specially crafted website, an attacker could
 potentially exploit these to cause a denial of service, obtain sensitive
 information across domains, or execute arbitrary code. (CVE-2023-4047,
 CVE-2023-4048, CVE-2023-4049, CVE-2023-4051, CVE-2023-4053, CVE-2023-4055,
 CVE-2023-4056, CVE-2023-4057, CVE-2023-4058)
 
 Max Vlasov discovered that Firefox Offscreen Canvas did not properly track
 cross-origin tainting. An attacker could potentially exploit this issue to
 access image data from another site in violation of same-origin policy.
 (CVE-2023-4045)
 
 Alexander Guryanov discovered that Firefox did not properly update the
 value of a global variable in WASM JIT analysis in some circumstances. An
 attacker could potentially exploit this issue to cause a denial of service.
 (CVE-2023-4046)
 
 Mark Brand discovered that Firefox did not properly validate the size of
 an untrusted input stream. An attacker could potentially exploit this issue
 to cause a denial of service. (CVE-2023-4050)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WoofLocker Toolkit Hides Malicious Codes in Images to Run Tech Support Scams]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/wooflocker-toolkit-hides-malicious.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/wooflocker-toolkit-hides-malicious.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T11:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have detailed an updated version of an advanced fingerprinting and redirection toolkit called WoofLocker that's engineered to conduct tech support scams.
The sophisticated traffic redirection scheme was first documented by Malwarebytes in January 2020, leveraging JavaScript embedded in compromised websites to perform anti-bot and web traffic filtering checks to serve]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Juniper Junos OS Flaws Expose Devices to Remote Attacks - Patch Now]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/new-juniper-junos-os-flaws-expose.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/new-juniper-junos-os-flaws-expose.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T07:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Networking hardware company Juniper Networks has released an "out-of-cycle" security update to address multiple flaws in the J-Web component of Junos OS that could be combined to achieve remote code execution on susceptible installations.
The four vulnerabilities have a cumulative CVSS rating of 9.8, making them Critical in severity. They affect all versions of Junos OS on SRX and EX Series.
"By]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thousands of Android Malware Apps Using Stealthy APK Compression to Evade Detection]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/thousands-of-android-malware-apps-using.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/thousands-of-android-malware-apps-using.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T06:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors are using Android Package (APK) files with unknown or unsupported compression methods to elude malware analysis.
That's according to findings from Zimperium, which found 3,300 artifacts leveraging such compression algorithms in the wild. 71 of the identified samples can be loaded on the operating system without any problems.
There is no evidence that the apps were available on the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friday Squid Blogging: Squid Brand Fish Sauce]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/08/friday-squid-blogging-squid-brand-fish-sauce.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/08/friday-squid-blogging-squid-brand-fish-sauce.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T21:02:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Squid Brand is a Thai company that makes <a href="https://www.foodnavigator-asia.com/Article/2023/07/24/thailand-s-squid-brand-capitalising-on-trending-flavours-and-personalised-healthy-options-to-stay-on-top">fish sauce</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>It is part of Squid Brand&#8217;s range of &#8220;personalized healthy fish sauces&#8221; that cater to different consumer groups, which include the Mild Fish Sauce for Kids and Mild Fish Sauce for Silver Ages.</p></blockquote>
<p>It also has a Vegan Fish Sauce.</p>
<p>As usual, you can also use this squid post to talk about the security stories in the news that I haven’t covered.</p>
<p>Read my blog posting guidelines <a href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2017/03/commenting_poli.html">here</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CyCognito Finds Large Volume of Personal Identifiable Information in Vulnerable Cloud and Web Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/cycognito-finds-large-volume-of-personal-identifiable-information-in-vulnerable-cloud-and-web-applications</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/cycognito-finds-large-volume-of-personal-identifiable-information-in-vulnerable-cloud-and-web-applications"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T20:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ProjectDiscovery Announces $25M Series A Financing and Launch of Cloud Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/projectdiscovery-announces-25m-series-a-financing-and-launch-of-cloud-platform</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/projectdiscovery-announces-25m-series-a-financing-and-launch-of-cloud-platform"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T20:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phishing Attack Targets Hundreds of Zimbra Customers in 4 Continents]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/phishing-attack-targets-hundreds-zimbra-customers-four-continents</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/phishing-attack-targets-hundreds-zimbra-customers-four-continents"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A good chunk of the entire user base of a particular email service is being targeted for sensitive credentials.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Committee Tackles Remote Monitoring and Management Protections]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/cisa-committee-tackles-remote-monitoring-and-management-protections</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/cisa-committee-tackles-remote-monitoring-and-management-protections"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CISA's public-private partnership produces RMM strategies to shore up critical infrastructure and to educate the MSPs that provide remote access to them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Becky Bracken, Editor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cyderes Dives In On Working Safely With AI and Upping Your IAM Game]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/cyderes-dives-in-on-working-safely-with-ai-and-upping-your-iam-game</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/cyderes-dives-in-on-working-safely-with-ai-and-upping-your-iam-game"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T18:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this Dark Reading News Desk segment, Mike Wyatt and John Ayers of Cyderes discuss how artificial intelligence has already been weaponized against businesses and consumers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[App Security Posture Management Improves Software Security, Synopsys Says]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/app-security-posture-management-improves-software-security-synopsys-says</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/app-security-posture-management-improves-software-security-synopsys-says"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T18:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this Dark Reading News Desk segment, Jim Ivers and Natasha Gupta of Synopsys discuss application security posture management and software consolidation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fortra Joins With Microsoft, Health-ISAC to Combat Cobalt Blue Fraud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/analytics/fortra-joins-with-microsoft-health-isac-to-combat-cobalt-blue-fraud</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/analytics/fortra-joins-with-microsoft-health-isac-to-combat-cobalt-blue-fraud"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T18:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this Dark Reading News Desk segment, Frotra's Bob Erdman discusses Fortra's recent collaboration with Microsoft and Health-ISAC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AT&T: How Secure Edge Computing Is Poised to Reshape Healthcare]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/att-how-secure-edge-computing-is-poised-to-reshape-healthcare</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/att-how-secure-edge-computing-is-poised-to-reshape-healthcare"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T18:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this Dark Reading News Desk segment, Theresa Lanowitz of AT&T Business discusses edge computing's impact on the healthcare industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Securonix: Making Sense of AI’s Rapid Acceleration in Cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/analytics/securonix-making-sense-of-ai-rapid-acceleration-in-cybersecurity</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/analytics/securonix-making-sense-of-ai-rapid-acceleration-in-cybersecurity"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T18:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this Dark Reading News Desk segment, Securonix CEO Nayaki Nayyar and Chris Inglis, Former NSA Deputy Director, discuss how AI will reshape cybersecurity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comcast: How to Wrap Enterprise Cybersecurity In the Data Fabric]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/analytics/comcast-how-wrap-enterprise-cybersecurity-data-fabric</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/analytics/comcast-how-wrap-enterprise-cybersecurity-data-fabric"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T18:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this Dark Reading News Desk segment, Comcast's Noopur Davis and Matthew Tharp discuss security management, big data, and data security fabric.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hubble Urges Customers, Security Pros to Return to Infosec Basics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/hubble-urges-customers-security-pros-to-return-to-infosec-basics</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/hubble-urges-customers-security-pros-to-return-to-infosec-basics"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T18:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this Dark Reading News Desk segment, Hubble Technology CEO/founder Tom Parker discusses infosec "back to basics,"  especially security asset visibility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bugcrowd Unleashes Hacker Ingenuity for Proactive, Crowdsourced Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/bugcrowd-unleashes-hacker-ingenuity-for-proactive-crowdsourced-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/bugcrowd-unleashes-hacker-ingenuity-for-proactive-crowdsourced-security"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T18:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this Dark Reading News Desk segment, Dave Gerry, CEO of Bugcrowd, and Casey Ellis, founder and CTO of Bugcrowd, discuss the company's latest "Inside the Mind of a Hacker" report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tel Aviv Stock Exchange CISO: Making Better Use of Your SIEM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/tel-aviv-stock-exchange-ciso-making-better-use-of-your-siem</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/tel-aviv-stock-exchange-ciso-making-better-use-of-your-siem"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T18:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If rule writing for SIEMs isn't managed properly, it can lead to false positives and misconfigurations, which create extra work for the SOC team.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Raywood, Senior Editor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expand Your Definition of ‘Endpoint,’ Get a Better Handle On Cloud Threats]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/expand-your-definition-of-endpoint-get-a-better-handle-on-cloud-threats</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/expand-your-definition-of-endpoint-get-a-better-handle-on-cloud-threats"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T18:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this Dark Reading News Desk segment, Sysdig's Anna Belak discusses how the boom in cloud services and applications expanded the definition of what constitutes an endpoint.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time To Address What’s Undermining SaaS Security, AppOmni Says]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/time-to-address-what-s-undermining-saas-security-appomni-says</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/time-to-address-what-s-undermining-saas-security-appomni-says"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T18:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this Dark Reading News Desk segment, Brendan O'Connor, CEO and Co-Founder of AppOmni describes some of the biggest security challenges for securing software-as-a-service (SaaS) applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PKI Maturity Model Aims to Improve Crypto Infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/pki-maturity-model-aims-to-improve-crypto-infrastructure</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/pki-maturity-model-aims-to-improve-crypto-infrastructure"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T15:23:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joining a growing group of cybersecurity-related "maturity models," PKIMM allows companies to measure their progress and benchmark themselves against other firms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Lemos, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[African Cybercrime Operations Shut Down in Law Enforcement Operation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/african-cybercrime-operations-taken-down-in-joint-interpol-afripol-effort</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/african-cybercrime-operations-taken-down-in-joint-interpol-afripol-effort"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Interpol- and Afripol-led crackdown disrupts cybercrime ecosystem responsible for some $40 million in losses to victims.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unveiling the Hidden Risks of Routing Protocols]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/unveiling-the-hidden-risks-of-routing-protocols</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/unveiling-the-hidden-risks-of-routing-protocols"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neglecting security of Border Gateway Protocol (BGP) and other routing protocols has created multiple vulnerabilities that must be addressed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel dos Santos, Head of Security Research, Forescout's Vedere Labs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MAR-10459736.r1.v1 WHIRLPOOL Backdoor]]></title>
        <id>/node/18646</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/analysis-reports/ar23-230a"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T13:38:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notification
This report is provided "as is" for informational purposes only. The Department of Homeland Security (DHS) does not provide any warranties of any kind regarding any information contained herein. The DHS does not endorse any commercial product or service referenced in this bulletin or otherwise.
This document is marked TLP:CLEAR--Recipients may share this information without restriction. Sources may use TLP:CLEAR when information carries minimal or no foreseeable risk of misuse, in accordance with applicable rules and procedures for public release. Subject to standard copyright rules, TLP:CLEAR information may be shared without restriction. For more information on the Traffic Light Protocol (TLP), see http://www.cisa.gov/tlp.
Summary
Description
CISA obtained a variant of the W…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[14 Suspected Cybercriminals Arrested Across Africa in Coordinated Crackdown]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/14-suspected-cybercriminals-arrested.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/14-suspected-cybercriminals-arrested.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T12:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A coordinated law enforcement operation across 25 African countries has led to the arrest of 14 suspected cybercriminals, INTERPOL announced Friday.
The exercise, conducted in partnership with AFRIPOL, enabled investigators to identify 20,674 cyber networks that were linked to financial losses of more than $40 million.
"The four-month Africa Cyber Surge II operation was launched in April 2023]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Juniper Releases Security Advisory for Multiple Vulnerabilities in Junos OS]]></title>
        <id>/node/18644</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/08/18/juniper-releases-security-advisory-multiple-vulnerabilities-junos-os"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Juniper has released a security advisory to address vulnerabilities in Junos OS on SRX Series and EX Series. A remote cyber threat actor could exploit these vulnerabilities to take control of an affected system.
CISA encourages users and administrators to review Juniper’s Support Portal and apply the necessary updates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Vulnerability of Zero Trust: Lessons from the Storm 0558 Hack]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/the-vulnerability-of-zero-trust-lessons.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/the-vulnerability-of-zero-trust-lessons.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T11:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While IT security managers in companies and public administrations rely on the concept of Zero Trust, APTS (Advanced Persistent Threats) are putting its practical effectiveness to the test. Analysts, on the other hand, understand that Zero Trust can only be achieved with comprehensive insight into one's own network. 
Just recently, an attack believed to be perpetrated by the Chinese hacker group]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Wave of Attack Campaign Targeting Zimbra Email Users for Credential Theft]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/new-wave-of-attack-campaign-targeting.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/new-wave-of-attack-campaign-targeting.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T11:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new "mass-spreading" social engineering campaign is targeting users of the Zimbra Collaboration email server with an aim to collect their login credentials for use in follow-on operations.
The activity, active since April 2023 and still ongoing, targets a wide range of small and medium businesses and governmental entities, most of which are located in Poland, Ecuador, Mexico, Italy, and Russia]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bots Are Better than Humans at Solving CAPTCHAs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/08/bots-are-better-than-humans-at-solving-captchas.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/08/bots-are-better-than-humans-at-solving-captchas.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T11:04:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Interesting research: &#8220;<a href="https://arxiv.org/pdf/2307.12108.pdf">An Empirical Study &#38; Evaluation of Modern CAPTCHAs</a>&#8220;:</p>
<blockquote><p><b>Abstract:</b> For nearly two decades, CAPTCHAS have been widely used as a means of protection against bots. Throughout the years, as their use grew, techniques to defeat or bypass CAPTCHAS have continued to improve. Meanwhile, CAPTCHAS have also evolved in terms of sophistication and diversity, becoming increasingly difficult to solve for both bots (machines) and humans. Given this long-standing and still-ongoing arms race, it is critical to investigate how long it takes legitimate users to solve modern CAPTCHAS, and how they are perceived by those users...</p></blockquote>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New BlackCat Ransomware Variant Adopts Advanced Impacket and RemCom Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/new-blackcat-ransomware-variant-adopts.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/new-blackcat-ransomware-variant-adopts.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T10:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft on Thursday disclosed that it found a new version of the BlackCat ransomware (aka ALPHV and Noberus) that embeds tools like Impacket and RemCom to facilitate lateral movement and remote code execution.
"The Impacket tool has credential dumping and remote service execution modules that could be used for broad deployment of the BlackCat ransomware in target environments," the company's]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Chrome's New Feature Alerts Users About Auto-Removal of Malicious Extensions]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/google-chromes-new-feature-alerts-users.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/google-chromes-new-feature-alerts-users.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T06:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has announced plans to add a new feature in the upcoming version of its Chrome web browser to proactively alert users when an extension they have installed has been removed from the Chrome Web Store.
The feature, set for release alongside Chrome 117, allows users to be notified when an add-on has been unpublished by a developer, taken down for violating Chrome Web Store policy, or marked]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fastly Launches Certainly CA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/fastly-launches-certainly-ca</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/fastly-launches-certainly-ca"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company’s moves to expand its TLS and domain name services strengthens the security and trust of its global web infrastructure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confusion Surrounds SEC's New Cybersecurity Material Rule]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge/confusion-surrounds-sec-new-cybersecurity-material-rule</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge/confusion-surrounds-sec-new-cybersecurity-material-rule"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Determining what to report and which details to disclose are complex questions with elusive answers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evan Schuman, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sophos: ‘Royal’ Is Trying to Make Itself the King of Ransomware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/sophos-royal-is-trying-to-make-itself-the-king-of-ransomware</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/sophos-royal-is-trying-to-make-itself-the-king-of-ransomware"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this Dark Reading News Desk segment, John Shier, Field CTO Commercial, Sophos, discusses the "Royal" ransomware.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel-US Binational Industrial R&D Foundation to Invest $3.85M in Critical Infrastructure Cybersecurity Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/israel-us-binational-industrial-r-d-foundation-to-invest-3-85m-in-critical-infrastructure-cybersecurity-projects</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/israel-us-binational-industrial-r-d-foundation-to-invest-3-85m-in-critical-infrastructure-cybersecurity-projects"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T20:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intelligent Vigilance: Empowering Security with Threat Intel's CoPilot AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/intelligent-vigilance-empowering-security-with-threat-intel-copilot-ai</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/intelligent-vigilance-empowering-security-with-threat-intel-copilot-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T20:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this Dark Reading News Desk segment, Cybersixgill's Michael-Angelo Zummo discusses how to empower security with AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco: Bringing More Intelligence to Bear on the Threat Landscape]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/cisco-bringing-more-intelligence-to-bear-on-the-threat-landscape</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/cisco-bringing-more-intelligence-to-bear-on-the-threat-landscape"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T20:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this Dark Reading News Desk segment, Nick Biasini from Cisco Talos discusses the latest attacker tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ISC2 Announces Milestone as Community Grows to Half a Million]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/isc2-announces-major-milestone-as-community-grows-to-half-a-million-strong</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/isc2-announces-major-milestone-as-community-grows-to-half-a-million-strong"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T20:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Foretrace Announces Launch of "Tim," Generative AI Analyst for Assessing and Responding to Data Leaks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/foretrace-announces-launch-of-tim-generative-ai-analyst-for-assessing-and-responding-to-data-leaks</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/foretrace-announces-launch-of-tim-generative-ai-analyst-for-assessing-and-responding-to-data-leaks"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T20:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Protect Against Nation-State APT Attackers Leveraging Mobile Users]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/mobile/how-to-protect-against-nation-state-apt-attackers-leveraging-mobile-users</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/mobile/how-to-protect-against-nation-state-apt-attackers-leveraging-mobile-users"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this Dark Reading News Desk segment, Lookout Mobile Security's Justin Albrecht discusses APT attacks targeting mobile users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Securing Critical Infrastructure in the Face of Evolving Cyber Threats]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/ics-ot/securing-critical-infrastructure-in-the-face-of-evolving-cyber-threats</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/ics-ot/securing-critical-infrastructure-in-the-face-of-evolving-cyber-threats"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T20:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this Dark Reading News Desk segment, OPSWAT founder Benny Czarny outlines the threat landscape affecting critical infrastructure sectors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitsight Leverages SPM to Bolster External Attack Surface Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/bitsight-leverages-spm-to-bolster-external-attack-surface-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/bitsight-leverages-spm-to-bolster-external-attack-surface-security"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T20:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this Dark Reading News Desk segment, BitSight's Gregory Keshian discusses external attack surface management and security performance management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CrowdSec: What the 'Network Effect' Brings to the Cybersecurity Table]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/crowdsec-what-network-effect-brings-to-cybersecurity-table</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/crowdsec-what-network-effect-brings-to-cybersecurity-table"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T20:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this Dark Reading News Desk segment, CrowdSec CEO/co-founder Philippe Humeau discusses how the concept of a network effect applies to threat management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6301-1: Linux kernel vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6301-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6301-1"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T20:11:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was discovered that the netlink implementation in the Linux kernel did
not properly validate policies when parsing attributes in some situations.
An attacker could use this to cause a denial of service (infinite
recursion). (CVE-2020-36691)

Billy Jheng Bing Jhong discovered that the CIFS network file system
implementation in the Linux kernel did not properly validate arguments to
ioctl() in some situations. A local attacker could possibly use this to
cause a denial of service (system crash). (CVE-2022-0168)

It was discovered that the ext4 file system implementation in the Linux
kernel contained a use-after-free vulnerability. An attacker could use this
to construct a malicious ext4 file system image that, when mounted, could
cause a denial of service (system crash). (CVE-2022-1184)

I…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TXOne: How to Improve Your Operational Technology Security Posture]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/ics-ot/txone-how-to-improve-your-operational-technology-security-posture</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/ics-ot/txone-how-to-improve-your-operational-technology-security-posture"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T20:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this Dark Reading News Desk segment, Terence Liu of TXOne Networks discusses operational technology and industrial cybersecurity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cribl, Exabeam Partner on Threat Detection, Investigation, and Response]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/cribl-exabeam-partner-on-threat-detection-investigation-and-response</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/cribl-exabeam-partner-on-threat-detection-investigation-and-response"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T20:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this Dark Reading News Desk segment, Cribl's Abby Strong and Exabeam's Chris Cesio discuss how their companies work together to detect and respond to threats.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Infoblox Blows Whistle On ‘Decoy Dog,’ Advocates For Better DNS Monitoring]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/infoblox-blows-whistle-on-decoy-dog-advocates-for-better-dns-monitoring</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/infoblox-blows-whistle-on-decoy-dog-advocates-for-better-dns-monitoring"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T20:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this Dark Reading News Desk segment, Infoblox's Dr. Renée Burton discusses why better DNS monitoring is so important.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qualys Offers Threat Forecast For Cloud, and Tips For Reducing Cloud Risks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/qualys-offers-threat-forecast-for-cloud-and-tips-for-reducing-cloud-risks</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/qualys-offers-threat-forecast-for-cloud-and-tips-for-reducing-cloud-risks"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T20:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this Dark Reading News Desk segment, Qualys CEO and president Sumedh Thakar offers advice on reducing cloud risks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interpres: Getting the Most Out of Threat Intelligence Resources]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/interpres-getting-the-most-out-of-threat-intelligence-resources</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/interpres-getting-the-most-out-of-threat-intelligence-resources"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T20:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this Dark Reading News Desk segment, Interpres Security's Nick Lantuh discusses how security practitioners can get the most out of various threat intelligence offerings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Normalyze: How Focusing on Data Can Improve Cloud Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/normalyze-how-focusing-on-data-can-improve-cloud-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/normalyze-how-focusing-on-data-can-improve-cloud-security"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this Dark Reading News Desk segment, Normalyze’s Ravi Ithal discusses cloud security and data security posture management (DPSM).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6300-1: Linux kernel vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6300-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6300-1"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T19:58:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[William Zhao discovered that the Traffic Control (TC) subsystem in the
Linux kernel did not properly handle network packet retransmission in
certain situations. A local attacker could use this to cause a denial of
service (kernel deadlock). (CVE-2022-4269)

It was discovered that the NTFS file system implementation in the Linux
kernel did not properly check buffer indexes in certain situations, leading
to an out-of-bounds read vulnerability. A local attacker could possibly use
this to expose sensitive information (kernel memory). (CVE-2022-48502)

Seth Jenkins discovered that the Linux kernel did not properly perform
address randomization for a per-cpu memory management structure. A local
attacker could use this to expose sensitive information (kernel memory)
or in conjunction with another…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[White House Orders Federal Agencies to Bolster Cyber Safeguards]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/white-house-orders-federal-agencies-to-bolster-cyber-safeguards</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/white-house-orders-federal-agencies-to-bolster-cyber-safeguards"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Biden administration adviser puts federal departments and agencies on notice to come into full compliance with presidential guidelines by the end of the year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Trick an iPhone Into Faking Airplane Mode]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/researchers-trick-iphone-faking-airplane-mode</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/researchers-trick-iphone-faking-airplane-mode"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T17:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How mobile attackers could gaslight iPhone users, allowing the perfect cover for post-exploitation malicious activity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Overview of Dubai's First and Second Cybersecurity Strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/overview-dubais-first-and-second-cybersecurity-strategy</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/overview-dubais-first-and-second-cybersecurity-strategy"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security demands a strong fortress in cyberspace, and Dubai has rolled out two cybersecurity strategies to protect the data of the government and citizens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diamaka Aniagolu, Cybersecurity Writer and Content Strategist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LinkedIn Suffers 'Significant' Wave of Account Hacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/linkedin-suffers-significant-wave-of-account-hacks</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/linkedin-suffers-significant-wave-of-account-hacks"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T16:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Users report losing access to their accounts, with some being pressured into paying a ransom to get back in or else face permanent account deletion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Montalbano, Contributor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NoFilter Attack: Sneaky Privilege Escalation Method Bypasses Windows Security]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/nofilter-attack-sneaky-privilege.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/nofilter-attack-sneaky-privilege.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T16:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A previously undetected attack method called NoFilter has been found to abuse the Windows Filtering Platform (WFP) to achieve privilege escalation in the Windows operating system.
"If an attacker has the ability to execute code with admin privilege and the target is to perform LSASS Shtinkering, these privileges are not enough," Ron Ben Yizhak, a security researcher at Deep Instinct, told The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China-Linked Bronze Starlight Group Targeting Gambling Sector with Cobalt Strike Beacons]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/china-linked-bronze-starlight-group.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/china-linked-bronze-starlight-group.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An ongoing cyber attack campaign originating from China is targeting the Southeast Asian gambling sector to deploy Cobalt Strike beacons on compromised systems. 
Cybersecurity firm SentinelOne said the tactics, techniques, and procedures point to the involvement of a threat actor tracked as Bronze Starlight (aka Emperor Dragonfly or Storm-0401), which has been linked to the use of short-lived]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Play' Ransomware Group Targeting MSPs Worldwide in New Campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/-play-ransomware-group-targeting-msps-worldwide-in-new-campaign</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/-play-ransomware-group-targeting-msps-worldwide-in-new-campaign"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T15:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attackers use remote monitoring and management tools at MSPs to gain unfettered access to target networks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Apple iOS 16 Exploit Enables Stealthy Cellular Access Under Fake Airplane Mode]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/new-apple-ios-16-exploit-enables.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/new-apple-ios-16-exploit-enables.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T14:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have documented a novel post-exploit persistence technique on iOS 16 that could be abused to fly under the radar and maintain access to an Apple device even when the victim believes it is offline.
The method "tricks the victim into thinking their device's Airplane Mode works when in reality the attacker (following successful device exploit) has planted an artificial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New LABRAT Campaign Exploits GitLab Flaw for Cryptojacking and Proxyjacking Activities]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/new-labrat-campaign-exploits-gitlab.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/new-labrat-campaign-exploits-gitlab.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T14:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new, financially motivated operation dubbed LABRAT has been observed weaponizing a now-patched critical flaw in GitLab as part of a cryptojacking and proxyjacking campaign.
"The attacker utilized undetected signature-based tools, sophisticated and stealthy cross-platform malware, command-and-control (C2) tools which bypassed firewalls, and kernel-based rootkits to hide their presence," Sysdig]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Innovation Accelerators Are at Work on the Dark Side]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/how-innovation-accelerators-are-at-work-on-the-dark-side</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/how-innovation-accelerators-are-at-work-on-the-dark-side"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Digital commerce remains the richest target for cybercriminals, yet physical payment threats remain strong.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Fabara, Chief Risk Officer, Visa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cyber Defenders Lead the AI Arms Race for Now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/cyber-defenders-lead-the-ai-arms</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/cyber-defenders-lead-the-ai-arms"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cyberattackers are slow to implement AI in their attack chains, according to Mandiant's analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Atlassian Releases Security Update for Confluence Server and Data Center]]></title>
        <id>/node/18631</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/08/17/atlassian-releases-security-update-confluence-server-and-data-center"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Atlassian has released its security bulletin for August 2023 to address a vulnerability in Confluence Server and Data Center, CVE-2023-28709. A remote attacker can exploit this vulnerability to cause a denial-of-service condition.
CISA encourages users and administrators to review Atlassian’s August 2003 Security Bulletin and apply the necessary update.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco Releases Security Advisories for Multiple Products]]></title>
        <id>/node/18636</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/08/17/cisco-releases-security-advisories-multiple-products"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco has released security advisories for vulnerabilities affecting multiple Cisco products. A cyber threat actor can exploit some of these vulnerabilities to take control of an affected system or cause a denial-of service condition.
CISA encourages users and administrators to review the following advisories and apply the necessary updates.
ThousandEyes Enterprise Agent
Duo Device Health Application
Unified CM
ClamAV HFS+
ClamAV]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why You Need Continuous Network Monitoring?]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/why-you-need-continuous-network.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/why-you-need-continuous-network.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T11:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changes in the way we work have had significant implications for cybersecurity, not least in network monitoring. Workers no longer sit safely side-by-side on a corporate network, dev teams constantly spin up and tear down systems, exposing services to the internet. Keeping track of these users, changes and services is difficult – internet-facing attack surfaces rarely stay the same for long.
But]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detecting “Violations of Social Norms” in Text with AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/08/detecting-violations-of-social-norms-in-text-with-ai.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/08/detecting-violations-of-social-norms-in-text-with-ai.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T11:07:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Researchers are trying to use AI to <a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-023-35350-x">detect</a> &#8220;social norms violations.&#8221; Feels a little sketchy right now, but this is the sort of thing that AIs will get better at. (Like all of these systems, anything but a very low false positive rate makes the detection useless in practice.)</p>
<p>News <a href="https://gizmodo.com/ai-text-social-norms-violations-pentagon-darpa-study-1850673979">article</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian Hackers Use Zulip Chat App for Covert C&C in Diplomatic Phishing Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/russian-hackers-use-zulip-chat-app-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/russian-hackers-use-zulip-chat-app-for.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T09:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An ongoing campaign targeting ministries of foreign affairs of NATO-aligned countries points to the involvement of Russian threat actors.
The phishing attacks feature PDF documents with diplomatic lures, some of which are disguised as coming from Germany, to deliver a variant of a malware called Duke, which has been attributed to APT29 (aka BlueBravo, Cloaked Ursa, Cozy Bear, Iron Hemlock,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Adds Citrix ShareFile Flaw to KEV Catalog Due to In-the-Wild Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/cisa-adds-citrix-sharefile-flaw-to-kev.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/cisa-adds-citrix-sharefile-flaw-to-kev.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T05:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has added a critical security flaw in Citrix ShareFile storage zones controller to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, based on evidence of active in-the-wild exploitation.
Tracked as CVE-2023-24489 (CVSS score: 9.8), the shortcoming has been described as an improper access control bug that, if successfully exploited]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PowerShell Gallery Prone to Typosquatting, Other Supply Chain Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/powershell-gallery-prone-to-typosquatting-other-supply-chain-attacks</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/powershell-gallery-prone-to-typosquatting-other-supply-chain-attacks"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is aware of the issue, but so far its attempts to address it don't appear to have worked, researchers say.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 AI Risk and Resilience Firms CISOs Should Track]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge-slideshows/8-ai-risk-and-resilience-firms-cisos-should-track</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge-slideshows/8-ai-risk-and-resilience-firms-cisos-should-track"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out our list of emerging firms that are building technology and services to assess the risk posture of AI systems and ML models.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ericka Chickowski, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Citrix ADC, Gateways Still Backdoored, Even After Being Patched]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge-threat-monitor/citrix-adc-gateways-still-backdoored-even-after-being-patched</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge-threat-monitor/citrix-adc-gateways-still-backdoored-even-after-being-patched"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even after updating Citrix networking appliances to address the critical vulnerability, enterprise defenders have to check each one to ensure they have not already been compromised.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edge Editors, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Harvest, Analyze 100K Cybercrime Forum Credentials]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/dark-web-forums-leak-100k-hacker-ids</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/dark-web-forums-leak-100k-hacker-ids"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T21:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers found that many Dark Web forums have stronger password rules than most government and military entities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dig Security State of Cloud Data Security 2023 Report Finds Exposed Sensitive Data in More Than 30% of Cloud Assets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/dig-security-state-of-cloud-data-security-2023-report-finds-exposed-sensitive-data-in-more-than-30-of-cloud-assets-</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/dig-security-state-of-cloud-data-security-2023-report-finds-exposed-sensitive-data-in-more-than-30-of-cloud-assets-"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T21:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[67% of Federal Government Agencies Are Confident in Meeting Zero Trust Executive Order Deadline]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/67-of-federal-government-agencies-are-confident-in-meeting-zero-trust-executive-order-deadline</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/67-of-federal-government-agencies-are-confident-in-meeting-zero-trust-executive-order-deadline"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T21:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Call for Applications Open for DataTribe's Sixth Annual Cybersecurity Startup Challenge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/careers-and-people/call-for-applications-open-for-datatribe-s-sixth-annual-cybersecurity-startup-challenge</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/careers-and-people/call-for-applications-open-for-datatribe-s-sixth-annual-cybersecurity-startup-challenge"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T21:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Insurance Data Breach Victims File Class-Action Suit Against Law Firm]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/class-action-lawsuit-follows-major-law-firm-data-breach</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/class-action-lawsuit-follows-major-law-firm-data-breach"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T21:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This time, it's the law firm that got breached, then sued for what victims claim was inadequate protection and compensation for theft of personal data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond Identity Launches Passkey Adoption Tool, The Passkey Journey]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/beyond-identity-launches-new-passkey-adoption-tool-the-passkey-journey</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/beyond-identity-launches-new-passkey-adoption-tool-the-passkey-journey"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mirai Common Attack Methods Remain Consistent, Effective]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/mirai-common-attack-methods-remain-consistent-effective</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/mirai-common-attack-methods-remain-consistent-effective"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While relatively unchanged, the notorious IoT botnet still continues to drive DDoS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Montalbano, Contributor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Gulf's Dizzying Tech Ambitions Present Risk & Opportunity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/the-gulfs-dizzying-tech-ambitions-present-risk-opportunity</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/the-gulfs-dizzying-tech-ambitions-present-risk-opportunity"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threats and opportunities abound for the UAE and Gulf states, so can they deal with being a cybersecurity stronghold?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cathy Simms, Cybersecurity Writer &amp; Columnist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VU#287122: Parsec Remote Desktop App is prone to a local elevation of privilege due to a logical flaw in its code integrity verification process]]></title>
        <id>https://kb.cert.org/vuls/id/287122</id>
        <link href="https://kb.cert.org/vuls/id/287122"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T16:18:56.828Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="overview">Overview</h3>
<p>Parsec updater for Windows was prone to a local privilege escalation vulnerability, this vulnerability allowed a local user with Parsec access to gain NT_AUTHORITY/SYSTEM privileges.</p>
<h3 id="description">Description</h3>
<p>The vulnerability is a time-of-check time–of-use (TOCTOU) vulnerability. There existed a small window between verifying the signature and integrity of the update DLL and the execution of DLL main. </p>
<p>By exploiting this race condition, a local attacker could swap out the officially signed Parsec DLL with a DLL that they created, which would subsequently be executed as the SYSTEM user as described in CVE-2023-37250.</p>
<p><strong>CVE-2023-37250</strong>
The application launches DLLs from a User owned directory. Since the user owns both the DLL file and the directory, it is possible to (successfully) attempt tricking Parsec into loading an unsigned/arbitrary DLL file and execute its DllMain() method with SYSTEM privileges, creating a Local Privilege Escalation vulnerability.</p>
<h3 id="impact">Impact</h3>
<p>By exploiting this race condition, a local attacker could swap out the officially signed Parsec DLL with a DLL that they created, which would subsequently be executed as the SYSTEM user.</p>
<h3 id="solution">Solution</h3>
<p>The vulnerability applies to a "Per User" installation as opposed to a "Shared User". There is an update that has been made available. To force an update, you can either completely quit, and re-open the application several times until the loader is updated (by confirming in the logs). Or you can download a special installer that only updates the files inside of the program files that can be downloaded from https://builds.parsec.app/package/parsec-update-executables.exe.</p>
<h3 id="acknowledgements">Acknowledgements</h3>
<p>Thanks to the reporter, Julian Horoszkiewicz.This document was written by Timur Snoke.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT Recently Published Vulnerability Notes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's the State of Credential theft in 2023?]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/whats-state-of-credential-theft-in-2023.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/whats-state-of-credential-theft-in-2023.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T11:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At a little overt halfway through 2023, credential theft is still a major thorn in the side of IT teams. The heart of the problem is the value of data to cybercriminals and the evolution of the techniques they use to get hold of it. The 2023 Verizon Data Breach Investigations Report (DBIR) revealed that 83% of breaches involved external actors, with almost all attacks being financially motivated]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Experts Uncover Weaknesses in PowerShell Gallery Enabling Supply Chain Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/experts-uncover-weaknesses-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/experts-uncover-weaknesses-in.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T11:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Active flaws in the PowerShell Gallery could be weaponized by threat actors to pull off supply chain attacks against the registry's users.
"These flaws make typosquatting attacks inevitable in this registry, while also making it extremely difficult for users to identify the true owner of a package," Aqua security researchers Mor Weinberger, Yakir Kadkoda, and Ilay Goldman said in a report shared]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK Electoral Commission Hacked]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/08/uk-electoral-commission-hacked.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/08/uk-electoral-commission-hacked.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T11:17:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The UK Electoral Commission discovered last year that it was <a href="https://www.electoralcommission.org.uk/privacy-policy/public-notification-cyber-attack-electoral-commission-systems/information-about-cyber-attack">hacked</a> the year before. That&#8217;s fourteen months between the hack and the discovery. It doesn&#8217;t know who was behind the hack.</p>
<blockquote><p>We worked with external security experts and the National Cyber Security Centre to investigate and secure our systems.</p></blockquote>
<p>If the hack was by a major government, the odds are really low that it has resecured its systems&#8212;unless it burned the network to the ground and rebuilt it from scratch (which seems unlikely).</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Guide: How Google Workspace-based Organizations can leverage Chrome to improve Security]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/guide-how-google-workspace-based.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/guide-how-google-workspace-based.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T11:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More and more organizations are choosing Google Workspace as their default employee toolset of choice. But despite the productivity advantages, this organizational action also incurs a new security debt. Security teams now have to find a way to adjust their security architecture to this new cloud workload.
Some teams may rely on their existing network security solutions. According to a new guide]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Introduces First Quantum Resilient FIDO2 Security Key Implementation]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/google-introduces-first-quantum.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/google-introduces-first-quantum.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T10:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google on Tuesday announced the first quantum resilient FIDO2 security key implementation as part of its OpenSK security keys initiative.
"This open-source hardware optimized implementation uses a novel ECC/Dilithium hybrid signature schema that benefits from the security of ECC against standard attacks and Dilithium's resilience against quantum attacks," Elie Bursztein and Fabian Kaczmarczyck]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Security Flaws Affect Ivanti Avalanche, Threatening 30,000 Organizations]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/critical-security-flaws-affect-ivanti.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/critical-security-flaws-affect-ivanti.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T10:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple critical security flaws have been reported in Ivanti Avalanche, an enterprise mobile device management solution that’s used by 30,000 organizations.
The vulnerabilities, collectively tracked as CVE-2023-32560 (CVSS score: 9.8), are stack-based buffer overflows in Ivanti Avalanche WLAvanacheServer.exe v6.4.0.0.
Cybersecurity company Tenable said the shortcomings are the result of buffer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly 2,000 Citrix NetScaler Instances Hacked via Critical Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/nearly-2000-citrix-netscaler-instances.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/nearly-2000-citrix-netscaler-instances.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T04:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly 2,000 Citrix NetScaler instances have been compromised with a backdoor by weaponizing a recently disclosed critical security vulnerability as part of a large-scale attack.
"An adversary appears to have exploited CVE-2023-3519 in an automated fashion, placing web shells on vulnerable NetScalers to gain persistent access," NCC Group said in an advisory released Tuesday.
"The adversary can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybercriminals Abusing Cloudflare R2 for Hosting Phishing Pages, Experts Warn]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/cybercriminals-abusing-cloudflare-r2.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/cybercriminals-abusing-cloudflare-r2.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T18:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors' use of Cloudflare R2 to host phishing pages has witnessed a 61-fold increase over the past six months.
"The majority of the phishing campaigns target Microsoft login credentials, although there are some pages targeting Adobe, Dropbox, and other cloud apps," Netskope security researcher Jan Michael said.
Cloudflare R2, analogous to Amazon Web Service S3, Google Cloud Storage, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Catching the Catphish: Join the Expert Webinar on Combating Credential Phishing]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/catching-catphish-join-expert-webinar.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/08/catching-catphish-join-expert-webinar.html"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T18:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is your organization constantly under threat from credential phishing? Even with comprehensive security awareness training, many employees still fall victim to credential phishing scams.
The result? Cybercriminals gaining immediate and unhindered access to sensitive data, email accounts, and other applications. But what if you could outsmart these criminals and protect your organization?
Join]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerability Summary for the Week of August 7, 2023]]></title>
        <id>/node/18623</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/bulletins/sb23-226"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T11:56:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[High Vulnerabilities

Primary
Description
Published
CVSS Score
Source & Patch Info


			phoenixcontact -- wp_6xxx_series
In PHOENIX CONTACTs WP 6xxx series web panels in versions prior to 4.0.10 a remote attacker with low privileges may use an attribute of a specific HTTP POST request releated to date/time operations to gain full access to the device.
2023-08-08
9.9
CVE-2023-3572
MISC

qualcomm_inc. -- snapdragon
Memory corruption due to buffer copy without checking size of input in Audio while voice call with EVS vocoder.
2023-08-08
9.8
CVE-2022-40510
MISC

microsoft -- exchange_server
Microsoft Exchange Server Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability
2023-08-08
9.8
CVE-2023-21709
MISC

joomla -- joomla
Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulne…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VU#127587: Python Parsing Error Enabling Bypass CVE-2023-24329]]></title>
        <id>https://kb.cert.org/vuls/id/127587</id>
        <link href="https://kb.cert.org/vuls/id/127587"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T22:22:46.010Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="overview">Overview</h3>
<p>urllib.parse is a very basic and widely used basic URL parsing function in various applications.</p>
<h3 id="description">Description</h3>
<p>An issue in the urllib.parse component of Python before v3.11 allows attackers to bypass blocklisting methods by supplying a URL that starts with blank characters.</p>
<p>urlparse has a parsing problem when the entire URL starts with blank characters. This problem affects both the parsing of hostname and scheme, and eventually causes any blocklisting methods to fail.</p>
<p><strong>URL Parsing Security</strong> *</p>
<p>The <a href="https://docs.python.org/3/library/urllib.parse.html#urllib.parse.urlsplit" title="urllib.parse.urlsplit"><code>urlsplit()</code></a> and <a href="https://docs.python.org/3/library/urllib.parse.html#urllib.parse.urlparse" title="urllib.parse.urlparse"><code>urlparse()</code></a> APIs do not perform <strong>validation</strong> of inputs. They may not raise errors on inputs that other applications consider invalid. They may also succeed on some inputs that might not be considered URLs elsewhere. Their purpose is for practical functionality rather than purity.</p>
<p>Instead of raising an exception on unusual input, they may instead return some component parts as empty strings. Or components may contain more than perhaps they should.</p>
<p>We recommend that users of these APIs where the values may be used anywhere with security implications code defensively. Do some verification within your code before trusting a returned component part. Does that <code>scheme</code> make sense? Is that a sensible <code>path</code>? Is there anything strange about that<code>hostname</code>? etc.</p>
<p>What constitutes a URL is not universally well defined. Different applications have different needs and desired constraints. For instance the living <a href="https://url.spec.whatwg.org/#concept-basic-url-parser">WHATWG spec</a> describes what user facing web clients such as a web browser require. While <a href="https://datatracker.ietf.org/doc/html/rfc3986.html"><strong>RFC 3986</strong></a> is more general. These functions incorporate some aspects of both, but cannot be claimed compliant with either. The APIs and existing user code with expectations on specific behaviors predate both standards leading us to be very cautious about making API behavior changes.</p>
<p>*Note: This was added as part of the documentation update in https://github.com/python/cpython/pull/102508</p>
<h3 id="impact">Impact</h3>
<p>Due to this issue, attackers can bypass any domain or protocol filtering method implemented with a blocklist. Protocol filtering failures can lead to arbitrary file reads, arbitrary command execution, SSRF, and other problems. Failure of domain name filtering may lead to re-access of blocked bad or dangerous websites or to failure of CSRF referer type defense, etc.</p>
<p>Because this vulnerability exists in the most basic parsing library, more advanced issues are possible.</p>
<h3 id="solution">Solution</h3>
<p>The fixes are in the following releases:
</p><p>fixed in &gt;= 3.12
<br>fixed in 3.11.x &gt;= 3.11.4
<br>fixed in 3.10.x &gt;= 3.10.12
<br>fixed in 3.9.x &gt;= 3.9.17
<br>fixed in 3.8.x &gt;= 3.8.17
<br>fixed in 3.7.x &gt;= 3.7.17</p><p></p>
<h3 id="acknowledgements">Acknowledgements</h3>
<p>Thanks to the reporter, Yebo Cao for researching and reporting this vulnerability.</p>
<p>This document was written by Ben Koo.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT Recently Published Vulnerability Notes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Serial Console Attack and Defense - Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://msrc.microsoft.com/blog/2023/08/azure-serial-console-attack-and-defense-part-1/</id>
        <link href="https://msrc.microsoft.com/blog/2023/08/azure-serial-console-attack-and-defense-part-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever had a virtual machine crash? Azure Serial console is a great way to directly connect to your Virtual machine and debug what went wrong. Azure Serial Console is a feature that’s available for free for everyone. While the primary intent of this feature is to assist users debug their machine, there are several interesting ways to abuse the features and compromise sensitive information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Microsoft Security Response Center</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MAR-10454006.r4.v2 SEASPY and WHIRLPOOL Backdoors]]></title>
        <id>/node/18600</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/analysis-reports/ar23-221a"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T16:50:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notification
This report is provided "as is" for informational purposes only. The Department of Homeland Security (DHS) does not provide any warranties of any kind regarding any information contained herein. The DHS does not endorse any commercial product or service referenced in this bulletin or otherwise.
This document is marked TLP:CLEAR--Recipients may share this information without restriction. Sources may use TLP:CLEAR when information carries minimal or no foreseeable risk of misuse, in accordance with applicable rules and procedures for public release. Subject to standard copyright rules, TLP:CLEAR information may be shared without restriction. For more information on the Traffic Light Protocol (TLP), see http://www.cisa.gov/tlp.
Summary
Description
CISA obtained four malware sampl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Congratulations to the MSRC 2023 Most Valuable Security Researchers!]]></title>
        <id>https://msrc.microsoft.com/blog/2023/08/congratulations-to-the-msrc-2023-most-valuable-security-researchers/</id>
        <link href="https://msrc.microsoft.com/blog/2023/08/congratulations-to-the-msrc-2023-most-valuable-security-researchers/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Microsoft Researcher Recognition Program offers public thanks and recognition to security researchers who help protect our customers through discovering and sharing security vulnerabilities under Coordinated Vulnerability Disclosure.
Today, we are excited to recognize this year’s top 100 Most Valuable Researchers (MVRs) based on the total number of points earned for each valid report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Microsoft Security Response Center</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Updating our Vulnerability Severity Classification for AI Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://msrc.microsoft.com/blog/2023/08/Updating-our-Vulnerability-Severity-Classification-for-AI-Systems/</id>
        <link href="https://msrc.microsoft.com/blog/2023/08/Updating-our-Vulnerability-Severity-Classification-for-AI-Systems/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Microsoft Security Response Center (MSRC) is always looking for ways to provide clarity and transparency around how we assess the impact of vulnerabilities reported in our products and services. To this end, we are announcing the Microsoft Vulnerability Severity Classification for AI Systems, an update to Microsoft’s existing vulnerability severity classification (i.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Microsoft Security Response Center</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VU#947701: Freewill Solutions IFIS new trading web application vulnerable to unauthenticated remote code execution]]></title>
        <id>https://kb.cert.org/vuls/id/947701</id>
        <link href="https://kb.cert.org/vuls/id/947701"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T15:57:00.716Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="overview">Overview</h3>
<p>Freewill Solutions IFIS new trading web application version 20.01.01.04 is vulnerable to unauthenticated remote code execution. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability allows an attacker to run arbitrary shell commands on the affected host.</p>
<h3 id="description">Description</h3>
<p>Freewill Solutions IFIS new trading web application passes a user controlled variable directly to a shell_exec function call on a specific report page. To exploit the vulnerability, an attacker can add shell meta characters to the user controlled variable so that the application executes attacker specified commands.</p>
<h3 id="impact">Impact</h3>
<p>An attacker with access to the applications web interface can execute code on the remote host. This level of access allows for complete compromise of the affected machine.</p>
<h3 id="solution">Solution</h3>
<p>The CERT/CC is currently unaware of a practical solution to this problem.</p>
<h3 id="acknowledgements">Acknowledgements</h3>
<p>Thanks to Sameer Mohite (Mandiant) for reporting the vulnerability.</p>
<p>This document was written by Kevin Stephens.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT Recently Published Vulnerability Notes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerability Summary for the Week of July 31, 2023]]></title>
        <id>/node/18580</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/bulletins/sb23-219"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T12:21:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[High Vulnerabilities

Primary
Description
Published
CVSS Score
Source & Patch Info

yunyecms -- yunyecms
SQL injection vulnerability in yunyecms 2.0.2 allows remote attackers to run arbitrary SQL commands via XFF.
2023-07-31
9.8
CVE-2020-21662
MISC

raspap -- raspap
A Command injection vulnerability in RaspAP 2.8.0 thru 2.8.7 allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary commands via the cfg_id parameter in /ajax/openvpn/activate_ovpncfg.php and /ajax/openvpn/del_ovpncfg.php.
2023-08-01
9.8
CVE-2022-39986
MISC
MISC

tp-link -- archer_ax21_firmware
TP-Link Archer AX21(US)_V3_1.1.4 Build 20230219 and AX21(US)_V3.6_1.1.4 Build 20230219 are vulnerable to Buffer Overflow.
2023-08-01
9.8
CVE-2023-31710
MISC

synel -- synergy_fingerprint_terminals
Synel SYnergy Fingerprint Terminals - CWE…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Bug Bounty Program Year in Review: $13.8M in Rewards]]></title>
        <id>https://msrc.microsoft.com/blog/2023/08/microsoft-bug-bounty-program-year-in-review-13.8m-in-rewards/</id>
        <link href="https://msrc.microsoft.com/blog/2023/08/microsoft-bug-bounty-program-year-in-review-13.8m-in-rewards/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are thrilled to share the results of our collaboration with over 345 security researchers from +45 countries around the world in the past 12 months. Together, we have discovered and fixed more than a thousand potential security issues before they impacted our customers. In recognition of this valuable collaboration, we have awarded $13.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Microsoft Security Response Center</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft mitigates Power Platform Custom Code information disclosure vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://msrc.microsoft.com/blog/2023/08/microsoft-mitigates-power-platform-custom-code-information-disclosure-vulnerability/</id>
        <link href="https://msrc.microsoft.com/blog/2023/08/microsoft-mitigates-power-platform-custom-code-information-disclosure-vulnerability/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summary Summary On 30 March 2023, Tenable informed Microsoft under Coordinated Vulnerability Disclosure (CVD) of a security issue concerning Power Platform Custom Connectors using Custom Code. This feature allows customers to write code for custom connectors. This issue has been fully addressed for all customers and no customer remediation action is required.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Microsoft Security Response Center</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2022 Top Routinely Exploited Vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>/node/18564</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/cybersecurity-advisories/aa23-215a"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T18:57:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUMMARY
The following cybersecurity agencies coauthored this joint Cybersecurity Advisory (CSA):
United States: The Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA), National Security Agency (NSA), and Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI)
Australia: Australian Signals Directorate’s Australian Cyber Security Centre (ACSC)
Canada: Canadian Centre for Cyber Security (CCCS)
New Zealand: New Zealand National Cyber Security Centre (NCSC-NZ) and Computer Emergency Response Team New Zealand (CERT NZ)
United Kingdom: National Cyber Security Centre (NCSC-UK)
This advisory provides details on the Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVEs) routinely and frequently exploited by malicious cyber actors in 2022 and the associated Common Weakness Enumeration(s) (CWE). In 2022, malicious cyber acto…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Threat Actors Exploiting Ivanti EPMM Vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>/node/18559</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/cybersecurity-advisories/aa23-213a"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T14:42:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUMMARY
The Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) and the Norwegian National Cyber Security Centre (NCSC-NO) are releasing this joint Cybersecurity Advisory (CSA) in response to active exploitation of CVE-2023-35078 and CVE-2023-35081. Advanced persistent threat (APT) actors exploited CVE-2023-35078 as a zero day from at least April 2023 through July 2023 to gather information from several Norwegian organizations, as well as to gain access to and compromise a Norwegian government agency’s network.
Ivanti released a patch for CVE-2023-35078 on July 23, 2023. Ivanti later determined actors could use CVE-2023-35078 in conjunction with another vulnerability CVE-2023-35081 and released a patch for the second vulnerability on July 28, 2023. NCSC-NO observed possible vulnerabili…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerability Summary for the Week of July 24, 2023]]></title>
        <id>/node/18551</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/bulletins/sb23-212"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T13:27:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[High Vulnerabilities

Primary
Description
Published
CVSS Score
Source & Patch Info

biltay_technology -- scienta
Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Biltay Technology Scienta allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Scienta: before 20230630.1953.
2023-07-25
9.8
CVE-2023-3046
MISC

infodrom_software -- e-invoice_approval_system
Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Infodrom Software E-Invoice Approval System allows SQL Injection.This issue affects E-Invoice Approval System: before v.20230701.
2023-07-25
9.8
CVE-2023-35066
MISC

house_rental_and_property_listing_php_project -- house_rental_and_property_listing_php
A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MAR-10454006-r3.v1 Exploit Payload Backdoor]]></title>
        <id>/node/18539</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/analysis-reports/ar23-209c"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T17:11:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notification
This report is provided "as is" for informational purposes only. The Department of Homeland Security (DHS) does not provide any warranties of any kind regarding any information contained herein. The DHS does not endorse any commercial product or service referenced in this bulletin or otherwise.
This document is marked TLP:CLEAR--Recipients may share this information without restriction. Sources may use TLP:CLEAR when information carries minimal or no foreseeable risk of misuse, in accordance with applicable rules and procedures for public release. Subject to standard copyright rules, TLP:CLEAR information may be shared without restriction. For more information on the Traffic Light Protocol (TLP), see http://www.cisa.gov/tlp.
Summary
Description
CISA obtained 14 malware samples…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MAR-10454006-r2.v1 SEASPY Backdoor]]></title>
        <id>/node/18537</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/analysis-reports/ar23-209b"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T17:08:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notification
This report is provided "as is" for informational purposes only. The Department of Homeland Security (DHS) does not provide any warranties of any kind regarding any information contained herein. The DHS does not endorse any commercial product or service referenced in this bulletin or otherwise.
This document is marked TLP:CLEAR--Recipients may share this information without restriction. Sources may use TLP:CLEAR when information carries minimal or no foreseeable risk of misuse, in accordance with applicable rules and procedures for public release. Subject to standard copyright rules, TLP:CLEAR information may be shared without restriction. For more information on the Traffic Light Protocol (TLP), see http://www.cisa.gov/tlp.
Summary
Description
CISA obtained two SEASPY malware…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MAR-10454006-r1.v2 SUBMARINE Backdoor]]></title>
        <id>/node/18536</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/analysis-reports/ar23-209a"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T17:03:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notification
This report is provided "as is" for informational purposes only. The Department of Homeland Security (DHS) does not provide any warranties of any kind regarding any information contained herein. The DHS does not endorse any commercial product or service referenced in this bulletin or otherwise.
This document is marked TLP:CLEAR--Recipients may share this information without restriction. Sources may use TLP:CLEAR when information carries minimal or no foreseeable risk of misuse, in accordance with applicable rules and procedures for public release. Subject to standard copyright rules, TLP:CLEAR information may be shared without restriction. For more information on the Traffic Light Protocol (TLP), see http://www.cisa.gov/tlp.
Summary
Description
CISA obtained seven malware samp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VU#813349: Software driver for D-Link Wi-Fi USB Adapter vulnerable to service path privilege escalation]]></title>
        <id>https://kb.cert.org/vuls/id/813349</id>
        <link href="https://kb.cert.org/vuls/id/813349"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T15:17:19.559Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="overview">Overview</h3>
<p>The software driver for D-Link DWA-117 AC600 MU-MIMO Wi-Fi USB Adapter contains a unquoted service path privilege escalation vulnerability. In certain conditions, this flaw can lead to a local privilege escalation.</p>
<h3 id="description">Description</h3>
<p>D-Link DWA-117 AC600 MU-MIMO is a Wi-Fi USB Adapter that enables Wi-Fi network accessible over USB. D-Link provides a software driver for Microsoft Windows operating system that enables proper operation of the device with the operating system. The latest software driver (as of Arpil 19, 2023) was found susceptible  to  an unquoted service path vulnerability. Given certain conditions are met, there is potential for a local privilege escalation allowing an attacker to escalate privileges to local administrative user.</p>
<p>The following conditions are required to trigger this bug
* The software is installed in a directory with a space in it. (The default settings for directory will work)
* An unprivileged user should have write access to the directory above the folder that contains the space in its name. (Typical default Windows user permissions is sufficient)</p>
<h3 id="impact">Impact</h3>
<p>An attacker with low level access can execute code as the system account. The increased privileges allow for access to sensitive files and malicious modifications to the system.</p>
<h3 id="solution">Solution</h3>
<p>D-Link has provided a patch that addresses the issue. Customers should update their driver to the latest version.</p>
<h3 id="acknowledgements">Acknowledgements</h3>
<p>Thanks to @L1v1ng0ffTh3L4n for reporting the vulnerability.</p>
<p>This document was written by Kevin Stephens.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT Recently Published Vulnerability Notes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>