<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://ehsanedalat.github.io/securitynews/index.html</id>
    <title>News | S&amp;P Homepage</title>
    <updated>2023-07-10T01:46:09.990Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://ehsanedalat.github.io/securitynews/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://ehsanedalat.github.io/securitynews/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two Spyware Apps on Google Play with 1.5 Million Users Sending Data to China]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/two-spyware-apps-on-google-play-with-15.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/two-spyware-apps-on-google-play-with-15.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-08T07:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two file management apps on the Google Play Store have been discovered to be spyware, putting the privacy and security of up to 1.5 million Android users at risk. These apps engage in deceptive behaviour and secretly send sensitive user data to malicious servers in China.
Pradeo, a leading mobile security company, has uncovered this alarming infiltration. The report shows that both spyware apps,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improve Your Security WordPress Spam Protection With CleanTalk Anti-Spam]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/improve-your-security-wordpress-spam.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/improve-your-security-wordpress-spam.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-08T06:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every website owner or webmaster grapples with the issue of spam on their website forms. The volume of spam can be so overwhelming that finding useful information within it becomes quite challenging. What exacerbates this issue is that spam can populate your public pages, appearing in comments and reviews. You likely understand how this can damage your website's reputation, affect search results]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exposure Management Looks to Attack Paths, Identity to Better Measure Risk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/exposure-management-looks-to-attack-paths-identity-to-better-measure-risk</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/exposure-management-looks-to-attack-paths-identity-to-better-measure-risk"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T22:43:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security firms analyze attack paths and seek out weak identities to find compromise vectors and critical assets that need better controls.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Lemos, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Safely Architect AI in Your Cybersecurity Programs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge/how-to-safely-architect-ai-in-your-cybersecurity-programs</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge/how-to-safely-architect-ai-in-your-cybersecurity-programs"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T21:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Guardrails need to be set in place to ensure confidentiality of sensitive information, while still leveraging AI as a force multiplier for productivity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Randleman, Field CISO — Application Security &amp; Pentest, Coalfire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global Hacking Competition Addresses Critical Increase in Cybersecurity Threats for Businesses]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/global-hacking-competition-addresses-critical-increase-in-cybersecurity-threats-for-businesses</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/global-hacking-competition-addresses-critical-increase-in-cybersecurity-threats-for-businesses"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T21:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hack The Box launches Capture The Flag competition, including offensive and defensive challenges, to unite teams as cyberattacks increase in 2023 to unprecedented levels.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta's Rush to Topple Twitter Sets Up Looming Privacy Debate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/meta-rush-to-topple-twitter-sets-up-looming-privacy-debate</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/meta-rush-to-topple-twitter-sets-up-looming-privacy-debate"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T21:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GDPR is halting Meta's new Threads app from entering EU markets, portending a broader struggle over the right ways to collect user data on social apps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friday Squid Blogging: Giant Squid Nebula]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/07/friday-squid-blogging-giant-squid-nebula.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/07/friday-squid-blogging-giant-squid-nebula.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T21:08:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://science.nasa.gov/ou4-giant-squid-nebula">Pretty</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>A mysterious squid-like cosmic cloud, this nebula is very faint, but also very large in planet Earth&#8217;s sky. In the image, composed with 30 hours of narrowband image data, it spans nearly three full moons toward the royal constellation Cepheus. Discovered in 2011 by French astro-imager Nicolas Outters, the Squid Nebula&#8217;s bipolar shape is distinguished here by the telltale blue-green emission from doubly ionized oxygen atoms. Though apparently surrounded by the reddish hydrogen emission region Sh2-129, the true distance and nature of the Squid Nebula have been difficult to determine. Still, a more recent investigation suggests Ou4 really does lie within Sh2-129 some 2,300 light-years away. Consistent with that scenario, the cosmic squid would represent a spectacular outflow of material driven by a triple system of hot, massive stars, cataloged as HR8119, seen near the center of the nebula. If so, this truly giant squid nebula would physically be over 50 light-years across...</p></blockquote>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Truebot Malware Variants Abound, According to CISA Advisory]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/truebot-malware-variants-abound-according-to-cisa-advisory</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/truebot-malware-variants-abound-according-to-cisa-advisory"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T20:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US and Canadian government agencies find that new variants of the malware are increasingly being utilized.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6212-1: Linux kernel (Intel IoTG) vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6212-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6212-1"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T19:40:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hangyu Hua discovered that the Flower classifier implementation in the
Linux kernel contained an out-of-bounds write vulnerability. An attacker
could use this to cause a denial of service (system crash) or possibly
execute arbitrary code. (CVE-2023-35788, LP: #2023577)

It was discovered that for some Intel processors the INVLPG instruction
implementation did not properly flush global TLB entries when PCIDs are
enabled. An attacker could use this to expose sensitive information
(kernel memory) or possibly cause undesired behaviors. (LP: #2023220)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6211-1: Linux kernel (Azure) regression]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6211-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6211-1"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T18:54:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6130-1 fixed vulnerabilities in the Linux kernel. Unfortunately, that
update introduced a spurious warning in the IPv6 subsystem. This update
removes the undesired warning message.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spyware Gamed 1.5M Users of Google Play Store]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/spyware-gamed-1-5m-users-of-google-play-store-</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/spyware-gamed-1-5m-users-of-google-play-store-"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malware spoofed file management applications thanks to elevated permissions, enabling exfiltration of sensitive data with no user interaction, researchers find.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Becky Bracken, Editor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MOVEit Transfer Faces Another Critical Data-Theft Bug]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/moveit-transfer-another-critical-data-theft-bug</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/moveit-transfer-another-critical-data-theft-bug"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T18:20:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Users need to patch the latest SQL injection vulnerability as soon as possible. Meanwhile, Cl0p's data extortion rampage gallops on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vishing Goes High-Tech: New 'Letscall' Malware Employs Voice Traffic Routing]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/vishing-goes-high-tech-new-letscall.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/vishing-goes-high-tech-new-letscall.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T18:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have issued a warning about an emerging and advanced form of voice phishing (vishing) known as "Letscall." This technique is currently targeting individuals in South Korea.
The criminals behind "Letscall" employ a multi-step attack to deceive victims into downloading malicious apps from a counterfeit Google Play Store website.
Once the malicious software is installed, it redirects]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After Zero-Day Attacks, MOVEit Turns to Security Service Packs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34226</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/after-zero-day-attacks-moveit-turns-to-security-service-packs/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T16:02:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Facing ransomware zero-days, Progress Software will release regular service packs to help customers mitigate critical security flaws.
The post After Zero-Day Attacks, MOVEit Turns to Security Service Packs appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Naraine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6210-1: Doorkeeper vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6210-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6210-1"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T15:14:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was discovered that Doorkeeper incorrectly performed authorization checks
for public clients that have been previous approved. An attacker could
potentially exploit these in order to impersonate another user and obtain
sensitive information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Other News: Healthcare Product Flaws, Free Email Security Testing, New Attack Techniques]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34223</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/in-other-news-healthcare-product-flaws-free-email-security-testing-new-attack-techniques/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T15:05:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Weekly cybersecurity news roundup that provides a summary of noteworthy stories that might have slipped under the radar for the week of July 3, 2023.
The post In Other News: Healthcare Product Flaws, Free Email Security Testing, New Attack Techniques appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SecurityWeek News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Contractor Employee Charged for Hacking California Water Treatment Facility]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34222</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/former-contractor-employee-charged-for-hacking-california-water-treatment-facility/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T14:42:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former contractor employee charged with hacking for accessing the systems of a water treatment facility in California to delete critical software.
The post Former Contractor Employee Charged for Hacking California Water Treatment Facility appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eduard Kovacs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another Critical Unauthenticated SQLi Flaw Discovered in MOVEit Transfer Software]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/another-critical-unauthenticated-sqli.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/another-critical-unauthenticated-sqli.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T14:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Progress Software has announced the discovery and patching of a critical SQL injection vulnerability in MOVEit Transfer, popular software used for secure file transfer. In addition, Progress Software has patched two other high-severity vulnerabilities.
The identified SQL injection vulnerability, tagged as CVE-2023-36934, could potentially allow unauthenticated attackers to gain unauthorized]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Generative AI Be Trusted to Fix Your Code?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/can-generative-ai-be-trusted-to-fix-your-code-</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/can-generative-ai-be-trusted-to-fix-your-code-"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not yet — but it can help make incremental progress in reducing vulnerability backlogs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eitan Worcel, Co-Founder &amp; CEO, Mobb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iranian Cyberspies Target US-Based Think Tank With New macOS Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34221</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/iranian-cyberspies-target-us-based-think-tank-with-new-macos-malware/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T13:42:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In May 2023, Iran-linked cyberespionage group Charming Kitten targeted a US-based think tank with new macOS malware.
The post Iranian Cyberspies Target US-Based Think Tank With New macOS Malware appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Arghire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerabilities in PiiGAB Product Could Expose Industrial Organizations to Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34219</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/vulnerabilities-in-piigab-product-could-expose-industrial-organizations-to-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T13:03:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Potentially serious vulnerabilities discovered by researchers in a PiiGAB product could expose industrial organizations to remote hacker attacks.
The post Vulnerabilities in PiiGAB Product Could Expose Industrial Organizations to Attacks appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eduard Kovacs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OWASP SwSec 5D Tool Provides SDLC Maturity Ratings, Aids Software Supply Chain]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34210</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/owasp-swsec-5d-tool-provides-sdlc-maturity-ratings-aids-software-supply-chain/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T12:57:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SwSec 5D framework aims to provide a roadmap for secure software development, and its use would help improve security in the software supply chain.
The post OWASP SwSec 5D Tool Provides SDLC Maturity Ratings, Aids Software Supply Chain appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Townsend</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastodon Social Network Patches Critical Flaws Allowing Server Takeover]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/mastodon-social-network-patches.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/mastodon-social-network-patches.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T12:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mastodon, a popular decentralized social network, has released a security update to fix critical vulnerabilities that could expose millions of users to potential attacks.
Mastodon is known for its federated model, consisting of thousands of separate servers called "instances," and it has over 14 million users across more than 20,000 instances.
The most critical vulnerability, CVE-2023-36460,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security Firm Finds Over 130k Internet-Exposed Photovoltaic Diagnostics Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34218</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/security-firm-finds-over-130k-internet-exposed-photovoltaic-diagnostics-systems/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T12:47:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cyble has discovered more than 130,000 Photovoltaic monitoring and diagnostic solutions exposed to the internet.
The post Security Firm Finds Over 130k Internet-Exposed Photovoltaic Diagnostics Systems appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Arghire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Progress Software Releases Service Pack for MOVEit Transfer Vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>/node/18414</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/07/07/progress-software-releases-service-pack-moveit-transfer-vulnerabilities"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Progress Software has released a Service Pack to address three newly disclosed vulnerabilities (CVE-2023-36934, CVE-2023-36932, CVE-2023-36933) in MOVEit Transfer. A cyber threat actor could exploit some of these vulnerabilities to obtain sensitive information. 
CISA encourages users to review Progress Software’s MOVEit Transfer article and apply product updates as applicable for security improvements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Adds One Known Vulnerability to Catalog]]></title>
        <id>/node/18413</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/07/07/cisa-adds-one-known-vulnerability-catalog"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CISA has added one new vulnerability to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog, based on evidence of active exploitation.
CVE-2021-29256 Arm Mali GPU Kernel Driver Use-After-Free Vulnerability
These types of vulnerabilities are frequent attack vectors for malicious cyber actors and pose significant risks to the federal enterprise. Note: To view other newly added vulnerabilities in the catalog, click on the arrow in the "Date Added to Catalog" column—which will sort by descending dates.
Binding Operational Directive (BOD) 22-01: Reducing the Significant Risk of Known Exploited Vulnerabilities established the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog as a living list of known Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVEs) that carry significant risk to the federal enterprise. BOD 22-01 requires Federal Civilian Executive Branch (FCEB) agencies to remediate identified vulnerabilities by the due date to protect FCEB networks against active threats. See the BOD 22-01 Fact Sheet for more information.
Although BOD 22-01 only applies to FCEB agencies, CISA strongly urges all organizations to reduce their exposure to cyberattacks by prioritizing timely remediation of Catalog vulnerabilities as part of their vulnerability management practice. CISA will continue to add vulnerabilities to the catalog that meet the specified criteria.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The AI Dividend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/07/the-ai-dividend.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/07/the-ai-dividend.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T11:11:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>For four decades, Alaskans have opened their mailboxes to find checks waiting for them, their cut of the black gold beneath their feet. This is Alaska&#8217;s Permanent Fund, funded by the state&#8217;s oil revenues and paid to every Alaskan each year. We&#8217;re now in a different sort of resource rush, with companies peddling bits instead of oil: generative AI.</p>
<p>Everyone is talking about these new AI technologies&#8212;like ChatGPT&#8212;and AI companies are touting their awesome power. But they aren&#8217;t talking about how that power comes from all of us. Without all of our writings and photos that AI companies are using to train their models, they would have nothing to sell. Big Tech companies are currently taking the work of the American people, without our knowledge and consent, without licensing it, and are pocketing the proceeds...</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two Apps Hosted on Google Play Caught Sending User Data to Chinese Servers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34216</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/two-apps-hosted-on-google-play-caught-sending-user-data-to-chinese-servers/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T10:51:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two applications hosted on Google Play, with over 1.5 million combined downloads, were caught sending user data to servers in China.
The post Two Apps Hosted on Google Play Caught Sending User Data to Chinese Servers appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ionut Arghire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Close Security Gaps with Continuous Threat Exposure Management]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/close-security-gaps-with-continuous.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/close-security-gaps-with-continuous.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T10:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CISOs, security leaders, and SOC teams often struggle with limited visibility into all connections made to their company-owned assets and networks. They are hindered by a lack of open-source intelligence and powerful technology required for proactive, continuous, and effective discovery and protection of their systems, data, and assets.
As advanced threat actors constantly search for easily]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackByte 2.0 Ransomware: Infiltrate, Encrypt, and Extort in Just 5 Days]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/blackbyte-20-ransomware-infiltrate.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/blackbyte-20-ransomware-infiltrate.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T10:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware attacks are a major problem for organizations everywhere, and the severity of this problem continues to intensify.
Recently, Microsoft's Incident Response team investigated the BlackByte 2.0 ransomware attacks and exposed these cyber strikes' terrifying velocity and damaging nature.
The findings indicate that hackers can complete the entire attack process, from gaining initial access]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Releases Android Patch Update for 3 Actively Exploited Vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/google-releases-android-patch-update.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/google-releases-android-patch-update.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T07:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has released its monthly security updates for the Android operating system, addressing 46 new software vulnerabilities. Among these, three vulnerabilities have been identified as actively exploited in targeted attacks.
One of the vulnerabilities tracked as CVE-2023-26083 is a memory leak flaw affecting the Arm Mali GPU driver for Bifrost, Avalon, and Valhall chips. This particular]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JumpCloud Resets API Keys Amid Ongoing Cybersecurity Incident]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/jumpcloud-resets-api-keys-amid-ongoing.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/jumpcloud-resets-api-keys-amid-ongoing.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T06:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JumpCloud, a provider of cloud-based identity and access management solutions, has swiftly reacted to an ongoing cybersecurity incident that impacted some of its clients.
As part of its damage control efforts, JumpCloud has reset the application programming interface (API) keys of all customers affected by this event, aiming to protect their valuable data.
The company has informed the concerned]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity Agencies Sound Alarm on Rising TrueBot Malware Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/cybersecurity-agencies-sound-alarm-on.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/cybersecurity-agencies-sound-alarm-on.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T05:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity agencies have warned about the emergence of new variants of the TrueBot malware. This enhanced threat is now targeting companies in the U.S. and Canada with the intention of extracting confidential data from infiltrated systems.
These sophisticated attacks exploit a critical vulnerability (CVE-2022-31199) in the widely used Netwrix Auditor server and its associated agents.
This]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Startup Spotlight: Endor Labs Focuses on Reachability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/startup-spotlight-endor-labs-focuses-on-reachability</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/startup-spotlight-endor-labs-focuses-on-reachability"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T04:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company, one of four finalists in Black Hat USA's 2023 startup competition, looks for the vulnerabilities an attacker could actually access.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karen Spiegelman, Features Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Black Hat Announces Maria Markstedter, Jen Easterly, Viktor Zhora, and Kemba Walden As Keynote Speakers for Black Hat USA 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/black-hat-announces-maria-markstedter-jen-easterly-viktor-zhora-and-kemba-walden-as-keynote-speakers-for-black-hat-usa-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/black-hat-announces-maria-markstedter-jen-easterly-viktor-zhora-and-kemba-walden-as-keynote-speakers-for-black-hat-usa-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T21:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[StackRot Linux Kernel Bug Has Exploit Code on the Way]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/stackrot-linux-kernel-bug-exploit-code</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/stackrot-linux-kernel-bug-exploit-code"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T21:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus Torvalds led a Linux kernel team in developing a set of patches for the privilege escalation flaw.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6208-1: Gorilla WebSocket vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6208-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6208-1"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T20:40:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was discovered that Gorilla WebSocket incorrectly handled decoding WebSocket
frames. An attacker could possibly use this issue to cause a crash, resulting
in a denial of service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Patchless Cisco Flaw Breaks Cloud Encryption for ACI Traffic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/perimeter/patchless-cisco-flaw-cloud-encryption-aci-traffic</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/perimeter/patchless-cisco-flaw-cloud-encryption-aci-traffic"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T20:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerable Nexus 9000 Series Fabric Switches in ACI mode should be disabled, Cisco advises.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Becky Bracken, Editor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6207-1: Linux kernel (Intel IoTG) vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6207-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6207-1"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T19:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was discovered that the TUN/TAP driver in the Linux kernel did not
properly initialize socket data. A local attacker could use this to cause a
denial of service (system crash). (CVE-2023-1076)

It was discovered that the Real-Time Scheduling Class implementation in the
Linux kernel contained a type confusion vulnerability in some situations. A
local attacker could use this to cause a denial of service (system crash).
(CVE-2023-1077)

It was discovered that the ASUS HID driver in the Linux kernel did not
properly handle device removal, leading to a use-after-free vulnerability.
A local attacker with physical access could plug in a specially crafted USB
device to cause a denial of service (system crash). (CVE-2023-1079)

It was discovered that the Xircom PCMCIA network device driver in th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shell Becomes Latest Cl0p MOVEit Victim]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/shell-latest-cl0p-moveit-victim</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/shell-latest-cl0p-moveit-victim"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T18:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In another MOVEit attack, oil and gas giant Shell saw the release of the private information of its employees.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Truebot Hackers Exploiting Netwrix Auditor Flaw: CISA, FBI Alert]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34215</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/cisa-fbi-warning-truebot-hackers-exploiting-netwrix-auditor-flaw/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T18:41:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers linked to the Truebot malware are exploiting a year-old Netwrix Auditor flaw to break into organizations in the U.S. and Canada.
The post Truebot Hackers Exploiting Netwrix Auditor Flaw: CISA, FBI Alert appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Naraine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6206-1: Linux kernel (OEM) vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6206-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6206-1"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T18:06:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hangyu Hua discovered that the Flower classifier implementation in the
Linux kernel contained an out-of-bounds write vulnerability. An attacker
could use this to cause a denial of service (system crash) or possibly
execute arbitrary code. (CVE-2023-35788, LP: #2023577)

It was discovered that the NTFS file system implementation in the Linux
kernel contained a null pointer dereference in some situations. A local
attacker could use this to cause a denial of service (system crash).
(CVE-2022-4842)

Seth Jenkins discovered that the CPU data to memory implementation for x86
processors in the Linux kernel did not properly perform address
randomization. A local attacker could use this to expose sensitive
information (kernel memory) or in conjunction with another kernel
vulnerability. (CVE-2023-0597)

It was discovered that the XFS file system implementation in the Linux
kernel did not properly perform metadata validation when mounting certain
images. An attacker could use this to specially craft a file system image
that, when mounted, could cause a denial of service (system crash).
(CVE-2023-2124)

It was discovered that for some Intel processors the INVLPG instruction
implementation did not properly flush global TLB entries when PCIDs are
enabled. An attacker could use this to expose sensitive information
(kernel memory) or possibly cause undesired behaviors. (LP: #2023220)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iranian Hackers' Sophisticated Malware Targets Windows and macOS Users]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/iranian-hackers-sophisticated-malware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/iranian-hackers-sophisticated-malware.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T18:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Iranian nation-state actor known as TA453 has been linked to a new set of spear-phishing attacks that infect both Windows and macOS operating systems with malware.
"TA453 eventually used a variety of cloud hosting providers to deliver a novel infection chain that deploys the newly identified PowerShell backdoor GorjolEcho," Proofpoint said in a new report.
"When given the opportunity, TA453]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6205-1: Linux kernel (GKE) vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6205-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6205-1"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T18:02:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hangyu Hua discovered that the Flower classifier implementation in the
Linux kernel contained an out-of-bounds write vulnerability. An attacker
could use this to cause a denial of service (system crash) or possibly
execute arbitrary code. (CVE-2023-35788, LP: #2023577)

It was discovered that for some Intel processors the INVLPG instruction
implementation did not properly flush global TLB entries when PCIDs are
enabled. An attacker could use this to expose sensitive information
(kernel memory) or possibly cause undesired behaviors. (LP: #2023220)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Privacy Woes Hold Up Global Instagram Threads Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/privacy-woes-hold-up-global-instagram-threads-launch</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/privacy-woes-hold-up-global-instagram-threads-launch"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T17:25:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta's answer to Twitter went live and quickly racked up millions of members — but the social media app's privacy practices are under the microscope.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tara Seals, Managing Editor, News, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now’s the Time for a Pragmatic Approach to New Technology Adoption]]></title>
        <id>https://www.securityweek.com/?p=34213</id>
        <link href="https://www.securityweek.com/nows-the-time-for-a-pragmatic-approach-to-new-technology-adoption/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T17:23:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What a cloud migration strategy did for cloud adoption, an automation implementation strategy does for security automation adoption.
The post Now’s the Time for a Pragmatic Approach to New Technology Adoption appeared first on SecurityWeek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marc Solomon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity's Future Hinges on Stronger Public-Private Partnerships]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/cybersecurity-future-hinges-stronger-public-private-partnerships</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/cybersecurity-future-hinges-stronger-public-private-partnerships"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Public and private sector organizations must collaborate on a shared cybersecurity agenda to protect and benefit society at large.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Boro, Managing Partner, ThomaBravo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Searches for 'USPS Package Tracking' Lead to Banking Theft]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/google-searches-usps-tracking-banking-theft</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/google-searches-usps-tracking-banking-theft"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T15:11:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attackers are leveraging well-executed brand impersonation in a Google ads malvertising effort that collects both credit card and bank details from victims.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Montalbano, Contributor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISOs Find 'Business as Usual' Shows the Harsh Realities of Cyber-Risk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/risk/cisos-find-business-as-usual-shows-the-harsh-realities-of-cyber-risk</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/risk/cisos-find-business-as-usual-shows-the-harsh-realities-of-cyber-risk"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[C-suite security leaders are feeling less prepared to cope with cyberattacks and more at risk than last year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kalember, Executive Vice President of Cybersecurity Strategy, Proofpoint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Botnets Send Exploits Within Days to Weeks After Published PoC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/botnets-send-exploits-only-day-to-weeks-after-published-poc</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/botnets-send-exploits-only-day-to-weeks-after-published-poc"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Six months of honeypot data finds that 19% of traffic to sensors were malicious exploit attempts, and 95% of those attempts came from just three botnets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Lemos, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Steps To Outsmart Business Email Compromise Scammers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/microsoft/6-steps-to-outsmarting-business-email-compromise-scammers</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/microsoft/6-steps-to-outsmarting-business-email-compromise-scammers"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Email fraud is a confidence game that costs the economy billions. An effective defense takes technology and vigilance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Microsoft Security, Microsoft</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Releases Three Industrial Control Systems Advisories]]></title>
        <id>/node/18411</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/07/06/cisa-releases-three-industrial-control-systems-advisories"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CISA has released three Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisories on July 6, 2023. These advisories provide timely information about current security issues, vulnerabilities, and exploits surrounding ICS.
CISA encourages users and administrators to review the newly released ICS advisory for technical details and mitigations:
ICSA-23-187-01 PiiGAB M-Bus
ICSA-23-187-02 ABUS TVIP
ICSA-23-143-03 Mitsubishi Electric MELSEC Series CPU module (Update A)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA and Partners Release Joint Cybersecurity Advisory on Newly Identified Truebot Malware Variants]]></title>
        <id>/node/18405</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/07/06/cisa-and-partners-release-joint-cybersecurity-advisory-newly-identified-truebot-malware-variants"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, the Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA), Federal Bureau of Investigations (FBI), the Multi-State Information Sharing and Analysis Center (MS-ISAC), and the Canadian Centre for Cyber Security (CCCS) released a joint Cybersecurity Advisory (CSA), Increased Truebot Activity Infects U.S. and Canada Based Networks, to help organizations detect and protect against newly identified Truebot malware variants. Based on confirmation from open-source reporting and analytical findings of Truebot variants, the four organizations assess cyber threat actors leveraged the malware through phishing campaigns containing malicious redirect hyperlinks.
Additionally, newer versions of Truebot malware allow malicious actors to gain initial access by exploiting a known vulnerability with Netwrix Auditor application (CVE-2022-31199). As recently as May 2023, cyber threat actors used this common vulnerability and exposure to deliver new Truebot malware variants and to collect and exfiltrate information against organizations in the U.S. and Canada.
CISA, FBI, MS-ISAC, and the CCCS encourage all organizations to review this joint advisory and implement the recommended mitigations contained therein—including applying patches to CVE-2022-31199, to reduce the likelihood and impact of Truebot activity, as well as other ransomware related incidents. To report incidents and anomalous activity, please contact one of the following organizations:
CISA, either through the agency’s online tool (cisa.gov/report) or the 24/7 Operations Center at report@cisa.gov or (888) 282-0870.
FBI via a local field office.
State, local, tribal, and territorial (SLTT) government entities can report to the MS-ISAC (SOC@cisecurity.org or 866-787-4522).
Organizations are also encouraged to visit StopRansomware.gov—which provides a range of free U.S. government resources and services that can help bolster cyber hygiene, cybersecurity posture and reduce risk to ransomware, and contains an updated Joint #StopRansomware Guide.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla Releases Security Advisories for Thunderbird, Firefox, and Firefox ESR]]></title>
        <id>/node/18408</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/07/06/mozilla-releases-security-advisories-thunderbird-firefox-and-firefox-esr"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla has released security advisories to address vulnerabilities in Thunderbird, Firefox, and Firefox ESR. A cyber threat actor could exploit some of these vulnerabilities to take control of an affected system. 
CISA encourages users and administrators to review the following advisories and apply the necessary updates:
Security Vulnerabilities fixed in Firefox 115 Mozilla Foundation Security Advisory 2023-24
Security Vulnerabilities fixed in Firefox ESR 102.13 Mozilla Foundation Security Advisory 2023-23
Security Vulnerabilities fixed in Thunderbird 102.13  Mozilla Foundation Security Advisory 2023-22]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Surviving the 800 Gbps Storm: Gain Insights from Gcore's 2023 DDoS Attack Statistics]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/surviving-800-gbps-storm-gain-insights.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/surviving-800-gbps-storm-gain-insights.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T11:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gcore Radar is a quarterly report prepared by Gcore that provides insights into the current state of the DDoS protection market and cybersecurity trends. This report offers you an understanding of the evolving threat landscape and highlights the measures required to protect against attacks effectively. It serves as an insight for businesses and individuals seeking to stay informed about the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Belgian Tax Hack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/07/belgian-tax-hack.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/07/belgian-tax-hack.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T11:03:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Here&#8217;s a fascinating tax hack from Belgium (listen to the details <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gb7TEkHwu_s/">here</a>, episode #484 of &#8220;No Such Thing as a Fish,&#8221; at 28:00).</p>
<p>Basically, it&#8217;s about a music festival on the border between Belgium and Holland. The stage was in Holland, but the crowd was in Belgium. When the copyright collector came around, they argued that they didn&#8217;t have to pay any tax because the audience was in a different country. Supposedly it worked.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Uncover New Linux Kernel 'StackRot' Privilege Escalation Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/researchers-uncover-new-linux-kernel.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/researchers-uncover-new-linux-kernel.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T10:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Details have emerged about a newly identified security flaw in the Linux kernel that could allow a user to gain elevated privileges on a target host.
Dubbed StackRot (CVE-2023-3269, CVSS score: 7.8), the flaw impacts Linux versions 6.1 through 6.4. There is no evidence that the shortcoming has been exploited in the wild to date.
"As StackRot is a Linux kernel vulnerability found in the memory]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Pen Testing can Soften the Blow on Rising Costs of Cyber Insurance]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/how-pen-testing-can-soften-blow-on.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/how-pen-testing-can-soften-blow-on.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T10:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As technology advances and organizations become more reliant on data, the risks associated with data breaches and cyber-attacks also increase. The introduction of data privacy laws, such as the GDPR, has made it mandatory for organizations to disclose breaches of personal data to those affected. As such, it has become essential for businesses to protect themselves from the financial and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Silentbob Campaign: Cloud-Native Environments Under Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/silentbob-campaign-cloud-native.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/silentbob-campaign-cloud-native.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T10:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have unearthed an attack infrastructure that's being used as part of a "potentially massive campaign" against cloud-native environments.
"This infrastructure is in early stages of testing and deployment, and is mainly consistent of an aggressive cloud worm, designed to deploy on exposed JupyterLab and Docker APIs in order to deploy Tsunami malware, cloud credentials]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INTERPOL Nabs Hacking Crew OPERA1ER's Leader Behind $11 Million Cybercrime]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/interpol-nabs-hacking-crew-opera1ers.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/interpol-nabs-hacking-crew-opera1ers.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T08:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A suspected senior member of a French-speaking hacking crew known as OPERA1ER has been arrested as part of an international law enforcement operation codenamed Nervone, Interpol has announced.
"The group is believed to have stolen an estimated USD 11 million -- potentially as much as 30 million -- in more than 30 attacks across 15 countries in Africa, Asia, and Latin America," the agency said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Startup Spotlight: Gomboc.ai Balances Cloud Infrastructure Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/startup-spotlight-gomboc-ai-balances-cloud-infrastructure-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/startup-spotlight-gomboc-ai-balances-cloud-infrastructure-security"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T03:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The startup, one of four finalists in Black Hat USA's 2023 startup competition, uses deterministic AI to optimize cloud security.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karen Spiegelman, Features Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 Critical RCE Bugs Threaten Industrial Solar Panels, Endangering Grid Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/ics-ot/3-critical-rce-bugs-threaten-industrial-solar-panels</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/ics-ot/3-critical-rce-bugs-threaten-industrial-solar-panels"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exposed and unpatched solar power monitoring systems have been exploited by both amateurs and professionals, including Mirai botnet hackers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mitigating Risk With Threat Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge/mitigating-risk-with-threat-intelligence</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge/mitigating-risk-with-threat-intelligence"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T00:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dark Reading's latest special report looks at a missing, but necessary, ingredient to effective third-party risk management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George V. Hulme, Contributor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Increased Truebot Activity Infects U.S. and Canada Based Networks]]></title>
        <id>/node/18407</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/cybersecurity-advisories/aa23-187a"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T21:30:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUMMARY
The Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA), the Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI), the Multi-State Information Sharing and Analysis Center (MS-ISAC), and the Canadian Centre for Cyber Security (CCCS) are releasing this joint Cybersecurity Advisory (CSA) in response to cyber threat actors leveraging newly identified Truebot malware variants against organizations in the United States and Canada. As recently as May 31, 2023, the authoring organizations have observed an increase in cyber threat actors using new malware variants of Truebot (also known as Silence.Downloader). Truebot is a botnet that has been used by malicious cyber groups like CL0P Ransomware Gang to collect and exfiltrate information from its target victims.
Previous Truebot malware variants were p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[83% of Brits Demand Messaging Apps Remain Private, Ahead of Threat From Online Safety Bill]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/iot/83-of-brits-demand-messaging-apps-remain-private-ahead-of-threat-from-online-safety-bill</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/iot/83-of-brits-demand-messaging-apps-remain-private-ahead-of-threat-from-online-safety-bill"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T21:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[70% think criminals will move from WhatsApp etc to non-regulated apps, post OSB.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Teams Exploit Tool Auto-Delivers Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/perimeter/microsoft-teams-exploit-toll-autodeliver-malware</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/perimeter/microsoft-teams-exploit-toll-autodeliver-malware"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T21:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The "TeamsPhisher" cyberattack tool gives pen testers — and adversaries — a way to deliver malicious files directly to a Teams user from an external account, or tenant.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MAR-10445155-1.v1 Truebot Activity Infects U.S. and Canada Based Networks]]></title>
        <id>/node/18403</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/analysis-reports/ar23-187a"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T19:56:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notification
This report is provided "as is" for informational purposes only. The Department of Homeland Security (DHS) does not provide any warranties of any kind regarding any information contained herein. The DHS does not endorse any commercial product or service referenced in this bulletin or otherwise.
This document is marked TLP:CLEAR--Recipients may share this information without restriction. Sources may use TLP:CLEAR when information carries minimal or no foreseeable risk of misuse, in accordance with applicable rules and procedures for public release. Subject to standard copyright rules, TLP:CLEAR information may be shared without restriction. For more information on the Traffic Light Protocol (TLP), see http://www.cisa.gov/tlp.
Summary
Description
CISA received one Windows Portab…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OPERA1ER Cybercrime Group's Leader Arrested by Interpol]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/opera1er-cybercrime-leader-arrested-interpol</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/opera1er-cybercrime-leader-arrested-interpol"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T19:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The group's mastermind was nabbed in Côte d'Ivoire for stealing up to $30 million using malware, phishing campaigns, and BEC scams, as part of international law enforcement's Operation Nervone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware Halts Operations at Japan's Port of Nagoya]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/ransomware-halts-operations-at-japan-port-of-nagoya</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/ransomware-halts-operations-at-japan-port-of-nagoya"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T17:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LockBit 3.0 claims responsibility for the cyberattack that shuttered the largest port in Japan, according to authorities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Golden Age of AI … or Security Threats?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/a-golden-age-of-ai-or-security-threats-</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/a-golden-age-of-ai-or-security-threats-"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now is the time to build safeguards into nascent AI technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joey Stanford, Vice President of Privacy &amp; Security, Platform.sh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cl0p's MOVEit Campaign Represents a New Era in Cyberattacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/c10p-moveit-campaign-new-era-cyberattacks</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/c10p-moveit-campaign-new-era-cyberattacks"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T16:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ransomware group shows an evolution of its tactics with MOVEit zero-day — potentially ushering in a new normal when it comes to extortion supply chain cyberattacks, experts say.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Becky Bracken, Editor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China's Mustang Panda Linked to SmugX Attacks on European Governments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/group-tied-to-china-s-mustang-panda-targets-european-governments-with-smugx</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/group-tied-to-china-s-mustang-panda-targets-european-governments-with-smugx"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T15:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attackers use HTML smuggling to spread the PlugX RAT in the campaign, which has been ongoing since at least December.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Montalbano, Contributor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6204-1: CPDB vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6204-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6204-1"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T15:23:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seth Arnold discovered that CPDB incorrectly handled certain characters.
An attacker could possibly use this issue to cause a crash or execute
arbitrary code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RedEnergy Stealer-as-a-Ransomware Threat Targeting Energy and Telecom Sectors]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/redenergy-stealer-as-ransomware-threat.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/redenergy-stealer-as-ransomware-threat.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A sophisticated stealer-as-a-ransomware threat dubbed RedEnergy has been spotted in the wild targeting energy utilities, oil, gas, telecom, and machinery sectors in Brazil and the Philippines through their LinkedIn pages.
The .NET malware "possesses the ability to steal information from various browsers, enabling the exfiltration of sensitive data, while also incorporating different modules for]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Can Fix Ransomware Tomorrow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/microsoft-can-fix-ransomware-tomorrow</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/microsoft-can-fix-ransomware-tomorrow"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can't encrypt a file you can't open — Microsoft could dramatically impact ransomware by slowing it down.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Shostack, Leading expert in threat modeling</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6203-1: Django vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6203-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6203-1"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T11:23:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seokchan Yoon discovered that Django incorrectly handled certain regular
expressions. A remote attacker could possibly use this issue to cause
Django to consume resources, leading to a denial of service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Class-Action Lawsuit for Scraping Data without Permission]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/07/class-action-lawsuit-for-scraping-data-without-permission.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/07/class-action-lawsuit-for-scraping-data-without-permission.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T11:14:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I have mixed feelings about this <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/wxjxgx/openai-and-microsoft-sued-for-dollar3-billion-over-alleged-chatgpt-privacy-violations">class-action lawsuit</a> against OpenAI and Microsoft, claiming that it &#8220;scraped 300 billion words from the internet&#8221; without either registering as a data broker or obtaining consent. On the one hand, I want this to be a protected fair use of public data. On the other hand, I want us all <a href="https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2023/06/29/ai-pay-americans-data-00103648">to be compensated</a> for our uniquely human ability to generate language.</p>
<p>There&#8217;s an interesting wrinkle on this. A <a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2305.17493">recent paper</a> showed that using AI generated text to train another AI invariably &#8220;causes irreversible defects.&#8221; From a ...</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secrets, Secrets Are No Fun. Secrets, Secrets (Stored in Plain Text Files) Hurt Someone]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/secrets-secrets-are-no-fun-secrets.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/secrets-secrets-are-no-fun-secrets.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T10:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secrets are meant to be hidden or, at the very least, only known to a specific and limited set of individuals (or systems). Otherwise, they aren't really secrets. In personal life, a secret revealed can damage relationships, lead to social stigma, or, at the very least, be embarrassing. In a developer's or application security engineer's professional life, the consequences of exposing secrets]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USN-6202-1: containerd vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6202-1</id>
        <link href="https://ubuntu.com/security/notices/USN-6202-1"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T10:44:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Korczynski and Adam Korczynski discovered that containerd
incorrectly processed certain images with large files. An attacker
could possibly use this issue to cause containerd to crash,
resulting in a denial of service. (CVE-2023-25153)

It was discovered that containerd incorrectly set up supplementary
groups inside a container. An attacker with direct access to the
container could possibly use this issue to obtain sensitive information
or execute code with higher privileges. (CVE-2023-25173)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ubuntu security notices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Node.js Users Beware: Manifest Confusion Attack Opens Door to Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/nodejs-users-beware-manifest-confusion.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/nodejs-users-beware-manifest-confusion.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The npm registry for the Node.js JavaScript runtime environment is susceptible to what's called a manifest confusion attack that could potentially allow threat actors to conceal malware in project dependencies or perform arbitrary script execution during installation.
"A npm package's manifest is published independently from its tarball," Darcy Clarke, a former GitHub and npm engineering manager]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Instagram's Twitter Alternative 'Threads' Launch Halted in Europe Over Privacy Concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/instagrams-twitter-alternative-threads.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/instagrams-twitter-alternative-threads.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T08:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Instagram Threads, the upcoming Twitter competitor from Meta, will not be launched in the European Union due to privacy concerns, according to Ireland's Data Protection Commission (DPC).
The development was reported by the Irish Independent, which said the watchdog has been in contact with the social media giant about the new product and confirmed the release won't extend to the E.U. "at this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Swedish Data Protection Authority Warns Companies Against Google Analytics Use]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/swedish-data-protection-authority-warns.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/swedish-data-protection-authority-warns.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-04T17:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Swedish data protection watchdog has warned companies against using Google Analytics due to risks posed by U.S. government surveillance, following similar moves by Austria, France, and Italy last year.
The development comes in the aftermath of an audit initiated by the Swedish Authority for Privacy Protection (IMY) against four companies CDON, Coop, Dagens Industri, and Tele2.
"In its audits]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Password Game]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/07/the-password-game.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/07/the-password-game.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-04T11:12:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://neal.fun/password-game/">Amusing</a> parody of password rules.</p>
<p><a href="https://boingboing.net/2023/06/30/the-ridiculous-and-fun-password-game-parodies-the-frustration-of-picking-a-password.html">BoingBoing</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>For example, at a certain level, your password must include today&#8217;s Wordle answer. And then there&#8217;s rule #27: &#8220;At least 50% of your password must be in the Wingdings font.&#8221;</p></blockquote>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DDoSia Attack Tool Evolves with Encryption, Targeting Multiple Sectors]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/ddosia-attack-tool-evolves-with.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/ddosia-attack-tool-evolves-with.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-04T10:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actors behind the DDoSia attack tool have come up with a new version that incorporates a new mechanism to retrieve the list of targets to be bombarded with junk HTTP requests in an attempt to bring them down.
The updated variant, written in Golang, "implements an additional security mechanism to conceal the list of targets, which is transmitted from the [command-and-control] to the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mexico-Based Hacker Targets Global Banks with Android Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/mexico-based-hacker-targets-global.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/mexico-based-hacker-targets-global.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-04T09:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An e-crime actor of Mexican provenance has been linked to an Android mobile malware campaign targeting financial institutions globally, but with a specific focus on Spanish and Chilean banks, from June 2021 to April 2023.
The activity is being attributed to an actor codenamed Neo_Net, according to security researcher Pol Thill. The findings were published by SentinelOne following a Malware]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alert: 330,000 FortiGate Firewalls Still Unpatched to CVE-2023-27997 RCE Flaw]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/alert-330000-fortigate-firewalls-still.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/alert-330000-fortigate-firewalls-still.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-04T06:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No less than 330,000 FortiGate firewalls are still unpatched and vulnerable to CVE-2023-27997, a critical security flaw affecting Fortinet devices that has come under active exploitation in the wild.
Cybersecurity firm Bishop Fox, in a report published last week, said that out of nearly 490,000 Fortinet SSL-VPN interfaces exposed on the internet, about 69 percent remain unpatched.
CVE-2023-27997]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fortanix Builds Hardware Security Wall Around Plaintext Search]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/fortanix-builds-hardware-security-wall-around-plaintext-search</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/fortanix-builds-hardware-security-wall-around-plaintext-search"/>
        <updated>2023-07-04T01:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company's Confidential Data Search technique relies on confidential computing to keep data secure even while it is in use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Agam Shah, Contributing Writer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Develop Exploit Code for Critical Fortinet VPN Bug]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/researchers-develop-exploit-code-for-critical-fortinet-bug</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/researchers-develop-exploit-code-for-critical-fortinet-bug"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some 340,000 FortiGate SSL VPN appliances remain exposed to the threat more than three weeks after Fortinet released firmware updates to address the issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian Satellite Internet Downed via Attackers Claiming Ties to Wagner Group]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/hackers-claiming-wagner-group-ties-down-russian-satellite-internet-comms-</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/hackers-claiming-wagner-group-ties-down-russian-satellite-internet-comms-"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T18:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attribution for the cyberattack on Dozor-Teleport remains murky, but the effects are real — downed communications and compromised data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel Aided UAE in Defending Against DDoS Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/israel-aided-uae-in-defending-against-ddos-attack</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/israel-aided-uae-in-defending-against-ddos-attack"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Israel's cyber head points finger at Iran-backed MuddyWater APT group as the perpetrator of a recent attack against a university.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Raywood, Senior Editor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SSH Servers Hit in 'Proxyjacking' Cyberattacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/risk/ssh-servers-hit-in-proxyjacking-cyberattacks</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/risk/ssh-servers-hit-in-proxyjacking-cyberattacks"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybercriminals employ obfuscated script to stealthily hijack victim server bandwidth for use in legitimate proxy networks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Montalbano, Contributor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A CISO's Guide to Paying Down Software Supply Chain Security Debt]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/ciso-guide-paying-down-software-supply-chain-security-debt</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/ciso-guide-paying-down-software-supply-chain-security-debt"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you just keep filing it away to handle "someday," security debt typically rears its head when you are most vulnerable and can least afford to pay it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Lorenc, Founder &amp; CEO, Chainguard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Name That Edge Toon: Three-Ring Circus]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge-articles/name-that-edge-toon-three-ring-circus</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge-articles/name-that-edge-toon-three-ring-circus"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Come up with a clever caption, and our panel of experts will reward the winner with a $25 Amazon gift card.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Klossner, Cartoonist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Hackers Use HTML Smuggling to Infiltrate European Ministries with PlugX]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/chinese-hackers-use-html-smuggling-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/chinese-hackers-use-html-smuggling-to.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T13:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Chinese nation-state group has been observed targeting Foreign Affairs ministries and embassies in Europe using HTML smuggling techniques to deliver the PlugX remote access trojan on compromised systems.
Cybersecurity firm Check Point said the activity, dubbed SmugX, has been ongoing since at least December 2022, adding it's part of a broader trend of Chinese adversaries shifting their focus]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerability Summary for the Week of June 26, 2023]]></title>
        <id>/node/18399</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/bulletins/sb23-184"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T11:44:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[High Vulnerabilities

Primary
Description
Published
CVSS Score
Source & Patch Info

apple -- mac_os_x
A use after free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in macOS Big Sur 11.6.6, macOS Monterey 12.3, Security Update 2022-004 Catalina. A remote user may cause an unexpected app termination or arbitrary code execution
2023-06-23
9.8
CVE-2022-22630
MISC
MISC
MISC

google -- android
In cd_CodeMsg of cd_codec.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to remote code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Product: Android Versions: Android kernel Android ID: A-250100597References: N/A
2023-06-28
9.8
CVE-2023-21066
MISC

wordpress -- wordpress
The…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Self-Driving Cars Are Surveillance Cameras on Wheels]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/07/self-driving-cars-are-surveillance-cameras-on-wheels.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/07/self-driving-cars-are-surveillance-cameras-on-wheels.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T11:04:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Police are <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-06-29/self-driving-car-video-from-waymo-cruise-give-police-crime-evidence?sref=P6Q0mxvj">already using</a> self-driving car footage as video evidence:</p>
<blockquote><p>While security cameras are commonplace in American cities, self-driving cars represent a new level of access for law enforcement ­ and a new method for encroachment on privacy, advocates say. Crisscrossing the city on their routes, self-driving cars capture a wider swath of footage. And it’s easier for law enforcement to turn to one company with a large repository of videos and a dedicated response team than to reach out to all the businesses in a neighborhood with security systems...</p></blockquote>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Flags 8 Actively Exploited Flaws in Samsung and D-Link Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/cisa-flags-8-actively-exploited-flaws.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/cisa-flags-8-actively-exploited-flaws.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T10:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has placed a set of eight flaws to the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, based on evidence of active exploitation.
This includes six shortcomings affecting Samsung smartphones and two vulnerabilities impacting D-Link devices. All the flaws have been patched as of 2021.

CVE-2021-25394 (CVSS score: 6.4) - Samsung mobile]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evasive Meduza Stealer Targets 19 Password Managers and 76 Crypto Wallets]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/evasive-meduza-stealer-targets-19.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/evasive-meduza-stealer-targets-19.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T09:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In yet another sign of a lucrative crimeware-as-a-service (CaaS) ecosystem, cybersecurity researchers have discovered a new Windows-based information stealer called Meduza Stealer that's actively being developed by its author to evade detection by software solutions.
"The Meduza Stealer has a singular objective: comprehensive data theft," Uptycs said in a new report. "It pilfers users' browsing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackCat Operators Distributing Ransomware Disguised as WinSCP via Malvertising]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/blackcat-operators-distributing.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/blackcat-operators-distributing.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T04:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors associated with the BlackCat ransomware have been observed employing malvertising tricks to distribute rogue installers of the WinSCP file transfer application.
"Malicious actors used malvertising to distribute a piece of malware via cloned webpages of legitimate organizations," Trend Micro researchers said in an analysis published last week. "In this case, the distribution]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Architecting XDR to Save Money and Your SOC's Sanity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/architecting-xdr-save-money-and-your-soc-sanity</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/architecting-xdr-save-money-and-your-soc-sanity"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T04:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XDR can lower platform costs and improve detection, but it requires committing to a few principles that go against the established way of thinking about SOC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Exploiting Unpatched WordPress Plugin Flaw to Create Secret Admin Accounts]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/unpatched-wordpress-plugin-flaw-could.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/unpatched-wordpress-plugin-flaw-could.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-01T07:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As many as 200,000 WordPress websites are at risk of ongoing attacks exploiting a critical unpatched security vulnerability in the Ultimate Member plugin.
The flaw, tracked as CVE-2023-3460 (CVSS score: 9.8), impacts all versions of the Ultimate Member plugin, including the latest version (2.6.6) that was released on June 29, 2023.
Ultimate Member is a popular plugin that facilitates the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beware: New 'RustBucket' Malware Variant Targeting macOS Users]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/beware-new-rustbucket-malware-variant.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/07/beware-new-rustbucket-malware-variant.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-01T05:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have pulled back the curtain on an updated version of an Apple macOS malware called RustBucket that comes with improved capabilities to establish persistence and avoid detection by security software.
"This variant of RustBucket, a malware family that targets macOS systems, adds persistence capabilities not previously observed," Elastic Security Labs researchers said in a report]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friday Squid Blogging: See-Through Squid]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/06/friday-squid-blogging-see-through-squid.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/06/friday-squid-blogging-see-through-squid.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T20:58:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p><i>Doryteuthis opalescens</i> is known as the market squid, and was <a href="https://www.sciencefriday.com/segments/albino-squid-rna-editing/">critical</a> in the recent squid RNA research.</p>
<p>As usual, you can also use this squid post to talk about the security stories in the news that I haven’t covered.</p>
<p>Read my blog posting guidelines <a href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2017/03/commenting_poli.html">here</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chip Giant TSMC Blames $70M LockBit Breach on IT Hardware Supplier]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/chip-giant-tsmc-blames-lockbit-breach-it-hardware-supplier</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/chip-giant-tsmc-blames-lockbit-breach-it-hardware-supplier"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T19:50:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The group has given one of Apple's biggest semiconductor suppliers until Aug. 6 to pay $70 million or risk having its data and "points of entry" to its network publicly leaked.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mobile Cyberattacks Soar, Especially Against Android Users]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/mobile-cyberattacks-soar-andoird-users</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/mobile-cyberattacks-soar-andoird-users"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The number of malware samples is up as attackers aim to compromise users where they work and play: Their smartphones.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Lemos, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nokod Raises $8M Seed Round From Seasoned Cybersecurity Investors to Enhance Low-Code/No-Code App Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/nokod-raises-8m-seed-round-from-seasoned-cybersecurity-investors-to-enhance-low-code-no-code-app-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/nokod-raises-8m-seed-round-from-seasoned-cybersecurity-investors-to-enhance-low-code-no-code-app-security"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T18:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nokod Security is building a platform that enables organizations to secure in-house low-code/no-code custom applications by scanning for security and compliance issues and applying remediation policies]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iran-Linked APT35 Targets Israeli Media With Upgraded Spear-Phishing Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/iran-linked-apt35-israeli-media-upgraded-spear-phishing</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/iran-linked-apt35-israeli-media-upgraded-spear-phishing"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T17:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The APT35 group (aka Charming Kitten) has added backdoor capabilities to their spear-phishing payloads — and targeted an Israeli reporter with it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Raywood, Senior Editor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[African Nations Face Escalating Phishing & Compromised Password Cyberattacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/african-nations-escalating-phishing-compromised-password-cyberattacks</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/african-nations-escalating-phishing-compromised-password-cyberattacks"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T17:12:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cyberattacks against organizations in some African nations increased significantly in 2022, despite a major expansion in cybersecurity hiring to support cloud and digital migration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Raywood, Senior Editor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian Hacktivist Platform 'DDoSia' Grows Exponentially]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/russian-hacktivist-platform-ddosia-grows-exponentially</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/russian-hacktivist-platform-ddosia-grows-exponentially"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T17:02:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As cybercrime amidst the Russia-Ukraine war continues to escalate, the DDoSia project, launched by a known hacktivist group, has exploded in its number of members and quality of tools used for attacks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Make Diversity the 'How,' Not the 'What,' of Cybersecurity Success]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge/making-diversity-the-how-and-not-the-what-of-cybersecurity-success</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge/making-diversity-the-how-and-not-the-what-of-cybersecurity-success"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity leaders should strive to reward high-performing teams that are powered by high levels of inclusion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ericka Chickowski, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IP Fabric Announces $25M Series B Funding to Accelerate Adoption of Network Assurance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/perimeter/ip-fabric-announces-25m-series-b-funding-to-accelerate-adoption-of-network-assurance</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/perimeter/ip-fabric-announces-25m-series-b-funding-to-accelerate-adoption-of-network-assurance"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T16:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One Peak investment will advance the ubiquity of network assurance, helping organizations to reduce network complexity, assure network automation, and improve network security.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Perception Point Unveils AI Model to Thwart Generative AI-Based BEC Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/perception-point-unveils-ai-model-to-thwart-generative-ai-based-bec-attacks</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/perception-point-unveils-ai-model-to-thwart-generative-ai-based-bec-attacks"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The detection model identifies LLM patterns to counter the rising abuse of generative AI in social engineering attacks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 Ways to Build a More Skilled Cybersecurity Workforce]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/microsoft/3-ways-to-build-a-more-skilled-cybersecurity-workforce</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/microsoft/3-ways-to-build-a-more-skilled-cybersecurity-workforce"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the right collaboration among employers, educators, and policymakers, we can come together to create a more secure environment for all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Microsoft Security, Microsoft</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA BOD 23-01: What Agencies Need to Know About Compliance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/risk/cisa-bod-23-01-what-agencies-need-to-know-about-compliance</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/risk/cisa-bod-23-01-what-agencies-need-to-know-about-compliance"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new network visibility mandate provides a good foundation for identifying risks and building better security programs at federal agencies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Song Pang, Senior VP of Engineering, NetBrain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Cloud GenAI Is Coming to Thales' Data Security Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/google-cloud-genai-is-coming-to-thales-data-security-platform</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/google-cloud-genai-is-coming-to-thales-data-security-platform"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thales will build new machine learning-powered data discovery and classification features based on Google Cloud's Vertex AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iranian Hackers Using POWERSTAR Backdoor in Targeted Espionage Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/iranian-hackers-charming-kitten-utilize.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/iranian-hackers-charming-kitten-utilize.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T13:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Charming Kitten, the nation-state actor affiliated with Iran's Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps (IRGC), has been attributed to a bespoke spear-phishing campaign that delivers an updated version of a fully-featured PowerShell backdoor called POWERSTAR.
"There have been improved operational security measures placed in the malware to make it more difficult to analyze and collect intelligence,"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DoS and DDoS Attacks against Multiple Sectors]]></title>
        <id>/node/18398</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/06/30/dos-and-ddos-attacks-against-multiple-sectors"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CISA is aware of open-source reporting of targeted denial-of-service (DoS) and distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attacks against multiple organizations in multiple sectors. These attacks can cost an organization time and money and may impose reputational costs while resources and services are inaccessible.
If you think you or your business is experiencing a DoS or DDoS attack, it is important to contact the appropriate technical professionals for assistance.
Contact your network administrator to confirm whether the service outage is due to maintenance or an in-house network issue. Network administrators can also monitor network traffic to confirm the presence of an attack, identify the source, and mitigate the situation by applying firewall rules and possibly rerouting traffic through a DoS protection service.
Contact your internet service provider to ask if there is an outage on their end or if their network is the target of an attack and you are an indirect victim. They may be able to advise you on an appropriate course of action.
Organizations can take proactive steps to reduce the effects of an attack—See the following guidance for more information:
Understanding and Responding to Distributed Denial-of-Service Attacks
Additional DDoS Guidance for Federal Agencies]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 Reasons SaaS Security is the Imperative First Step to Ensuring Secure AI Usage]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/3-reasons-saas-security-is-imperative.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/3-reasons-saas-security-is-imperative.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T11:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's fast-paced digital landscape, the widespread adoption of AI (Artificial Intelligence) tools is transforming the way organizations operate. From chatbots to generative AI models, these SaaS-based applications offer numerous benefits, from enhanced productivity to improved decision-making. Employees using AI tools experience the advantages of quick answers and accurate results, enabling]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The US Is Spying on the UN Secretary General]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/06/the-us-is-spying-on-the-un-secretary-general.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/06/the-us-is-spying-on-the-un-secretary-general.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T11:02:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The <i>Washington Post</i> is <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/national-security/2023/04/15/united-nations-leaked-documents/">reporting</a> that the US is spying on the UN Secretary General.</p>
<blockquote><p>The reports on Guterres appear to contain the secretary general&#8217;s personal conversations with aides regarding diplomatic encounters. They indicate that the United States relied on spying powers granted under the Foreign Intelligence Surveillance Act (FISA) to gather the intercepts.</p></blockquote>
<p>Lots of details about different conversations in the article, which are based on classified documents leaked on Discord by Jack Teixeira.</p>
<p>There will probably a lot of faux outrage at this, but spying on foreign leaders is a perfectly legitimate use of the NSA&#8217;s capabilities and authorities. (If the NSA didn&#8217;t spy on the UN Secretary General, we should fire it and replace it with a more competent NSA.) It&#8217;s the bulk surveillance of whole populations that should outrage us...</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WhatsApp Upgrades Proxy Feature Against Internet Shutdowns]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/whatsapp-upgrades-proxy-feature-against.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/whatsapp-upgrades-proxy-feature-against.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T09:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta's WhatsApp has rolled out updates to its proxy feature, allowing more flexibility in the kind of content that can be shared in conversations.
This includes the ability to send and receive images, voice notes, files, stickers and GIFs, WhatsApp told The Hacker News. The new features were first reported by BBC Persian.
Some of the other improvements include streamlined steps to simplify the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybercriminals Hijacking Vulnerable SSH Servers in New Proxyjacking Campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/cybercriminals-hijacking-vulnerable-ssh.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/cybercriminals-hijacking-vulnerable-ssh.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T08:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An active financially motivated campaign is targeting vulnerable SSH servers to covertly ensnare them into a proxy network.
"This is an active campaign in which the attacker leverages SSH for remote access, running malicious scripts that stealthily enlist victim servers into a peer-to-peer (P2P) proxy network, such as Peer2Profit or Honeygain," Akamai researcher Allen West said in a Thursday]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MITRE Unveils Top 25 Most Dangerous Software Weaknesses of 2023: Are You at Risk?]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/mitre-unveils-top-25-most-dangerous.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/mitre-unveils-top-25-most-dangerous.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T05:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MITRE has released its annual list of the Top 25 "most dangerous software weaknesses" for the year 2023.
"These weaknesses lead to serious vulnerabilities in software," the U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) said. "An attacker can often exploit these vulnerabilities to take control of an affected system, steal data, or prevent applications from working."
The list is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pepper and Embedded Insurance Partner on Cyber Insurance for Consumers, SMBs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/pepper-and-embedded-insurance-partner-on-cyber-insurance-for-consumers-smbs</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/pepper-and-embedded-insurance-partner-on-cyber-insurance-for-consumers-smbs"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T22:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have an IoT network powered by Pepper, you can now insure it through Embedded Insurance — even if your business is too small to support a SOC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Lawton, Contributing Writer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Wants Exposed Government Devices Remediated in 14 Days]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/cisa-wants-exposed-government-devices-remediated-14-days</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/cisa-wants-exposed-government-devices-remediated-14-days"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T21:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Though government agencies have hundreds of devices exposed to the open Internet, experts wonder if CISA is moving at the right pace.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IEC Standardization Leaders Convene in Amsterdam to Review Utility Interworking of Key Standards]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/ics-ot/iec-standardization-leaders-convene-in-amsterdam-to-review-utility-interworking-of-iec-61850-for-substations-iec-cim-for-control-centers-and-iec-62443-for-ot-cybersecurity</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/ics-ot/iec-standardization-leaders-convene-in-amsterdam-to-review-utility-interworking-of-iec-61850-for-substations-iec-cim-for-control-centers-and-iec-62443-for-ot-cybersecurity"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T21:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Objects to UK Bill That Would Break Encrypted Messaging]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/apple-objects-to-uk-bill-that-would-break-encrypted-messaging-</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/apple-objects-to-uk-bill-that-would-break-encrypted-messaging-"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T21:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New online safety bill could force encrypted messaging apps like iMessage and WhatsApp to scan for child abuse material, but platforms warn about privacy implications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Becky Bracken, Editor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Detail 4 SAP Bugs, Including Flaw in ABAP Kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/researchers-release-technical-details-pocs-for-4-sap-bugs</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/researchers-release-technical-details-pocs-for-4-sap-bugs"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T21:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Patches are available for three bugs, but with technical details and PoCs now available, threat actors can craft targeted attacks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Center for Internet Security, CREST Join Forces to Secure Organizations Globally]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/perimeter/center-for-internet-security-crest-join-forces-to-secure-organizations-globally</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/perimeter/center-for-internet-security-crest-join-forces-to-secure-organizations-globally"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T20:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New program provides organizations a way to show customers and partners their cybersecurity posture meets rigorous standards of CREST accreditation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TXOne Networks' Stellar Solution Safeguards Operational Stability for Organizations in Various Industries]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/ics-ot/txone-networks-stellar-solution-safeguards-operational-stability-for-organizations-in-semiconductors-manufacturing-oil-and-gas-banking-pharma-and-other-verticals</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/ics-ot/txone-networks-stellar-solution-safeguards-operational-stability-for-organizations-in-semiconductors-manufacturing-oil-and-gas-banking-pharma-and-other-verticals"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stellar leverages cyber physical system detection and response (CPSDR) to prevent unexpected system changes from impacting operational reliability and availability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WatchGuard Threat Lab Report Reveals New Browser-Based Social Engineering Trends]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/perimeter/watchguard-threat-lab-report-reveals-new-browser-based-social-engineering-trends</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/perimeter/watchguard-threat-lab-report-reveals-new-browser-based-social-engineering-trends"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T19:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key findings from the research also show three of the four new malware threats on this quarter's top-ten list originated in China and Russia, living-off-the-land attacks on the rise, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Employer Demand for Technology Workers Across Europe Remains on Firm Footing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/employer-demand-for-technology-workers-across-europe-remains-on-firm-footing</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/employer-demand-for-technology-workers-across-europe-remains-on-firm-footing"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T19:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than 950,000 job postings for tech positions in Q4 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybellum Unveils New Brand, Amplifying Commitment to Team-Centric Product Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/cybellum-unveils-new-brand-amplifying-commitment-to-team-centric-product-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/cybellum-unveils-new-brand-amplifying-commitment-to-team-centric-product-security"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T19:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new brand is launched alongside new product security platform capabilities such as a vulnerability management (VM) co-pilot and incident response investigation management, providing automation and workflows for the many teams involved in product security.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OTORIO Rolls Out Advanced Attack Graph Analysis for OT Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/ics-ot/otorio-rolls-out-advanced-attack-graph-analysis-for-ot-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/ics-ot/otorio-rolls-out-advanced-attack-graph-analysis-for-ot-security"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T19:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Innovative risk-based model enables better security measures.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Invary Raises $1.85M in Pre-Seed Funding to Close Critical Gap in Zero Trust Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/analytics/invary-raises-1-85m-in-pre-seed-funding-to-close-critical-gap-in-zero-trust-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/analytics/invary-raises-1-85m-in-pre-seed-funding-to-close-critical-gap-in-zero-trust-security"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T19:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company introduces a solution to restore trust in customers' existing cyber defense techstack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mend.io Launches Inaugural Open Source Reliability Leaderboard]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/mend-io-launches-inaugural-open-source-reliability-leaderboard</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/mend-io-launches-inaugural-open-source-reliability-leaderboard"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T19:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New report offers valuable resource to help organizations evaluate the safety and reliability of open-source packages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI-Enabled Voice Cloning Anchors Deepfaked Kidnapping]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/ai-enabled-voice-cloning-deepfaked-kidnapping</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/ai-enabled-voice-cloning-deepfaked-kidnapping"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T18:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Virtual kidnapping is just one of many new artificial intelligence attack types that threat actors have begun deploying, as voice cloning emerges as a potent new imposter tool.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thousands of Filipinos, Others Rescued From Forced Cybercrime Labor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/physical-security/filipinos-rescued-forced-cybercrime-labor</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/physical-security/filipinos-rescued-forced-cybercrime-labor"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T17:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Workers were lured in by false job promises from Facebook ads, only to be tricked into committing cybercrimes with no way out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity Is the Healthcare Your Organization Needs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/cybersecurity-is-the-healthcare-your-organization-needs</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/cybersecurity-is-the-healthcare-your-organization-needs"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Organizations should consider their security practices the same way people think about their well-being. Focus on staying healthy instead of finding a new pill for every security symptom you see.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Danahy, Vice President of Strategy and Innovation, NuHarbor Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Patent Office Data Spill Exposes Trademark Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/physical-security/us-patent-office-hacked-trademark-apps-accessed</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/physical-security/us-patent-office-hacked-trademark-apps-accessed"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T16:45:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Misconfiguration exposed the physical addresses of 60,000 patent filers over three years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From MuddyC3 to PhonyC2: Iran's MuddyWater Evolves with a New Cyber Weapon]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/from-muddyc3-to-phonyc2-irans.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/from-muddyc3-to-phonyc2-irans.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T16:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Iranian state-sponsored group dubbed MuddyWater has been attributed to a previously unseen command-and-control (C2) framework called PhonyC2 that's been put to use by the actor since 2021.
Evidence shows that the custom made, actively developed framework has been leveraged in the February 2023 attack on Technion, an Israeli research institute, cybersecurity firm Deep Instinct said in a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 Tips to Increase Hybrid and Multicloud Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/microsoft/3-tips-to-increase-hybrid-and-multicloud-security-</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/microsoft/3-tips-to-increase-hybrid-and-multicloud-security-"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T14:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As cloud adoption grows, organizations need to rethink their approaches to securing hybrid cloud and multicloud environments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Microsoft Security, Microsoft</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Redacting Documents with a Black Sharpie Doesn’t Work]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/06/redacting-documents-with-a-black-sharpie-doesnt-work.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/06/redacting-documents-with-a-black-sharpie-doesnt-work.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T14:37:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We have learned this lesson <a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/6/28/23777298/sony-ftc-microsoft-confidential-documents-marker-pen-scanner-oops">again</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>As part of the <a href="https://www.theverge.com/23768244/ftc-microsoft-activision-blizzard-case-news-announcements"><em>FTC v. Microsoft</em> hearing</a>, Sony supplied a document from PlayStation chief Jim Ryan that includes redacted details on the margins Sony shares with publishers, its <em>Call of Duty</em> revenues, and even the cost of developing some of its games.</p>
<p>It looks like someone redacted the documents with a black Sharpie ­ but when you scan them in, it’s easy to see some of the redactions. Oops.</p></blockquote>
<p>I don&#8217;t particularly care about the redacted information, but it&#8217;s there in the article.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When It Comes to Secure Coding, ChatGPT Is Quintessentially Human]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/when-it-comes-to-secure-coding-chatgpt-is-quintessentially-human</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/when-it-comes-to-secure-coding-chatgpt-is-quintessentially-human"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're still unprepared to fight the security bugs we already encounter, let alone new AI-borne issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pieter Danhieux, CEO, Chairman, &amp; Co-Founder, Secure Code Warrior</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Newbie Akira Ransomware Builds Momentum With Linux Shift]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/iot/akira-ransomware-builds-momentum-linux-shift</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/iot/akira-ransomware-builds-momentum-linux-shift"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T13:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new version of the double-extortion group's malware reflects a growing trend among ransomware actors to expand cybercrime opportunities beyond Windows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Montalbano, Contributor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fluhorse: Flutter-Based Android Malware Targets Credit Cards and 2FA Codes]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/fluhorse-flutter-based-android-malware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/fluhorse-flutter-based-android-malware.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T13:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have shared the inner workings of an Android malware family called Fluhorse.
The malware "represents a significant shift as it incorporates the malicious components directly within the Flutter code," Fortinet FortiGuard Labs researcher Axelle Apvrille said in a report published last week.
Fluhorse was first documented by Check Point in early May 2023, detailing its]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UAE, Israel Ink Pivotal Joint Cyber-Threat Intelligence Agreement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/uae-israel-joint-cyber-threat-intelligence-agreement</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/uae-israel-joint-cyber-threat-intelligence-agreement"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T13:06:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two Mideast nations that were at odds until recently have announced the "Crystal Ball" project, aimed at better protecting against cyberattacks via collaboration and knowledge sharing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Raywood, Senior Editor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Adds Eight Known Exploited Vulnerabilities to Catalog]]></title>
        <id>/node/18386</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/06/29/cisa-adds-eight-known-exploited-vulnerabilities-catalog"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CISA has added eight new vulnerabilities to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog, based on evidence of active exploitation.
CVE-2019-17621 D-Link DIR-859 Router Command Execution Vulnerability
CVE-2019-20500 D-Link DWL-2600AP Access Point Command Injection Vulnerability
CVE-2021-25487 Samsung Mobile Devices Out-of-Bounds Read Vulnerability
CVE-2021-25489 Samsung Mobile Devices Improper Input Validation Vulnerability
CVE-2021-25394 Samsung Mobile Devices Race Condition Vulnerability
CVE-2021-25395 Samsung Mobile Devices Race Condition Vulnerability
CVE-2021-25371 Samsung Mobile Devices Unspecified Vulnerability
CVE-2021-25372 Samsung Mobile Devices Improper Boundary Check Vulnerability
These types of vulnerabilities are frequent attack vectors for malicious cyber actors and pose significant risks to the federal enterprise. Note: To view other newly added vulnerabilities in the catalog, click on the arrow in the "Date Added to Catalog" column—which will sort by descending dates.
Binding Operational Directive (BOD) 22-01: Reducing the Significant Risk of Known Exploited Vulnerabilities established the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog as a living list of known Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVEs) that carry significant risk to the federal enterprise. BOD 22-01 requires Federal Civilian Executive Branch (FCEB) agencies to remediate identified vulnerabilities by the due date to protect FCEB networks against active threats. See the BOD 22-01 Fact Sheet for more information.
Although BOD 22-01 only applies to FCEB agencies, CISA strongly urges all organizations to reduce their exposure to cyberattacks by prioritizing timely remediation of Catalog vulnerabilities as part of their vulnerability management practice. CISA will continue to add vulnerabilities to the catalog that meet the specified criteria.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2023 CWE Top 25 Most Dangerous Software Weaknesses]]></title>
        <id>/node/18393</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/06/29/2023-cwe-top-25-most-dangerous-software-weaknesses"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Homeland Security Systems Engineering and Development Institute, sponsored by the Department of Homeland Security and operated by MITRE, has released the 2023 Common Weakness Enumeration (CWE) Top 25 Most Dangerous Software Weaknesses. The CWE Top 25 is calculated by analyzing public vulnerability data in the National Vulnerability Data (NVD) for root cause mappings to CWE weaknesses for the previous two calendar years. These weaknesses lead to serious vulnerabilities in software. An attacker can often exploit these vulnerabilities to take control of an affected system, steal data, or prevent applications from working. 
The 2023 CWE Top 25 also incorporates updated weakness data for recent CVE records in the dataset that are part of CISA’s Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog (KEV). 
CISA encourages developers and product security response teams to review the CWE Top 25 and evaluate recommended mitigations to determine those most suitable to adopt. Over the coming weeks, the CWE program will be publishing a series of further articles on the CWE Top 25 methodology, vulnerability mapping trends, and other useful information that help illustrate how vulnerability management plays an important role in Shifting the Balance of Cybersecurity Risk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Releases Nine Industrial Control Systems Advisories]]></title>
        <id>/node/18394</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/06/29/cisa-releases-nine-industrial-control-systems-advisories"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CISA released nine Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisories on June 29, 2023. These advisories provide timely information about current security issues, vulnerabilities, and exploits surrounding ICS. 
ICSA-23-180-01 Delta Electronics InfraSuite Device Master
ICSA-23-180-02 Schneider Electric EcoStruxure
ICSA-23-180-03 Ovarro TBox RTUs
ICSA-23-180-04 Mitsubishi Electric MELSEC-F Series
ICSMA-23-180-01 Medtronic Paceart Optima System
ICSA-19-120-01 Rockwell Automation CompactLogix 5370 (Update A)
ICSA-20-245-01 Mitsubishi Electric Multiple Products (Update F)
ICSA-22-333-05 Mitsubishi Electric FA Engineering Software (Update B)
ICSA-23-171-02 Enphase Installer Toolkit Android App (Update A)
CISA encourages users and administrators to review the newly released ICS advisories for technical details and mitigations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Right Way to Enhance CTI with AI (Hint: It's the Data)]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/the-right-way-to-enhance-cti-with-ai.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/the-right-way-to-enhance-cti-with-ai.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T10:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cyber threat intelligence is an effective weapon in the ongoing battle to protect digital assets and infrastructure - especially when combined with AI. But AI is only as good as the data feeding it. Access to unique, underground sources is key.
Threat Intelligence offers tremendous value to people and companies. At the same time, its ability to address organizations' cybersecurity needs and the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean Hacker Group Andariel Strikes with New EarlyRat Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/north-korean-hacker-group-andariel.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/north-korean-hacker-group-andariel.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T10:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The North Korea-aligned threat actor known as Andariel leveraged a previously undocumented malware called EarlyRat in phishing attacks, adding another piece to the group's wide-ranging toolset.
"Andariel infects machines by executing a Log4j exploit, which, in turn, downloads further malware from the command-and-control (C2) server," Kaspersky said in a new report.
Also called Silent Chollima]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android Spy App LetMeSpy Suffers Major Data Breach, Exposing Users' Personal Data]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/android-spy-app-letmespy-suffers-major.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/android-spy-app-letmespy-suffers-major.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T10:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Android-based phone monitoring app LetMeSpy has disclosed a security breach that allowed an unauthorized third-party to steal sensitive data associated with thousands of Android users.
"As a result of the attack, the criminals gained access to email addresses, telephone numbers and the content of messages collected on accounts," LetMeSpy said in an announcement on its website, noting the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Security Flaw in Social Login Plugin for WordPress Exposes Users' Accounts]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/critical-security-flaw-in-social-login.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/critical-security-flaw-in-social-login.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T07:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A critical security flaw has been disclosed in miniOrange's Social Login and Register plugin for WordPress that could enable a malicious actor to log in as any user-provided information about email address is already known.
Tracked as CVE-2023-2982 (CVSS score: 9.8), the authentication bypass flaw impacts all versions of the plugin, including and prior to 7.6.4. It was addressed on June 14, 2023]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Newly Uncovered ThirdEye Windows-Based Malware Steals Sensitive Data]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/newly-uncovered-thirdeye-windows-based.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/newly-uncovered-thirdeye-windows-based.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T04:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A previously undocumented Windows-based information stealer called ThirdEye has been discovered in the wild with capabilities to harvest sensitive data from infected hosts.
Fortinet FortiGuard Labs, which made the discovery, said it found the malware in an executable that masqueraded as a PDF file with a Russian name "CMK Правила оформления больничных листов.pdf.exe," which translates to "CMK]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian Spies, War Ministers Reliant on Cybercrime in Pariah State]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/russia-reliant-on-cybercrime-as-international-pariah</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/russia-reliant-on-cybercrime-as-international-pariah"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T22:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Swiss intelligence warns that Russia ramping up cyberattacks on infrastructure and cyber espionage as on-the-ground options evaporate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Becky Bracken, Editor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1Password Launches Unlock With Single Sign-On for OIDC-Supported Identity Providers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/1password-launches-unlock-with-single-sign-on-for-oidc-supported-identity-providers</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/1password-launches-unlock-with-single-sign-on-for-oidc-supported-identity-providers"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T22:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enterprises can now integrate 1Password with Duo, OneLogin, JumpCloud, Ping Identity, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Ways Cybersecurity Is Gut-Checking the ChatGPT Frenzy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/perimeter/cybersecurity-gut-checking-chatgpt-ai-chatbots-chatgpt</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/perimeter/cybersecurity-gut-checking-chatgpt-ai-chatbots-chatgpt"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T21:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Generative AI chatbots like ChatGPT are the buzziest of the buzzy right now, but the cyber community is starting to mature when it comes to assessing where it should fit into our lives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tara Seals, Managing Editor, News, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Npm Plagued With 'Manifest Confusion' Malware-Hiding Weakness]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/npm-manifest-confusion-malware-hiding-weakness</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/npm-manifest-confusion-malware-hiding-weakness"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T20:53:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The popular package manager for software developers has been vulnerable to this attack vector for a while, and negligent in fixing the problem, according to a former employee.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LetMeSpy Phone-Tracking App Hacked, Revealing User Data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/letmespy-phone-tracking-app-hacked-revealing-user-data</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/letmespy-phone-tracking-app-hacked-revealing-user-data"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T20:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With at least 13,000 compromised devices in the data leak, it is still unknown who the threat actor is or whether or not victims will be personally notified.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Social Engineering Adds Depth to Red Team Exercises]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/social-engineering-adds-depth-to-red-team-exercises</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/social-engineering-adds-depth-to-red-team-exercises"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T18:50:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Because social engineering usually succeeds, companies need to test whether their defenses can block adversaries that gain employees' trust.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Lemos, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Astrix Security Raises $25M in Series A Funding]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/astrix-security-raises-25m-in-series-a-funding</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/astrix-security-raises-25m-in-series-a-funding"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T18:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The investment will allow enterprises to further secure non-human identities and safely leverage the soaring adoption of third-party apps and Generative AI services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cato Networks Revolutionizes Network Security With Real-Time, Machine Learning-Powered Protection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/perimeter/cato-networks-revolutionizes-network-security-with-real-time-machine-learning-powered-protection</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/perimeter/cato-networks-revolutionizes-network-security-with-real-time-machine-learning-powered-protection"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T18:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The combination of data science expertise, cloud resources, and Cato's vast data lake enables real-time, ML-powered protection against evasive cyberattacks, reducing risk and improving security.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malwarebytes ChatGPT Survey Reveals 81% are Concerned by Generative AI Security Risks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/malwarebytes-chatgpt-survey-reveals-81-are-concerned-by-generative-ai-security-risks</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/malwarebytes-chatgpt-survey-reveals-81-are-concerned-by-generative-ai-security-risks"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T17:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Survey also uncovers 63% of respondents distrust ChatGPT while 51% question AI's ability to improve Internet safety.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FIDO Alliance Publishes Guidance for Deploying Passkeys in the Enterprise]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/fido-alliance-publishes-guidance-for-deploying-passkeys-in-the-enterprise</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/fido-alliance-publishes-guidance-for-deploying-passkeys-in-the-enterprise"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T17:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Half-day virtual Authenticate Summit to educate on how passkeys can fit into a variety of enterprise environments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia's Cyber Capabilities Ranked Second Globally]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/saudi-arabia-cyber-capabilities-ranked-second-globally</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-global/saudi-arabia-cyber-capabilities-ranked-second-globally"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T16:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia is one of the world's leaders in cybersecurity development and preparedness, according to the latest rankings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generative AI Projects Pose Major Cybersecurity Risk to Enterprises]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/generative-ai-projects-cybersecurity-risks-enterprises</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/generative-ai-projects-cybersecurity-risks-enterprises"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T16:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers' enthusiasm for ChatGPT and other LLM tools leaves most organizations largely unprepared to defend against the vulnerabilities that the nascent technology creates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Montalbano, Contributor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alert: New Electromagnetic Attacks on Drones Could Let Attackers Take Control]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/alert-new-electromagnetic-attacks-on.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/alert-new-electromagnetic-attacks-on.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T15:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drones that don't have any known security weaknesses could be the target of electromagnetic fault injection (EMFI) attacks, potentially enabling a threat actor to achieve arbitrary code execution and compromise their functionality and safety.
The research comes from IOActive, which found that it is "feasible to compromise the targeted device by injecting a specific EM glitch at the right time]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 Strategies for Bringing Rigor to Software Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/3-strategies-for-bringing-rigor-to-software-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/3-strategies-for-bringing-rigor-to-software-security"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the National Cybersecurity Strategy planning to add real teeth into enforcement actions, software vendors have extra incentive to reduce applications' security debt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Eng, Chief Research Officer, Veracode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CryptosLabs Scam Ring Targets French-Speaking Investors, Rakes in €480 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/cryptoslabs-scam-ring-targets-french.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/cryptoslabs-scam-ring-targets-french.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T13:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have exposed the workings of a scam ring called CryptosLabs that's estimated to have made €480 million in illegal profits by targeting users in French-speaking individuals in France, Belgium, and Luxembourg since April 2018.
The syndicate's massive fake investment schemes primarily involve impersonating 40 well-known banks, fin-techs, asset management firms, and crypto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Source LLM Projects Likely Insecure, Risky to Use]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/tech-trends/open-source-llm-project-insecure-risky-use</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/tech-trends/open-source-llm-project-insecure-risky-use"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New LLM-based projects typically become successful in a short period of time, but the security posture of these generative AI projects are very low, making them extremely unsafe to use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA and NSA Release Joint Guidance on Defending Continuous Integration/Continuous Delivery (CI/CD) Environments]]></title>
        <id>/node/18385</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/06/28/cisa-and-nsa-release-joint-guidance-defending-continuous-integrationcontinuous-delivery-cicd"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, CISA, together with the National Security Agency (NSA), released a Cybersecurity Information Sheet (CSI) to provide recommendations and best practices for organizations to strengthen the security of their CI/CD pipelines against the threat of malicious cyber actors (MCAs).
Recognizing the various types of security threats that could affect CI/CD operations and taking steps to defend against each one is critical in securing a CI/CD environment. Organizations will find in this guide a list of common risks found in CI/CD pipelines and attack surfaces that could be exploited and threaten network security.     
CISA and NSA encourage all organizations to review this CSI and apply the recommended actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stalkerware Vendor Hacked]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/06/stalkerware-vendor-hacked.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2023/06/stalkerware-vendor-hacked.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T11:17:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The stalkerware company LetMeSpy has been <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2023/06/27/letmespy-hacked-spyware-thousands/">hacked</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>TechCrunch reviewed the leaked data, which included years of victims&#8217; call logs and text messages dating back to 2013.</p>
<p>The database we reviewed contained current records on at least 13,000 compromised devices, though some of the devices shared little to no data with LetMeSpy. (LetMeSpy claims to delete data after two months of account inactivity.)</p>
<p>[&#8230;]</p>
<p>The database also contained over 13,400 location data points for several thousand victims. Most of the location data points are centered over population hotspots, suggesting the majority of victims are located in the United States, India and Western Africa...</p></blockquote>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Things CISOs Need to Know About Securing OT Environments]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/5-things-cisos-need-to-know-about.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/5-things-cisos-need-to-know-about.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T10:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For too long the cybersecurity world focused exclusively on information technology (IT), leaving operational technology (OT) to fend for itself. Traditionally, few industrial enterprises had dedicated cybersecurity leaders. Any security decisions that arose fell to the plant and factory managers, who are highly skilled technical experts in other areas but often lack cybersecurity training or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8Base Ransomware Spikes in Activity, Threatens U.S. and Brazilian Businesses]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/8base-ransomware-spikes-in-activity.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/8base-ransomware-spikes-in-activity.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T10:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A ransomware threat called 8Base that has been operating under the radar for over a year has been attributed to a "massive spike in activity" in May and June 2023.
"The group utilizes encryption paired with 'name-and-shame' techniques to compel their victims to pay their ransoms," VMware Carbon Black researchers Deborah Snyder and Fae Carlisle said in a report shared with The Hacker News. "8Base]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical SQL Injection Flaws Expose Gentoo Soko to Remote Code Execution]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/critical-sql-injection-flaws-expose.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/critical-sql-injection-flaws-expose.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T07:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities have been disclosed in Gentoo Soko that could lead to remote code execution (RCE) on vulnerable systems.
"These SQL injections happened despite the use of an Object-Relational Mapping (ORM) library and prepared statements," SonarSource researcher Thomas Chauchefoin said, adding they could result in RCE on Soko because of a "misconfiguration of the database.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking Barriers: Aditi’s Journey Through Sight Loss to Microsoft AI Innovator]]></title>
        <id>https://msrc.microsoft.com/blog/2023/06/breaking-barriers-aditis-journey-through-sight-loss-to-microsoft-ai-innovator/</id>
        <link href="https://msrc.microsoft.com/blog/2023/06/breaking-barriers-aditis-journey-through-sight-loss-to-microsoft-ai-innovator/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Facts about Aditi Shah:
Tools she uses: Aditi’s main tool is JAWS, a screen reader from Freedom Scientific, which she touts as the best in the market. This tool has made her digital life more manageable, enabling her to perform almost any task independently.
Aditi also uses Seeing AI, a Microsoft app that she uses for important life tasks, like reading her mail, providing descriptions of different products, identifying colors for her outfits, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Microsoft Security Response Center</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UCLA, Siemens Among Latest Victims of Relentless MOVEit Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/ucla-siemens-among-latest-victims-of-relentless-moveit-attacks</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/ucla-siemens-among-latest-victims-of-relentless-moveit-attacks"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cl0p ransomware group uses its Dark Web leak site to identify five new victims of MOVEit cyberattacks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Becky Bracken, Editor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jscrambler Launches JavaScript Scanner for PCI DSS 4.0 Compliance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/jscrambler-launches-javascript-scanner-for-pci-dss-4-0-compliance</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/jscrambler-launches-javascript-scanner-for-pci-dss-4-0-compliance"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T01:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The free tool aims to help organizations meet the requirements of the new version of the payment standard, which takes effect next March.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting Small Businesses From Ransomware on a Budget]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/edge/protecting-a-small-business-from-ransomware-on-a-budget</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/edge/protecting-a-small-business-from-ransomware-on-a-budget"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One ransomware attack can be devastating for a small or midsize business. Here are four solid survival tips to ensure it doesn't turn into a disaster.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sue Poremba, Contributing Writer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cequence Security Adds Generative AI to API Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/cequence-security-adds-generative-ai-to-api-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/dr-tech/cequence-security-adds-generative-ai-to-api-security"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cequence's latest updates to its Unified API Protection platform help organizations reduce the time needed to create API security testing plans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mockingjay Slips By EDR Tools With Process Injection Technique]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/mockingjay-edr-tools-process-injection-technique</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/mockingjay-edr-tools-process-injection-technique"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T21:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By leveraging misconfigured DLLs instead of EDR-monitored APIs, this new technique injects malicious code into running processes, completely evading endpoint security.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trans-Rights Hacktivists Steal City of Ft. Worth's Data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/trans-rights-hacktivists-steal-fort-worth-data</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/trans-rights-hacktivists-steal-fort-worth-data"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T21:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a move to embarrass the city, hacking group known as SiegedSec accessed thousands of files with administrator logins, but it's making no ransom demands.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pilot Applicant Information for American, Southwest Hacked]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/pilot-applicant-information-for-american-southwest-hacked-</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/pilot-applicant-information-for-american-southwest-hacked-"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T18:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The attack exposed personal information from pilot applicants, prompting both airlines to ditch their third-party provider and move services internally.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Most Enterprise SIEMs Blind to MITRE ATT&CK Tactics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/analytics/enterprise-siem-blind-mitre-attack-coverage</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/analytics/enterprise-siem-blind-mitre-attack-coverage"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T18:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Organizations are largely deluded about their own security postures, according to an analysis, with the average SIEM failing to detect a whopping 76% of attacker TTPs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Montalbano, Contributor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why the FDA's SBOM Mandate Changes the Game for OSS Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/fda-sbom-mandate-changes-oss-security</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/fda-sbom-mandate-changes-oss-security"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new FDA software bill of materials (SBOM) guidelines for medical devices could have broad impact on the healthcare industry and the broader open source ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jenn Gile, Head of Product Marketing, F5 NGINX</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Cyber Funding Flows for Rural Water Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/ics-ot/cyber-funding-rural-water-systems</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/ics-ot/cyber-funding-rural-water-systems"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T16:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The $7.5 million in new funds from the Cybersecurity for Rural Water Systems Act of 2023 is not just a drop in the bucket for crucially important rural water systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jai Vijayan, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Mockingjay Process Injection Technique Could Let Malware Evade Detection]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/new-mockingjay-process-injection.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/new-mockingjay-process-injection.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T14:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new process injection technique dubbed Mockingjay could be exploited by threat actors to bypass security solutions to execute malicious code on compromised systems.
"The injection is executed without space allocation, setting permissions or even starting a thread," Security Joes researchers Thiago Peixoto, Felipe Duarte, and Ido Naor said in a report shared with The Hacker News. "The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Ongoing Campaign Targets npm Ecosystem with Unique Execution Chain]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/new-ongoing-campaign-targets-npm.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/new-ongoing-campaign-targets-npm.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a new ongoing campaign aimed at the npm ecosystem that leverages a unique execution chain to deliver an unknown payload to targeted systems.
"The packages in question seem to be published in pairs, each pair working in unison to fetch additional resources which are subsequently decoded and/or executed," software supply chain security firm Phylum said in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Preventing Cyberattacks on Schools Starts With K–12 Cybersecurity Education]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/preventing-cyberattacks-schools-k-12-cybersecurity-education</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/preventing-cyberattacks-schools-k-12-cybersecurity-education"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By investing in a strong future cybersecurity workforce, we can prevent future attacks on US critical infrastructure before they occur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laurie Salvail, Executive Director, CYBER.ORG</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond Asset Discovery: How Attack Surface Management Prioritizes Vulnerability Remediation]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/beyond-asset-discovery-how-attack.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/06/beyond-asset-discovery-how-attack.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T11:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the business environment becomes increasingly connected, organizations’ attack surfaces continue to expand, making it challenging to map and secure both known and unknown assets. In particular, unknown assets present security challenges related to shadow IT, misconfigurations, ineffective scan coverage, among others. 
Given attack surface sprawl and evolving threats, many organizations are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genworth Financial Reports Data Breach Leaking SSNs Belonging to 2.7M Policyholders and Customers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/genworth-financial-reports-data-breach-leaking-social-security-numbers-belonging-to-as-many-as-2-7m-policyholders-and-customers</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/genworth-financial-reports-data-breach-leaking-social-security-numbers-belonging-to-as-many-as-2-7m-policyholders-and-customers"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T21:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SolarWinds Execs Targeted by SEC, CEO Vows to Fight]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/operations/solarwinds-execs-targeted-sec-ceo-fight</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/operations/solarwinds-execs-targeted-sec-ceo-fight"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T21:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CEO says SEC penalties related to the 2020 SolarWinds supply chain attacks are unwarranted and is ready to mount a defense to any legal actions against the company or its employees.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Becky Bracken, Editor, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China's 'Volt Typhoon' APT Turns to Zoho ManageEngine for Fresh Cyberattacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/china-volt-typhoon-apt-zoho-manageengine-fresh-cyberattacks</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/cloud/china-volt-typhoon-apt-zoho-manageengine-fresh-cyberattacks"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T21:05:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent campaign shows that the politically motivated threat actor has more tricks up its sleeve than previously known, targeting an old RCE flaw and wiping logs to cover their tracks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Nelson, Contributing Writer, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter Celeb Account Hacker Heads to Jail for 5 Years]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/twitter-celeb-account-hacker-jail-5-years</id>
        <link href="https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/twitter-celeb-account-hacker-jail-5-years"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T21:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Extradited from Spain, PlugWalkJoe has been sentenced in US court and is now headed to federal prison on a raft of charges related to account hijacking and cyber stalking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dark Reading Staff, Dark Reading</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerability Summary for the Week of June 19, 2023]]></title>
        <id>/node/18378</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/bulletins/sb23-177"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T11:44:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CISA Vulnerability Bulletin provides a summary of new vulnerabilities that have been recorded by the National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) National Vulnerability Database (NVD) in the past week. NVD is sponsored by CISA. In some cases, the vulnerabilities in the bulletin may not yet have assigned CVSS scores. Please visit NVD for updated vulnerability entries, which include CVSS scores once they are available.
Vulnerabilities are based on the Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVE) vulnerability naming standard and are organized according to severity, determined by the Common Vulnerability Scoring System (CVSS) standard. The division of high, medium, and low severities correspond to the following scores:
High: vulnerabilities with a CVSS base score of 7.0–10.0
Medium…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UEFI: 5 Recommendations for Securing and Restoring Trust]]></title>
        <id>http://insights.sei.cmu.edu/blog/uefi-5-recommendations-for-securing-restoring-trust/</id>
        <link href="http://insights.sei.cmu.edu/blog/uefi-5-recommendations-for-securing-restoring-trust/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post expands on concerns brought to light from recent UEFI attacks, such as BlackLotus, and highlights 5 recommendations to secure and restore trust in the UEFI ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SEI Blog | CERT/CC Vulnerabilities</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerability Summary for the Week of June 12, 2023]]></title>
        <id>/node/18354</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/bulletins/sb23-171"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T13:57:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CISA Vulnerability Bulletin provides a summary of new vulnerabilities that have been recorded by the National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) National Vulnerability Database (NVD) in the past week. NVD is sponsored by CISA. In some cases, the vulnerabilities in the bulletin may not yet have assigned CVSS scores. Please visit NVD for updated vulnerability entries, which include CVSS scores once they are available.
Vulnerabilities are based on the Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVE) vulnerability naming standard and are organized according to severity, determined by the Common Vulnerability Scoring System (CVSS) standard. The division of high, medium, and low severities correspond to the following scores:
High: vulnerabilities with a CVSS base score of 7.0–10.0
Medium…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Potential Risk of Privilege Escalation in Azure AD Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://msrc.microsoft.com/blog/2023/06/potential-risk-of-privilege-escalation-in-azure-ad-applications/</id>
        <link href="https://msrc.microsoft.com/blog/2023/06/potential-risk-of-privilege-escalation-in-azure-ad-applications/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summary Summary Microsoft has developed mitigations for an insecure anti-pattern used in Azure AD (AAD) applications highlighted by Descope, and reported to Microsoft, where use of the email claim from access tokens for authorization can lead to an escalation of privilege. An attacker can falsify the email claim in tokens issued to applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Microsoft Security Response Center</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Response to Layer 7 Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://msrc.microsoft.com/blog/2023/06/microsoft-response-to-layer-7-distributed-denial-of-service-ddos-attacks/</id>
        <link href="https://msrc.microsoft.com/blog/2023/06/microsoft-response-to-layer-7-distributed-denial-of-service-ddos-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-16T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summary Summary Beginning in early June 2023, Microsoft identified surges in traffic against some services that temporarily impacted availability. Microsoft promptly opened an investigation and subsequently began tracking ongoing DDoS activity by the threat actor that Microsoft tracks as Storm-1359.
These attacks likely rely on access to multiple virtual private servers (VPS) in conjunction with rented cloud infrastructure, open proxies, and DDoS tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Microsoft Security Response Center</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MAR-10443863-1.v1 CVE-2017-9248 Exploitation in U.S. Government IIS Server]]></title>
        <id>/node/18332</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/analysis-reports/ar23-166a"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T21:28:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summary
Description
CISA received three files for analysis. The files included three webshells written in PHP: Hypertext Preprocessor (PHP), Active Server Pages Extended (ASPX), and .NET Dynamic-Link Library (DLL). The sample “sd.php” is highly obfuscated and uses rot13 algorithm, zlib for compression and base64 encoding for obfuscation. The “osker.aspx” webshell code was padded with junk code. The .NET DLL webshell is a .NET compiled version of osker.aspx. The samples are interactive webshells and have the ability to upload and manage files, create directories and files, and execute commands on the target machine.
For more information about this compromise, see Joint Cybersecurity Advisory Threat Actors Exploit Progress Telerik Vulnerabilities in Multiple U.S. Government IIS Servers
Downl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft mitigates set of cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in Azure Bastion and Azure Container Registry]]></title>
        <id>https://msrc.microsoft.com/blog/2023/06/microsoft-mitigates-set-of-cross-site-scripting-xss-vulnerabilities-in-azure-bastion-and-azure-container-registry/</id>
        <link href="https://msrc.microsoft.com/blog/2023/06/microsoft-mitigates-set-of-cross-site-scripting-xss-vulnerabilities-in-azure-bastion-and-azure-container-registry/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summary Summary Microsoft recently mitigated a set of cross-site scripting vulnerabilities affecting Azure Bastion and Azure Container Registry (ACR). Exploitation of these vulnerabilities could have potentially allowed for an unauthorized user to gain access to a target user’s session within the compromised Azure service, and subsequently lead to data tampering or resource modification.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Microsoft Security Response Center</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Ransomware Threat Actors: LockBit]]></title>
        <id>/node/18313</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/cybersecurity-advisories/aa23-165a"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T16:22:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUMMARY
In 2022, LockBit was the most deployed ransomware variant across the world and continues to be prolific in 2023. Since January 2020, affiliates using LockBit have attacked organizations of varying sizes across an array of critical infrastructure sectors, including financial services, food and agriculture, education, energy, government and emergency services, healthcare, manufacturing, and transportation. LockBit ransomware operation functions as a Ransomware-as-a-Service (RaaS) model where affiliates are recruited to conduct ransomware attacks using LockBit ransomware tools and infrastructure. Due to the large number of unconnected affiliates in the operation, LockBit ransomware attacks vary significantly in observed tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs). This variance in obse…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerability Summary for the Week of June 5, 2023]]></title>
        <id>/node/18307</id>
        <link href="https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/bulletins/sb23-163"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T14:56:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CISA Vulnerability Bulletin provides a summary of new vulnerabilities that have been recorded by the National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) National Vulnerability Database (NVD) in the past week. NVD is sponsored by CISA. In some cases, the vulnerabilities in the bulletin may not yet have assigned CVSS scores. Please visit NVD for updated vulnerability entries, which include CVSS scores once they are available.
Vulnerabilities are based on the Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVE) vulnerability naming standard and are organized according to severity, determined by the Common Vulnerability Scoring System (CVSS) standard. The division of high, medium, and low severities correspond to the following scores:
High: vulnerabilities with a CVSS base score of 7.0–10.0
Medium…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>